<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this is absolutely awesome....till date this is the best smart phone I have ever seen...its too good and too smart...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesomeness Redefined.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its not a phone. Its iPhone. Totally different smartphone as compare to others available in the market in terms of performance, stability, design, multitasking.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Happy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very satisfied with the service and the quality&lt;br&gt;just love it man&lt;br&gt;keep it up mmmm&lt;br&gt;thank u&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple IPhone 5S - You cannot get better then this&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is an excellent product from Apple.&lt;br&gt;Even being at the original MRP of 53,500, I got this for 46,969 and over and above this, I got a cash back of 2,000 by using American Express Credit Card.  The ultimately I got this phone at 44,969 which you will never get anywhere at least today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am very happy with Apple, Amazon and American Express. AAA!!! What a coincidence!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple rockz!!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A pint sized Powerhouse!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A powerhouse really, deceptively small in size.  A breeze to use &amp;amp; the touch id works perfectly.  The only thing that could possibly be considered as an enhancement is a larger screen, and expect apple will yield in the next iPhone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A premium phone with lots of flow.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;While I buying a premium phone , I have not imagine the phone will have bugs ... bugs and lots of bugs. People those are HAPPY with iphone , I think they have not tried other phone, trust me a LUMIA 520 , Rs. 7000 phone has far better camera, email app, map and interface.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; if use camera with FLASH it generate HAZE images only. trust me the camera is worst , if have a low cost nokia lumia 520 which has far better camera than iphone 5s.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; The gps is not accurate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; The free games app are full of advertise as compare to android or windows free apps has limited advertise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; All apps in terms of memory size are very big.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; Battery drain rapidly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;gt; As claimed about fast internet speed, it works SLOW as compare to android or windows phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apple charging a premium cost for the phone and still you are not able to produce a stable feature phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very disappointing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Iphone5s&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Really disappointing as the battery don't keep charge for the whole day.&lt;br&gt;I would never recommend this to anyone&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCD38?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Gold, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best phone ever. I have used windows, android phone in the past. From my experience iOS is the best mobile platform. Once you start using apple product you will never look for any other brand. Phone's design is sleek, beautiful, vary light weight. Camera quality is best. I am vary much satisfied with my first apple device. The Screen size is perfect because at 4 inch you can operate your phone with single hand. Battery charges vary fast. Overall i will recommend this product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I phone 5s mother of all smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I m happy with the phone 5s and also two days service given is awesome thanks you amazon ....................!!!!!!!!!!!!!!' Love you amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Service And Price.. Thankyou&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Far Better then other sites&lt;br&gt;trusted site&lt;br&gt;and i got everything here.&lt;br&gt;Good Service And Price..&lt;br&gt;Thank you .. ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best mobile handset&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;as usual great buying experince with amazon&lt;br&gt;super fast next day service&lt;br&gt;And for apple iphone i don`t have any words&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Serivce is so good....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I happy with service.  They give in time. And product purchase from amazon is always good.&lt;br&gt;I purchase the iphone 5s from amazon is good in quaility.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Gold colour looks brilliant and lucrative. EMI facility is an advantage. After all iphone does not have any competitor. Prompt delivery. Rate it 5*&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very nice product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Genuine buy and less price, i love to buy from amazon. thank you&lt;br&gt;five star from me to amazon :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth the money spend&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the product at the best of price and that too at a quick time. Way to go........ Amazon rocks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very nice service :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought it on 30th and got it the next day without any worries. Very nice service, safely packed overall fuss free service.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good built quality,good photos  performance is very good , Overall system is reliable and sturdy Only downside is battery life&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCD38?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Gold, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;its worth what it is&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i like it.....and forgot samsung after using it. it works well for me and it is the premium smartphone .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone....The Apple iPhone 5s 16GB features a 4-inch Retina multi-touch that gives you an enhanced user experience. What makes this advanced smartphone from Apple distinct from other phones is its precision construction mark in a sleek glass and metal golden colour aluminium casing.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;First in Class!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No need to review this product. Classic !!  This is a piece of art made by the APPLE company !!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A wonderful product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;An excellent product from Apple ... overpriced though. It was for my daughter who is an apple fan .. so nothing else would do. Got the IMEI checked on Apple and confirmed genuineness of product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Was going mad to purchase iphone 5s and was looking out for some cashback offers all around. However amazon gave me a best price for the phone. Thums up&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone and amazon is best website for buy any thing ....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is funtestic and Amazon gave me this in great prize .... Wow Thanks Amazon I love iphone 5&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SATISFYING&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazon has an excellent service for a great phone. now waiting for the rs 2000. refund on my SBI credit card which amazon offered at the time of purchase.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Mobile Ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;So many persons reviewed that this 5S is not working properly and it has some defects like quick drainage of battery and some Touch ID problem. But I got this recently from amazon.in in a attractive price and quick delivery.&lt;br&gt;After Using this only i found that no such problems occurred on mine. So the persons who reviewed some negative may be have a defective piece. So you can have trust to buy this one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;THE BEST THERE IS!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Forget ANDROID......this is the best phone on the market, period. People may complain about it being expensive, but so are mercedes and bmw's. Buy this without any 2nd thoughts....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;So fast so good !! as it looks ..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Thanks Amazon team .. never knew its such a wonderful buying experience .. by the time I reached home after ordering .. it was there...  wow!!  I was bit in dilemma Android Vs IOS - was reading lot of reviews all around for the same.. So I decided to buy both - one in store purchase and another online purchase .. Android and IOS both are great techs ..  enjoying best of both... I phone still carries status symbol...  thanks Amzon !!  100 star for you all .. No human touch except delivery boy !!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCD38?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Gold, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Iphone 5s is Swiss watch of phones&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When we buy a swiss watch, What we get for such high price is the Quality, Design and Perfection. The same is applied to iPhone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. I love its design over any other phone.&lt;br&gt;2. UI is so clean, clear and with useful features&lt;br&gt;3. Data/Charging cable that can be used in any direction is a unique feature.&lt;br&gt;4. Fingerprint scanner is faster than my office attendance machine and that too from any angle.&lt;br&gt;5. Exclusive features like Fingerprint and 64 bit Desktop Class processor in which competition is lagging about a year&lt;br&gt;6. 120 fps slo mo is awesome. It replaced old Go Pro camera.&lt;br&gt;7. Dual flash also produce excellent lighting results.&lt;br&gt;8. Airplay offer audiophile quality audio transmission to Airplay speaker.&lt;br&gt;9. M7 sensor help my NIKE+ move app to be more accurate for health tracking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;all in all The best phone that i can have&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The worst retailer to buy from&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had purchased a 5s on my birthday from Big Retail which was defective. Such a huge disappointment from retailer!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;One of the Best phone out there in the market&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Product was delivered as described in the product description and handel with care during delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to Amazon, I have got the great deal and smooth transaction made my shopping experience even better.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone want to buy an iPhone 5s definitely go for Amazon :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone book issues&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is well made but complicated in comparison. Have some issues with Phone book memory. Unable to feed phone numbers and addresses. Shall wait for more time to understand the issue involved&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone, no words to describe. Perfection. Some think that Android is the best with all best configuration and plenty of features. And they debate saying its cheap too. For all of that opinion, people who cannot afford apple wil always says that. People who can afford wil enjoy the iPhone silently.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Device becomes hot&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The device becomes v hot..&lt;br&gt;Doubt the authenticity.&lt;br&gt;... ..... ..... ....... ......... ...... ....... ...... .. ....... ....... .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am rural area but still phone arrived in just 4 days. Nice packing, original product.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I used almost all brands of phone but this iphone is ultimate.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPhone 5s Review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There is something a prospective buyer should understand before even looking to buy an iphone 5s.&lt;br&gt;I'm no apple fanboy, trust me, but it IS the best phone available on market right now.&lt;br&gt;Not the most value for money, but the ultimate best. The Primera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks wise, I'd say its not a bad job. The same signature look that it has carried on since long. The gold and gray look fantastic, and feels nice in hand as well. But looks aren't even the intro to the whole story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The A7 chip inside is the best processor available on market for mobile devices, even better than the top of the line SnapDragon 800 which is the best any android/windows phone can offer.&lt;br&gt;The performance gains are not significant enough to matter to a casual user, or any user unless you were really looking for it. Its like saying ones a lockhead blackbird and others a falcon htv2. FYI, they're both insanely fast aircrafts. For people like us, its insignificant which is really faster. The 64bit architecture wouldnt matter much to the normal user as long as the applications dont make use of it. Its just apple being paranoid as usual about being future proof.&lt;br&gt;In addition to the processor capabilities, a major plus of Apple devices is that iOS7 was optimized for A7, while android(kitkat or jbean or whatever) is not. Android runs on a vm which leeches out a bit of the potency.&lt;br&gt;The GPU performance is commendable, and the motion processor m7 is also a unique characteristic, though if its full potential can be used in normal scenario remains to be seen. Yet.&lt;br&gt;The fingerprint scanner is a new innovation, and seems to work pretty good unless your hands are too sweaty. Currently its use is limited though in time in-app authentication as well as credit card/bank acc/wallet authentication could also be done using it. Lots to look forward to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downsides are also there, iOS7 needs more optimization to be better. And some might prefer a bigger screen to utilize all that juice inside. Though IMO the size seems optimum, not too big for a phone, and not too small to be disappointed. The battery could be a bit improved too, to last more than a day. A7/M7/PowerVR6 does drink a lot of power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All in all, I5s is not your casual whip-it-out-of-the-pocket-and-throw-it-to-the-bed smartphone, its a carefully constructed marvel. Powerful, future proof upto maybe 2+years, which is not something any other phone can boast about. Only two things stand in the way of it being the optimum phone, 1st being on the higher side of the food chain, and 2nd the more important one, we dont need that much power or performance. Yet. The app ecosystem, however large and varied it is, still doesnt have any applications that make use of the a7/m7 processors inside, or the 64bit architecture for that matter. And without it, its just a lamborghini on indian roads. Still, It IS the most expensive phone on the market. And again, it IS better than any, and you don't get to be the best without beating the best, and it costs to do that, like, a LOT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Build Quality: Unmatched (The closest competitor would be the HTC One)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Display: Many people complain that this 4-inch retina display offering is joke when compared to what other manufacturers offer these days. But this is not a phablet; it's comparatively much easier to use with one hand and the color tone of the 5S is much better than the overly saturated displays on the Galaxy S4 and Galaxy Note 3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Processor and RAM: The 5S has only 1GB RAM and a Dual Core processor which seemingly pales in comparison to what other flagship phones have to offer. But if you are a serious buyer, don't be fooled by these specs because the iPhone 5S is actually "The Fastest Phone ever tested" till date. The reason why the iPhone 5S blows away the competition is because it's processor is made specifically for the phone and it utilizes and squeezes processing power in the most efficient way unlike other phones whose processors are generic and used across various manufacturers without really utilizing available power to it's full extent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera: The 5S has a excellent camera but it is not the best in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call Quality: Normal calls are just as good as any other phone. But not many people are aware of the new facetime audio HD calling feature across iOS 7 users, the clarity is almost too much! You can even hear a person swallow or smack his/her lips. Little too intimate if you ask me :-)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Feature: Fingerprint Scan and unlock your phone. People may argue over the pros and cons of such a feature but I would personally prefer such a feature which I will certainly make use of; instead of an almost useless fancy feature which I rarely use. (Eg: Touch to share)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Price: Considering that the manufacturing cost of the iPhone 5S is just one dollar more than that of the iPhone 5 whose manufacturing cost is around INR 13,000; I would have liked the 5S to be priced at 40,000. It is without doubt EXPENSIVE!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome is the word! An amazing phone worth having. The Light weight n sleek body makes it more desirable !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is simply awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great service... Received it within24 hours... Has awesome features..great battery backup.. Gets charged really fast! I just love it :)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCD38</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Gold, 16GB)</value></title></item></items>