<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got what written in deal in time..value for money...keep it up Amazon India... A deal worth for....if u looking for iPad mini this is the deal&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth the bucks!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very close to what I was looking for and&lt;br&gt;surely is a remarkable piece of technology !&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Awesome experience all the way&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon has great service and efficiency. The ipad mini is a great product .Very handy to hold and easy to use. Came packed in apple packing with the charger .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Price increased&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;OMG till yesterday i was viewing this product to buy it tommorow and the price increased ! hoping the price will come back to old i love the ipad !&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got what was mentioned on the website. I thought headphones will accompany the box as i paid 28,000 for this I pad but there was no headphones which was disappointing.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Beautifull Product from Apple&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is an excellent product from Apple Store. I love this product and spend almost half of the day in weekend with this ipad mini only.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lots of apps from apple store.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Display is excellent and never hanged.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome deal. great delivery and nice product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome deal. You know apple is the best in the touch. Good product and nice delivery. Looking for similar good deals on other products as well.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it is very nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;soo sweeet....good product every one can buy this product and thanx for the amzon also.&lt;br&gt;hav a nyc day ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The iPad mini, at this price. Simply amazing.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Kudos to Amazon for such an incredible price for the iPad mini. The iPad itself doesn't need further reviews. Simply the best sub 8" tablet in the market today.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Loved it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really satisfied with the product. Best worth for the money. Really amazing product from apple. 5 stars to the amazon.in&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Color mismatch&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Sorry for saying this, I received only black color instead of White- Silver. I don't want to make big issue over this so i left it behind.&lt;br&gt;Kindly make sure you are not repeating this mistake.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards,&lt;br&gt;Karthikeyan Thamaraiselvan&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent product. Excellent Service by Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I need not add more eulogizing this wonderful Product. I wanted to gift it to my son on Gudhi Padva (new year) and order it a day before and lo behold, it was delivered dot on at 1 PM on Gudhi Padva - in less than 20 hours. We were delighted; more so because in early march another big e-seller had ditched us (out of stock) after keeping money for 15 days !!! To add sugar to icing I got it cheaper by Rs 500.&lt;br&gt;The strong packaging and express couriering needs special mention too. I have realized over the years that e-buying saves me several thousand rupees, lots of time and mental agony of asking for a product the local shop has no clue about, and most important - I do not waste fuel in going from one mall to another and coming back empty handed most of the time.&lt;br&gt;On the whole the experience was great this time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A caution here - some products may turn out to be different than described. (read my reviews of other products)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;FINALLY!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After waiting for more than a month,apple releases the much awaited apple ipad mini&lt;br&gt;specifications&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;pros&lt;br&gt;1)handy size-7.9 inches&lt;br&gt;2)5Mp isight camera-visually stunning&lt;br&gt;3)1.2 Mp front camera&lt;br&gt;3)extremely light weight&lt;br&gt;4)full aluminium body&lt;br&gt;5) 1GHz dual core processor,this works like a charm&lt;br&gt;6)light on your pocket for the features&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;cons&lt;br&gt;1) resolution-not expected from apple&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thats it...but the resolution is not such a downer&lt;br&gt;and please,now that the mini is out,DONT THINK ABOUT SAMSUNG OR GOOGLE,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the tablet doesnt exactly come in one hand..but its still a handy size..the resolution is more than enough...all games run smoothly as expected and the camer is awesome..build quality is mind blowing...&lt;br&gt;enjoy&lt;br&gt;cheers&lt;br&gt;ram viswanath&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It's simply awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;"Firstly I am happy with the Amazon customer service. Delivery was on time and packing was absolutely fine. About iPad mini it's an awesome Apple to have."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;Battery backup was good.&lt;br&gt;Display was so clear.&lt;br&gt;Camera clarity was good and it's so light weight to carry any where.&lt;br&gt;Accessibility was nice.&lt;br&gt;Wifi connection was in stream line.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;But it doesn't have head set in the accessories provided.&lt;br&gt;I found out speaker clarity was not up to the mark.&lt;br&gt;And a known thing without network or iTunes software this is worthless.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Ontime delivery and Ipad rocks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Thanks for Amozon for ontime delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ipad is working fine. First time i am shelling 18k online and worried about how would be the product. Packing is original. Got 4k less than Apple store. When I asked apple store guy how amozon can sell 4k compared to apple store, he said mostly these are refurbished. But it's not. Regarding service anyway product will be having 1yr warranty from apple. I am not sure this is true even if I buy from amozon. Anyway, now that i have Ipad in my hand, I will see what I got there.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the IPAD in 4 days.&lt;br&gt;Very good support &amp;amp; offer from SATNAM electronics and Amazon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank You&lt;br&gt;Ganesh VL&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple products are produce by great product designer and collectable device. And now with reduced price it is a deal.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got a new iPad mini from amazon India at a stealing price on the next day of order. I have  already couple of apple devices including iPad 3rd gen. But the mini version without retina display is made to fulfil the basic need of internet browsing,social networking and utility apps on a big screen. iPad give a moderate screen resolution of 1024 x 768 with 163PPI, which is enough for the day-today usages. If you compare the screen with retina one then difference can be seen in fonts and the edge of app icon, brightness is also less then retina display. iPad is available in two different sizes of 7.9 and 9.7 inches, 9.7 inches screen is the perfect size gives full advantage and feel of big screen. But mini version is more popular then the full version of iPad. iPad mini is more affordable and easy to carry around, when somebody use public transport during travel mini is advisable. Professional graphic designer, photographer and gamer will not satisfied with the mini iPad. iPad air and mini with retina display and A7 chip is for professionals. The basic difference between the tablet computer with android OS and made by apple with iOS is the screen aspect ratio and application specially made for iPad. iPad has 4:3 aspect ratio and android has 16:9, 4:3 ratio made iPad around 30% more spacious then android tablets. iPad is more useful to browse net because of the screen ratio. For most of the works 4:3 screen is perfect other then watching movies which are made into 16:9 ratio. App Store is the one the strongest point of iPad with more then 475000 apps specially made for the big screen and still increasing. Apple products are produce by great product designer and collectable device. And now with reduced price it is a deal.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Going for any other product.....missing the ultimate experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The title is a little confusing but this is I want to say that if you are going for Other Products then you are certainly going to miss the ultimate apple experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unlike it's competitors when apple launches something for a cheaper price, it still makes sure that the quality is not compromised.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope you will benefit from this tab as much as I did.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;Display&lt;br&gt;Speed&lt;br&gt;Wi Fi connectivity&lt;br&gt;Battery life&lt;br&gt;Pretty Handy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;None till now for me&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Wonderful&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Wonderful. As expected. Apple rarely disappoints you. Light and comfortable.  Go for it without any doubt. Thoroughly enjoying all the apps&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Item as described, reasonable price, fast shipping.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;iPad Mini is every inch an iPad. The model is A1455 which has all the frequency bands including LTE and CDMA which no other tablet has. Fast, lightweight.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good performance ...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased iPad Mini after watching the reviews from YouTube.&lt;br&gt;I'm happy with its performance and battery life. The sleek design impress everyone .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Product At Awesome Price..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros :&lt;br&gt;Battery&lt;br&gt;display&lt;br&gt;sound&lt;br&gt;Performance&lt;br&gt;Clarity&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons :&lt;br&gt;Weight.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's just awesome. More than worth for money. Highly Recommended.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;waste of Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Please do not purchase it as it's do not have any futures like 3g, voice calling, SIM support etc..Surely you will be disappointed..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;apple amaz(on)ing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;To amazon&lt;br&gt;Received it in good condition.&lt;br&gt;Quick delivery.&lt;br&gt;Ordered for space grey but received white.&lt;br&gt;Not an issue apple always an apple.&lt;br&gt;To apple&lt;br&gt;My first apple product .&lt;br&gt;It's awesome interface still exploring&lt;br&gt;have issue with Bluetooth connectivity&lt;br&gt;No file manager a big disappointment.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One of my first Apple product and i love my iPad. It is flawlessly smooth and is a great carry around unlike the other tablets in the market.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Product was nice in time delevared price also reasonable compared with other online sights try to give fast  dele vary&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;not worth buying&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you are looking for this only for gaming or surfing purpose then good but apart from this not worth. you cannot using map as places are still not updated as per apple care, that to places like Bangalore. No whats-app and all. OK but not worth.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good in this price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)  is good for the people who just want to use an apple product. but if u come to play high graphic games this product will disappoint you. Sound quality also not good as other apple products like iphone and ipods. Wi-Fi accessibility is also bad due to its aluminum cover. Overall this product will disappoint you but if u want to buy just an apple product then go for it.......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using Symbian,Windows and Android. Gave a thought of using apple product and believe me apple is apple. The touch interface clarity, configuration it's a charm. Added a new gadget to my collection. Liked the performance. after my purchase my cousins also purchased. This was my 2nd purchase from Amazon and it's great experience. Selected one day delivery and it was delivered within the time. Thanks Amazon for the service. All in all purchase was worth.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Product at awesome Pricing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Product Coupled with Pricing was the Main Reason I bought this ... also it was the Lowest Price available for this Product when compared to anyh online or offline retailer&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;The best mid sized tablet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it stands up to the tag of ipad... honestly the best sub 7 inch tablet in the market....the update to ios 7 will be an icing on the cake.....  for sure the update looks its best in the ipad mini's 7.9 inch screen...i recommend this tablet&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Miniature ipad 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A fluid os, powerful processor, sensible interface, millions of apps, these are some of many attributes which set aside an ipad mini from rest of the mini tabs in the market. So if you want a really portable tab which looks and feels awesome, go for ipad mini(personally i like black).&lt;br&gt;Then what is it missing? Well it is a generation ahead tab wrt any other competitor product, what makes me give a second thought is the fact that it fells much short of its big brother, "the ipad" or the ipad with retina display. If you imagine ipad mini as a small compact ipad, then you can be right as well as wrong at the same time. Right, because it has all the features of an ipad 2. Wrong, because it does not have many features which set ipad 4 a league ahead.&lt;br&gt;Well what does it miss? Well if you compare the spec of ipad mini and ipad 4, you will notice many features are absent in the former. But most of thesew are not noticeable except the retina display.&lt;br&gt;If you can spend an extra 10k and can carry a 10" slate with you go for ipad4, and if u don't abt the display, and need something really portable buy ipad mini.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Item!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Top branded item, perfect item without any flaws, this product is recommended to all the friends and family. Thank you&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Please get the data correct&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Dear Amazon team,&lt;br&gt;I am a kindle owner and I just love your way of treating customers but this time I would like to warn you about the wrong details and associated product pictures (here given 1GB Ram instead of 512 MB and in a 9.7 ipad given a pic of Ipad mini !!!! )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As you know flipkart is your biggest competitor in India, so if you want to pull customers to you then first get all the data right to the facts.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vipin.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;customer support is clueless&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Clue less about product &amp;amp; cluless about technomart . No emi's , Not ideal for Indian way of purchasing. cluless on resellers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Simply Amazing!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The Video viewing and game playing experience is just awesome!&lt;br&gt;Besides the textures and browsing experience is mind blowing.&lt;br&gt;User Interface - No words to describe !&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5 on 5&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good thats all&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good that's all. Good Price and Product.. Cool to use and  happy having the same . Not for coe au&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Wonderful Product &amp;amp; Excellent Service by Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Wanted to buy this for my son &amp;amp; Amazon gave me the best price. Wonderful Product &amp;amp; Excellent Service by Amazon. Thanks.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPad mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This device is absolutely super fantastic, mind blowing. Apple's one of the best device so far.&lt;br&gt;Thank you amazon for the service provided.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great tablet at a good price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The screen dimensions are good. There is no lag with the interface even when running multiple apps.&lt;br&gt;The look and feel is great.&lt;br&gt;But with iOS, it is a pain to transfer files onto the tablet, especially Office docs.&lt;br&gt;But at around 17K, it is a good buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Experiance to use ipad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it was a good experience to use ipad,expect some of the flow which i felt.&lt;br&gt;related to data transfer from computer to ipad.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Met my expectations of personal requirements. Easy to use and good value for money. Would recommend this for anyone. Thanks.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb Tablet. Quality Redefined.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Though Apple is a little restrictive, the design and quality of Apps will make that up !!! Recommended for purchase.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ITZ amazing product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought apple ipad mini 17K .I ordered on 6th jun &amp;amp; received by afternoon 9th jun.Thanks amazon .Its a wonderful product ,wondering feeling .Every feature z just awesome.Never think before buying this product.No lagging in higher ends games.good picture &amp;amp; video quality.sound is just awesome.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great product.Does exactly what it says.&lt;br&gt;Good value for money, just ensure you have wifi connection. Not 3G.&lt;br&gt;Very happy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;No words needed&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One needs no words to praise Apple iPad. Excellent tablet of all time.&lt;br&gt;The size is perfect and works great.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Super Product! Go for Retina Display If Looking To Splurge.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fabulous product at the price I got it for. Don't really need to talk a lot about the performance of apple products. If you are willing to splurge, go for the retina display. For me this is good enough.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Good!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product as usual was as expected from Apple and Amazon service was excellent.&lt;br&gt;There are a few limitations in this ipad but those are inherent in nature.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome!!!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome geat!!!!&lt;br&gt;Within few days after order i have received the product. No issue. I am happy. 5 star rating !!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Utsav&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fully setisfide . I get product as per my need and within time . Good good good good good good&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=5</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best For Reading&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Screen size if perfect for reading. Battery backup is also superior compared to the android tables.&lt;br&gt;Excellent for reading purpose.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Quality&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Here Iam giving my reviews&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product is robust&lt;br&gt;BIt low dpi so you won't find crisp display while reading ebook&lt;br&gt;sound is good&lt;br&gt;battery is ok but works good in standby mode.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPad Review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome product.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great features, faster browsing experience using wifi, better battery life, connect apple store to get huge downloadable components.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Proud iDevice owner&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought this powerful tablet from amazon before a month. Now I feel like I own the best of all. Finally Apple conquered my heart. Lol. If you want a tablet with midrange price and full fledge features go for this. Camera and the apps are great. Best sound quality. Screen resolution is a bit low as it don't have retina display. For the price range as we compare other android tablets, apple will be way ahead from all. Smooth operation and the battery life is way too long to hold. Handling the device is also pretty great. Best for travelers. No regret if you own one of this cute tab.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad fills my apple collectables&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the piece as expected on time.sealed and safely packed, best price in the market along with citi bank cash back offer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon team&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Ipad mini as expected&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The ipad mini is easy to hold (compared to Ipad) and the screen size is right for readying. I have observed lot of people cant hold the Ipad in hand for longer, most people place it on a surface. I am disappointed with display may be i should have gone with retina display. Somehow I find fewer apps for mini than IPad.  Also I have a Nexus phone, I feel android has more apps than apple (may be its me),  i do so much with my nexus. Apple UI is more intuitive and easy to use.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;AMAZON U R THE BEST. WELCOME TO INDIA&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this is first apple product ihav bought. gr8 one but should hav gone for ipad air. love the apps. my little daughter loves the rhymes app on ipad.now i know why apple is the best. AMAZON U R THE BEST. WELCOME TO INDIA&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got best deal in way lesser than market price. Amazon rocks!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best Product. Best Price. Loved it. overall very satisfied! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! ! !&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;using internet outside wifi network is a handicap&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is otherwise a very good product, except that there is no SIM card slot which makes it difficult to use internet when u r outside the wifi network&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;is it surely  wifi+ cellular ??&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;headline is wifi+cellular&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but in description it is written data connectivity is only  with wifi.. please tell me it is with cellular or not.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=7</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product was excellent and in original packing, future purchase by me only through amazon India. It is very good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;wow ! amazing amazon shopping experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very interesting ,excited,extraordinary SHOPPING experience  !  Hereafter i will do all my purchases only through AMAZON  thank you very much AMAZON&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad wth anyi Cable is not working showing "This cable or accessory is not certified and may not work reliably with this ipad"&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How i can get order product return back. How i can apply return policy.&lt;br&gt;iPad wth anyi Cable is not working showing "This cable or accessory is not certified and may not work reliably with this ipad"&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks &amp;amp; Regards,&lt;br&gt;Ch Sunil KUmar&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Ipad mini 32&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;product is very good product and use full for all ages one can opt for it with out any doughts&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome from Apple ipad Mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this product for a less price when compare to other shopping cart sites. I am using it on a daily basis to browse internet and for playing games.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;product was in good quality. It exceed my overall expectation of buying it online. Shall come back again to buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Thanks Amazone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it in a day as promised by Amazon. Ipad came in perfectly packed small box. Great server. Nothing to talk about the ipad. One of the best tablet. This one I bought for my daughter and she is very happy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its great product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product was as described....It is working perfectly for a week now....The display and app selection are awesome as per apple quality&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Hassle free online buying experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ipad mini was a gift for my daughters birthday and she fell in love with it. Thanks amazon for delivering ontime as promised. Product was exactly the same as described on the site&lt;br&gt;I now regularly visit amazon site for exciting offers as they don't want to miss them&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;At this price, the best value for money tablet around!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;(this review is being written for the iPad mini priced at Rs 16,990). It might be getting close to two years in age, but the iPad mini remains a very good device. The 1024 x 768 is half of what you get on an iPad mini with retina display but it honestly does not make as much of a difference as some people think it does. Almost all the apps work brilliantly and the camera is superb. Of course, in terms of design, this remains one of the best-looking tablets around. My advice: if you are on a tight budget, grab it!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=6</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;best buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this appple mini pad is the best buy in could find on amazon, i gifted to my close relative, the best buy *****&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Apple product is always great, nothing specific to add, what is amazing is the price at which we got, thanks to Amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth buying an apple product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it was as always amazon delivery and packing is good. Ipad mini is worth 18k and it does feel that . since ipad has 512 RAM , it does nt lack , it works so smooth...playing games on mini is just amazing experience...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Perfect Tab&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A Perfect Tab with a reasonable price. Excellent service and ontime delivery by Amazon. Will recommend this tab to everybody who is looking to purchase a tab with in 20k. I agree that there are many limitations (like No SIM, No Watsapp, No External Memory) compare to Samsung Tab3 and Google Nexus. But believe me, u wont regret after buying Apple Mini with the unique features it has (like Touch sensitivity, Clearatiy, Performance, Battery Backup, High Resolution Games, Kids Apps etc..)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product is awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I love iPad. Its brand new and working perfectly. But taking 16GB is not enough. Apple should provide an easy way to extend it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great product, great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One of the best tabs for the price point, although it's not the latest from apple. Shipped promptly and reached in very good condition&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It's awesome!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered this with one day deliver. Received as per promise. Excellent service from Amazon. Got it for 3k lesser price. Very happy. Coming to ipad, trust me, if you are an average user, it will make your day. As it's a premium tablet, it satisfies all your needs. Thinking to buy it? Go ahead !!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best starter. Apple!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all I got this product within 3 days of purchase. Totally satisfied with amazon packaging and all..&lt;br&gt;Coming to the product.. It was originally sealed pack by apple on April.. Also it is running on ios7 update is available as well..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome product Awesome quality&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Like:&lt;br&gt;-Awesome feel.&lt;br&gt;-Awesome touch and UI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dislikes :&lt;br&gt;-Charging takes lot of time(using the charger).&lt;br&gt;-You can't charge using your laptop until u have USB 3.0 (more power requirement).&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Feeling Lucky to bought my iPad mini in Amazon website!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got my device at unbelievable price! And they selling all new stuff like new new updated things.&lt;br&gt;Thank you Amazon :)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=9</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This come out to be as expected. Master piece...Apple always rock...i m loving it....totally new experience to read books for me...:-D&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Simple and awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all very speedy and perfect delivery by amazon..&lt;br&gt;This is my first iPad and it is the best choice after all.. I needed a tablet to partly replace my laptop, this machine does the job well.. Also the battery life is good... Don't really miss retina display, go for it only if u are a media professional. All in all a good buy.. Thank u Amazon!.. Thank you Apple!!!..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A very good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was initially confused between retina and non retina, ofcause retina display make sense but for purpose I bought this this product is awesome. And with this supplier a got it with 18 k while its actual price is 22k... The paxkin was nice, original apple packing and received in one day only.... Thank you&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Wonderful experience using iPad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;iPad has helped me reinvent my studies, be it newspapers, PDF files,taking swift notes, working on an album, projects, interviews it has  replaced a lot of conventional materials into this wonderful light weight marvel. Loving my iPad, loving my work. Thanks amazon for the price and prompt delivery.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;disappointed with the product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hello,&lt;br&gt;I  gave 4 stars to the product but I have learn recently we found out the games which are downloaded from app store are not functioning properly. Apple ipad mini was purchased on 26th March 2014, it is very much within warranty period . Kindly replace it or whatever necessary steps required.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Super Super Super Super Super Super Super Super Super Super Super Super  I pad i love it&lt;br&gt;Thanks to Amazon and Retailer.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;iPad Mini was received in its original sealed box (Apple) in two days flat. The iPad gave no problem in installation which only shows the item was not tampered with.Very dependable supplier.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Sim problem&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After some tym the device shows invalid sim......this is annoying&lt;br&gt;Otherwise very nice i like it great device and service&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nothing like an Apple Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Frankly, I wanted to buy the Samsung TAB 3 311. But mu 7 year old was not impressed and insisted on the Apple...nothing beats the experience on an apple product...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Product !!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best deal @ 27000 I am using this from 2 weeks and it is working smoothly with no problem . Thanks to amazon best services !!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=10</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good, product, delivery time..happy..only one thing i didnt like is that it doesnt have an earphone...ear phone would have made this excellent buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;How can we accept heating issue in Apple Product ?&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is little unrealistic for me that its heating when using SIM Network in case am out or sitting at one place . please consider this while buying but anyway Apple is Apple and rest are banana ;)&lt;br&gt;Good Luck&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was a b'day gift....product arrived as described. There were some delays from the courier....but, I was simply delighted with this!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent response from customer, very prompt! gave all the details that I had requested for before I placed the order. The handset came in very neat package and product was excellent!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Pal..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am really loving my iPad Mini. Superb Build Quality, lil upset that some of the iPhone Apps cannot be installed in it but, that's fine as it is not meant for that (Whatsapp, Viber etc.). Guys go for it..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;All that you want in a small package&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had an iPad Air and wanted a smaller one for my wife. This fits the bill perfectly -  All the goodness in a small lightweight format.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great product......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great product packaged in small and handy tab. Excellent wifi reception. I have GSM also and it provides adequate reception along with Reliance 3G SIM for emergency. However WiFi is the best. I was a bit apprehensive based on earlier reviews on what will be delivered. White or Black iPad. .? However I got exactly what I had placed order.&lt;br&gt;Good job...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my best experience of online shopping.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Apple iPad mini is amazing and Amazon.com too as much as good like Apple iPad Mini. I luv this site sooo much.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very reasonable price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was super impressed with the postage of the item.&lt;br&gt;I was a bit concerned that the item was fake but it was an original piece and I also got the serial number checked by Apple.&lt;br&gt;It is very reasonable for the cost I purchased the ipad.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I just loved dis product... Especially the picture quality, it's awesome... Everyone must go for this product...☺️ Perfect product with this price..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=11</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Touch Responsive&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The ipad has got an excellent screen and is very responsive to the touch.&lt;br&gt;I am finding using gmail on it more difficult than I do on my laptop.&lt;br&gt;It also has other features, which are a tad difficult for the initial user&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Genuine product with at a dirt cheap price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Recently I have ordered this iPad and using it. It's a genuine n you will not get this product at this price anywhere in retail or any other web portal. I m happy, I snapped this deal, it's been a month I was looking for deal for iPad and finally I got it. I highly recommend this product. I chose express way of delivery, it came before the time they promised so another surprise from the seller. I have got a bill and genuine accessories n original box. Totally loving it..!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;What to write about Apple product! It's just awesome.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A must have product from Apple! Just go for it, you will not find a reason to complain. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my new apple iPad mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A very good product. A very good service by amazon, got the product in just 2 days. Awesome awesome service&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is good and reached before the stipulated time period. The only concern was the courier service's response, they weren't sure when and how the shipment will b done.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great value for money compared to all tabs. Best is class. 64 gb can store all your songs. User friendly!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Value&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am extremely happy with this mini IPad. It is lightweight and fits easily into the handbag so really easy for carrying around&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A wonderful gadget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its just the thing I needed for reading my etextbooks.... after trying ebook reader(which is a good choice for reading fiction, but not for text books with illustrations and tables), android device etc&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;got it for reduced price @ 27000..but the set i got was packed in dec.2012...i think that may be the reason for price drop..&lt;br&gt;nothing to say about the tab- everybody knows- except for the low resolution display you will love it..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Tablet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought my ipad from amazon. I got a good price and the service and packaging from amazon was also good. I wanted to have this tablet primarily for my studies and I was concerned about the display quality of the device as it was not with retina display. But surprisingly I found the display quality was completely satisfactory and I am very happy with this purchase. The operation of the device is as smooth as a hot knife through butter. From my experience i would highly recommend the ipad mini to people who study or who need to do office work.Investing in this has brought about quite a substantial increase in my productivity. The screen is a lot bigger than the competitors like nexus and amazon fire(about 35% of screen real estate) and is ideal for reading or browsing .With so many great apps available I have almost completely digitized my studies. So if you can afford it, this is one great tablet.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=13</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Need one say anything about an Apple product? Except the price the product was excellent. Would love to possess Apple any day.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;In love with the device&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After using the iPad mini I got reminded why Apple is so expensive. The tablet is an absolute delight and any day better then any 8-inch Android tablet available in the market. The display is crisp and performance is very much pleasing. Another fantastic point is the long battery life. I have bought the wi-if version since at home I have a wireless connection and while travelling I will use my iPhone as a hotspot to connect to internet from my iPad. I am glad I chose this version.  Not omit I saved almost 7k, I also saved on the double monthly internet recharges. My iPad is the space grey one. All in all this is a fantastic piece of gadget from Apple. A must buy for all gadget lovers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Product and best price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought at this price and all my friends thought this is an old version so this low price.&lt;br&gt;but MFD is Mar 2014 i got this on April 1st. this is best price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I really love this ipad.&lt;br&gt;it has great performance. i wonder how, eventhough it is 512mb RAM but the functionlity of the apps are very smooth never has any lagging. (Saw many android devices more than 1GB has so many performance issues).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Batter backup is awesome its almost 2days with heavy load of usage.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent Product though have limitations on day to day requirement specially on Email attachemnts / uploading of some files on internet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hardware, graphics is excellent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Services from Amazon are amazing. I booked the product at 0930 PM and got delivery by 0300 PM next day. Excellent.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Brand new Apple product @ much lower price than Apple outlets&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First, it was more about good margins that I got when compared to market(Apple outlets) - almost 15% less. Which is quite a deal when it comes to apple products. Second, When one buys online, one get into doubts as one don't get to see the products beforehand and that too at a cheaper price. Surprisingly, on the both accounts, Amazon delightfully surprised me. I think, I'll be more frequent on Amazon now.Am satisfied to the core..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ipad mini is a great tab to buy.at this price i think its a good buy.apple has always been the leader in the tablet market.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Complete package in terms of Entertainment and prodcutivity&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This device meets all end user requirements in terms of reading, entertainment and productivity, very light weight and handy, excellent battery life.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money @17k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good build quality- display, speakers, wifi,. A decent ebook reader but features are lesser than android tablets.&lt;br&gt;Transferring files is harder as bluetooth works only with iOS devices i.e. Ipad and Iphone. Without jail-breaking, there are lots of restriction like external app installs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Appstore has good apps but most apps are premium.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;IOS 7&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Surprisingly iOS is installed on the iPad mini-1.Is this normal.Can somebody suggest a good keyboard for ipad mini. Need info&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money, sleek and easy to use&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have used the Samsung Tab 7" and then the first IPad. I discarded both the devices soon enough and purchased a Samsung Laptop with solid state drives. I thought Tabs are not for me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But, the IPad mini has changed this mindset. It is good looking for sure, more important it is easy to use. I am now using it for browsing as well as for creating and editing documents. The small size makes it a perfect travel companion.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=12</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth Buying&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;1. Brand&lt;br&gt;2. Touch sensitivity is excellent&lt;br&gt;3. Battery back is good&lt;br&gt;4. Lighter in weight&lt;br&gt;5. No flaws while playing game.&lt;br&gt;6. Display is very good&lt;br&gt;7. Easy to customize the apps in screen.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Love it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Have always been Apple fan. Enjoy watching videos, photos; fast surfing, extremely user friendly apps and above all too handy. A great improvement on iPad 1 that I was using so far.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;about ipad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is nice and good in speed games are look like real and good wi-fi speed and good sound effect&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple is Apple let others graple&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fulfills my requirement and very handy light and easy to Carry.go for it and see the difference .u will forget samsung&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;first of all its Apple product and its Mini. Its very handy and the new OS is superb ..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has all i wanted.. Outlook e-mails, Music, Games, Movies, Apps etc ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A good buy as a present to my wife. Wish a suitable cover was also a part of this deal.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;mini i pad status&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i am happy with app i pad mini &amp;amp; very very enjoying with  the same ,&lt;br&gt;lovely &amp;amp; nice i pad mini&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;My iPad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got my iPad in just two days...thank u Amazon.......  . .. . . . ..  ...  ..  .. .  .. .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;simply love it....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;deliverd within 4 days...good packaging..already with ios 7 version, required just little upgrade....working very fine. very good product quality as it is apple....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ipad mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery s reallly bad....dint expect dis frm apple :( it doesnt even stay for 2 days,,,:@ try to improve it :/&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=14</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad Mini vs Nexus 7 - Comparison Review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon is offering this, the older version of iPad Mini, at an exceptional price (below INR 20,000), which became even more lucrative with an ongoing offer on my credit card. This brings it very close to Nexus 7 territory and in case you are wondering which one to buy, read on!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I was a little apprehensive ordering from an unknown seller initially, given that every other retailer was selling it at well above 20K. Decided to go ahead purely on Amazon's reputation and my long standing experience of ordering through their US and Indian websites. I was glad I did, because the product I received is genuine (the seller in my case was 'Compushop'). Amazon did a good job of delivering it within 2 days and kept me updated on the status throughout.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;==========&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here are some quick thoughts after using it for a little over 1 week:-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Screen**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I love the 7.9 inch formfactor, which is wider than the Nexus 7, resulting in 35% more on-screen real-estate. Yet, it comfortable enough to hold with one hand for long periods of time. The wide screen makes it feel more 'book-like' than the Nexus 7. I personally think Apple has cracked this feature (pun unintended!) - it has achieved the perfect trade-off between portability and screen size.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The new iPad Mini comes with a Retina display, which is twice as sharp as this model. Even the new Nexus 7 screen is much sharper. That said, this display is not bad, particularly if you haven't used any of the Retina iOS devices or aren't comparing them side by side. Videos and photos are quite decent (unless you are playing true 1080p video, it's hard to notice any difference). Text is definitely much sharper on the new one, however given the price difference, I think you'll be happy with this one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So unless you are obsessed with the ppi count (pixels per inch, in case you wondering), I would recommend this over the Nexus 7. Trust me, the bigger screen matters... a lot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 1, Nexus 7 - 0&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Build Quality**&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini, like all iPads, comes with a brushed aluminium back that looks sleek and beautiful. Nexus 7 has a rubberized plastic back, which is great but not half as sexy as the iPad. Build quality on both tablets is very good, I don't think you'll be unhappy with either.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The side bezel on iPad Mini is incredibly thin, which is what enables Apple to provide such a large screen in a smallish form factor. Neither tablet is uncomfortable to hold in one hand. However, Apple has customized the software so that if you are holding the tablet with your thumb resting on the screen, it won't register the touch. This feature is not available on the Nexus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, iPad Mini trumps over the Nexus 7 in build quality for sure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 2, Nexus 7 - 0&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Battery Life**&lt;br&gt;Both tablets pack enough juice to keep you going all day with normal use. I've not run any tests, but from experience, the iPad Mini battery seems to last slightly longer than the Nexus 7. This is not to say that the Nexus 7 battery is bad, it's still better than many other tablets in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'm going to declare a tie since both offer adequate battery life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 2.5, Nexus 7 - 0.5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Music**&lt;br&gt;Music sounds much better on the iPad than comparable android devices (incl. the Nexus 7), which is not surprising given that Apple revolutionized this market and continues to dominate it in every segment. Yes, iTunes can be a pain sometimes and there are other options to transfer music, but from experience I would recommend using iTunes to non tech-savvy people. There are just too many issues that keep cropping up with using other methods. Android has iOS beat in this - all it takes is a simple copy paste to put music on the Nexus 7.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, it's another tie between the two. Music sounds better on the iPad but transferring music is much easier on the Nexus 7 - go for the one you prefer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 3, Nexus 7 - 1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Reading &amp;amp; Browsing**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iBooks takes ebooks in ePub format and its easy to sideload books that you already have. I use Calibre to manage my ebook collection and would highly recommend it (its free!). Calibre will automatically convert ebooks in any format into ePub and transfer it the iPad in a seamless manner. Unlike music, transferring books onto the iPad is just as easy as it is on the Nexus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I prefer browsing in potrait mode and the iPad mini allows you to see more content than a comparable 7 inch tablet because of its wider screen. It's easy to zoom into any section by double-tapping on it and the interface is smooth and responsive.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Unfortunately, Apple products do not offer built in support for flash, so some websites won't display properly. However, the web is slowly but steadily moving towards HTML5 and the absence of flash support is not likely to prove too much of a hindrance as time goes by. And this is not specific to iOS, Adobe has stopped supporting flash on Android as well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Again, I'm going with the iPad in this segment purely because of the larger screen. If you are OK with the Nexus 7 screen size, go for it. Text is much sharper on the Nexus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 4, Nexus 7 - 1&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Games/Apps**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This iPad Mini comes with Apple's A5 dual core processor, which is also featured in iPhone 5. It's a little old, but still has enough juice to run most games and apps without any lag. Unless you are an avid gamer and play games with very demanding graphics, you won't notice any difference. However, this is one area where the Nexus 7 beats the iPad Mini squarely.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Compared to the android space where most of the apps are not optimized for running on a tablet, there are no such concerns here. Almost all popular apps in iTunes have a specific version that is optimized for the iPad.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, Nexus 7 scores with a much faster processor (Quad-core 1.5 Ghz vs. Dual-core 1.0 Ghz) and a humongous RAM (2 GB vs. 512 MB), while the iPad scores on the back of a much more vibrant app space. I would go with the Nexus however, as the app space in Android is sure to catch up and the Nexus hardware specs make it more future-proof.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 4, Nexus 7 - 2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;**Camera**&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In good light conditions, photos turn out very well on the iPad Mini. Low light photography may not be up to par when compared with current generation iPads, but it's still better than the current generation Nexus 7.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Videos can be recorded in full 1080p. Do keep in mind that 1080p videos require an incredible amount of space and will fill up your storage space in a jiffy. For typical usage conditions, 720p would be more than adequate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No comparison here - iPad mini beats the Nexus 7 camera hands down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 5, Nexus 7 - 2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;==========&lt;br&gt;Final Score&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini - 5&lt;br&gt;Nexus 7 - 2&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, the iPad Mini comes out the clear winner in the head-to-head. However, do keep in mind that I went for the iPad over the Nexus in the Screen and Reading/Browsing segments, which comes down to personal preference. It could easily have been 4-3 in favour of the Nexus 7 if you don't mind the narrower screen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;==========&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All things considered, I'm very satisfied with the purchase. Why 4 stars then? Well, I was tempted to give it 5 stars purely because the price drop makes it incredible value, especially considering you get much better build quality than the Nexus 7 (not to forget the bragging rights!). However, I'll stick with 4 stars because of the lower resolution screen and below par RAM, which makes it very likely that the growth in app demands will outpace the hardware shortcomings sooner rather than later.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope this review proves to be helpful. In case you have any specific queries, do leave a comment below and I'll be happy to respond asap.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Wrong Model delivered&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had the worst experience with Amazon , I can't believe brand name like Amazon has this quality of sellers.&lt;br&gt;I ordered ipad mini cellular white -silver  as a gift for special occasion . But when gift pack was opened ,ipad mini was black in color, in my order it is clearly mentioned that I have ordered for white-silver , even the bill/invoice sent from amazon mentioned it as White-silver . This gift is ruined now. When I contacted Amazon they said they don't have replacement policy , I have to return the order ,  once the order is returned, they will return the money and I have to order again.&lt;br&gt;With experience like this I don't think I will order anything from Amazon again.&lt;br&gt;Beware of this seller.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon- this is not expected from you guys.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Trust the buyer. This is a genuie product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Most of us have read reviews of iPad mini in different forums. So I should not waste time to repeat the same. I liked almost everything about iPad mini. However, I didnot like the photo quality of the photo taken in so called 5 MP camera. I will need to get in touch with the service center to understand what is the problem. Is it anything to do with this make or it's a limitation in all iPad mini, since I liked the quality of photo taken in iPad 2.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would also like to tell that I bought this product at 10% less price than it is sold in iStore or imagine or in other online sites. So I think the deal is really good and I should also assure the readers that the product is genuine. The product got delivered in 2 days time from the date of order placement. This is something which I really liked about the seller and amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Have been android user for long time...&lt;br&gt;Just for a change i tried the ipad mini.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;though the specifications of this device is lower(ram,cpu..),  surprisingly the performance&lt;br&gt;is better than high end android device . (ignoring the gaming performance).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What I liked most is lag free experience  (which cannot be found in any high end android device)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However there are many limitations with iOS OS when compared to Android.&lt;br&gt;Nevertheless, considering the lag free experience i  like ipad mini very much.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing Amazon experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's excellent deal and great service from Amazon . I must say it's really build for genuine customer like us.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;keep it up&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good service&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;the service provided was really good , i did like it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i would definitely  recommend amazon to all my friends and relatives as well&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thank you&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Finally an Apple user...I love my iPad mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got the cheapest deal on amazon and was glad to grab it. Even though this was an old-generation iPad it feels damn smooth.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lovely product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very much good. Nicely packed by amazon. Amazing service that's why they are called amazon.really love you amazon.got the product within 30 hrs of order. Product is fine.going to use sim internet.as of now using in friends wifi hotspot.really satisfied.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It's a Buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;You should absolutely buy this if your thinking about buying a tablet under 25k.&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Amazing Battery Life&lt;br&gt;2. Light weight.&lt;br&gt;3. Apple Ecosystem&lt;br&gt;4. Free iWork Apps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons.&lt;br&gt;1. The screen is really good but if your used to the retina world you'll notice pixels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's a Buy..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Product..awesome amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Well,anything said about the ipad is less.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Camera is one of the best cameras i have ever seen.The 5 mp camera does wonders when taking pictures outdoors though ,It is a bit grainier indoors .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And about amazon ,The Product was delivered to me in less than three days.I gave my office address but as it was Saturday and i was at home so the amazon people made arrangements for the delivery to my home :).Just an online chat with customer care executive and it was delivered to my home address the same day&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Product for &amp;lt;20k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this on Amazon on 14th November 2013. It is amazing and super fluid. Have not experienced any lag so far and the sound and picture are excellent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy it if you're looking for a &amp;lt;20k product. You will not regret it. Only wish they bundled earphones with the tablet.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my first apple product. Very good usability , display, smooth touch screen and fast. Excellent for reading. I wish it had phone calling facility in addition to the data sim.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Good as expected.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my second apple device and it was as good as the first one. I think ipad mini is a better device than ipad and everyone shpuld get one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPad Mini&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent service by Amazone. Item was received before expectation time.&lt;br&gt;Product performance is also too good. Only problem with some of Bank sites are not supported by Ipad.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;An excellent compact tablet. But overprized&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;### First of all,dont confuse this with the latest iPad Mini Apple released recently . This is the first ipad mini released a while ago and it does NOT come with a Retina Display.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPad Mini has a 4:3, 7.9in display with the same 1,024x768 resolution as the iPad 2.  Comparing to the other compact devices at this price range, Nexus 7 2013 comes with a far better display in terms of resolution and pixels per inch. iPad mini only has a poor 161 PPI while Nexus 7 has 331 PPI. Even the old Nexus 7 2012 had 216PPI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Excellent Build Quality - No compromises as always from Apple.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; iOS 7 upgradable.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Good Battery Backup.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Lightweight and Portable.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Great App Ecosystem. Plenty of apps well designed for Tablet available in the Apple Appstore. Most Android apps are not well designed for tablet use.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Low resolution Display. ( reflective,but with good viewing angles)&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; 512 MB of Ram !! ( Nexus 7 2013 comes with 2GB of ram )&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; 16:9 Nexus 7 is far better suited to video playback than the iPad Mini, as the Mini's 4:3 ratio gives films huge black bars on either side. Video on Nexus 7 looks way sharper than on iPad mini.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; The Mini is powered by the same 1GHz dual-Core A5 processor as the iPad 2. This is very usable,but since this is an expensive tablet they should have powered this with a more powerful processor.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Need iTunes to transfer files. Time consuming.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Like any other Apple product, No Sdcard Slot.&lt;br&gt;=&amp;gt; Expensive&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Is this tablet for you?&lt;br&gt;Apple iPad mini is overall a good compact tablet,but with a low resolution display. Even with the low end internals it has,it performs quite well.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy this only if you are an iOS lover and want a decent compact tablet with great battery backup. Otherwise go for Nexus 7 2013 edition which is a great value for money device than this over priced mini tablet from Apple. Both Nexus 7 and iPad Mini are eligible for future software updates directly from their respective manufactures.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are looking for a pure gaming tablet, Xolo/Nvidia Tegra Note would be an ideal choice as it blows out both nexus 7 and ipad mini in terms of graphics performance.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;AMAZING INVENTION EVER&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Instead of repeated praising let me tell you some facts. Hope this will help you chose the right tab - I know a lot of people in India are confused between iPad and android tabs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. If you are planning to buy nexus 7 (yes even the new one which launched on 24 july) you can't get the battery backup and apps that apple provides.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. I opted for a 16gb wifi over nexus 7 32 gb+3G (remember both have the same price point ).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Don't just go for the specs as apples 800 MHz processor in iPhone 4 is still runs smooth than the unlimited number of galaxies in the tech world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. There are over 3 Lakhs iPad optimised apps in the App Store but when it comes to android there are a few.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad Mini WiFi&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon India rocks, I mean just awesome services by Amazon and Amazon India rocks.&lt;br&gt;  My experience of buying through Amazon India was well beyond my expectations.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Just Awsome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great product From a Great Brand at Great Website...Got best price ever.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ipad can't be compared thats what I will say.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ULTIMATE!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;BETTER than what i expected.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am a big Fan of Apple now. Thanks to Amazon for providing it at the best possible price and quick delivery was additional feather.. Enjoying using this mini packet of big utility.. I am doing every online task in time now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to Apple for this marvelous product. Very much handy and light.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would say one of the best product in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Happy to use and recommend it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Sealed packed......  Just awesome. Thanks guys. It is worth buying ios. Everyone should have one of these. Close ur eyes n buy it.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DFDU248?pageNumber=15</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Mini (White-Silver, 16GB, WiFi)</value></title></item></items>