<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good and at a very best price. I bought it for my wife and she loved it a lot. Good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I like Windows Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I choose this product because of its features and low cost. I hate Android OS so i choose windows that leads to Nokia Lumia520&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product for the price range..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia is known for its battery and this mobile does have a pretty decent battery.. The OS and form factor are decent.. Good Product for the price range.. Worth buying for hard core use..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A Must buy in the 7-8k budget!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought it from Amazon, special offer. get delivered on DhanTeras by a simple request.&lt;br&gt;VERDICT : If you budget is near 8000 buck , voilà! buy this phone asap. :)&lt;br&gt;Review after ~2 months of use.&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;• The adorable part of phone and its USP is its design, every Lumia phone comes with Stamp-of-good-design.&lt;br&gt;the rectangular design looks premium with sharp edges.&lt;br&gt;• Phone's camera is awesome &amp;amp; mind-blowing, digital lences provided by Nokia like smart shoot, panorama,Nokia camera, cinemagraph makes its one of the best contender in budget phone segment. Although the flash is missing but in case of indoor photography where the light is incident directly on the object still good results found. Manual controls is also provided (such as iso, exposer, shutter speed etc.)&lt;br&gt;its camera provides focusing the objects like in PnS cameras and believe me its working smarty and detects the focal length to the object in the centre of screen while focusing, Touch focus it is also provide but is it is not give the optimum results relatively.&lt;br&gt;• Also you can control focal length in Nokia camera app.&lt;br&gt;• The beautiful thing about phone is it its User Interface and  live tiles, they are two adoring and attractive.&lt;br&gt;• The touch screen is capacitive and runs like butter. muhhhaah&lt;br&gt;• The screen size is 4'' (personally i thinks 4''-4.8'' is the range of comfort)..  phone comes easily in hand. Also resolution is descent with a descent ppi.( 480 x 800px &amp;amp; 233 ppi).&lt;br&gt;• Internet explorer is too good (the ease of browsing)switches between the mobile sites or dekstop sites based on your preferences, but there is no flash support(not a big issue)&lt;br&gt;One must have improvement should be provided to control of pop-up window.(i.e. in some sites popup appears automatically or by clicking action but in desktop it appears in new window/tab but in IE for windows phone it appears frequently in the same tab &amp;amp; overlaps your original tab.&lt;br&gt;except overall browsing is fluid in it :)  .&lt;br&gt;Also thanks to UC browser(third party app) for the better file downloading management.&lt;br&gt;• I think 512MB RAM is sufficient to this phone[more precisely cheap windows phones(not low-end windows phones)],, as windows phone architecture is quite fluid and its rarely deal with a phone hang. Also there is neglegible frequency of application crashes.&lt;br&gt;• In the price range of 7000-7800k(yes,it is varying these days), this phone is really a must have.&lt;br&gt;don't think much and grab this phone if your budget is near 8000k.&lt;br&gt;• The battery backup is quite good and it charges quickly as well.&lt;br&gt;• we can choose favourite photos it in the Photo-app so that these can be appeared as photo app background &amp;amp; shown on the live tiles.&lt;br&gt;• Cloud management of contact is a very good idea so that no fear of losing contacts and also synced with your windowsPC and outlook, linking contacts to the facebook and other services update latest contact photo(non-of-us updates contact photos manually!)&lt;br&gt;• HERE maps provides too good navigation. also you can download yours region maps for free that work even when if eventually out of network coverage.&lt;br&gt;• Some would say there are few apps available in windows phone Store but almost all the major apps are available and you won't need others than these apps. and the success of windows phone attracting developers on and on.&lt;br&gt;• You can switch the back covers of your own colour choice everyday, because Nokia provides its officially, named as &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.in/gp/product/B00BRPTT9K"&gt;Nokia CC-3068&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br&gt;• Free Office app provided by Microsoft , the app is too good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons-&lt;br&gt;• The File manager is missing, that leads to various limitations like sharing a particular file type, knowing details of file like size etc.&lt;br&gt;• Lack of flash is too disappointing! even in the successor phone &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.in/gp/product/B00HRUQ2L2"&gt;Nokia Lumia 525&lt;/a&gt; there is no flash, that phone have one major improvement of 1GB RAM.&lt;br&gt;• To share a file via bluetooth to a device you have to pair them first.&lt;br&gt;• You can't seek while playing music like that in video you can. to seek you have to long press 'next' button.&lt;br&gt;• No provision of advanced sync setting i.e. to sync photos or not &amp;amp; No selective sync such as which facebook Albums to sync etc.&lt;br&gt;• NO USB tethring support.&lt;br&gt;• Calling a contact by the contact list is too procedural task ,,can be improved by updates.&lt;br&gt;• Volume control for the phone and voice call is same &amp;amp; must be different control provided.&lt;br&gt;• As there is no app in the store for the password protection of some apps(as in android) like access protection of messages, whatsapp, facebook, chats etc. oh yes Kids corner is such a waste thing.&lt;br&gt;• The internal is 8GB , and usable is ~6GB. although you can extend it with a SD card but as app will only install in internal memory and you can't move apps to SD card.&lt;br&gt;• .xap file are similar to .apk file in android but there are too limitation in installing apps from these.(Because removing limitations encourages piracy so its good too)&lt;br&gt;• No pc companion software for advance control.&lt;br&gt;• No compass, missing HERE-city lens(formerly known as Nokia-city lens)&lt;br&gt;• No Auto-rotate control. Although it will be fixed in the Lumia-Black update.&lt;br&gt;• Limitation to run a task in background such as torrent, background file downloading etc.&lt;br&gt;• Some apps are paid in windows store that are free on other platforms.&lt;br&gt;• No front camera.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;More valuable compare to android for d cost  i paid&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this with 10% cash back offer. Earlier I was android user compared to that windows s too good to use. Display in Lumia s superb. But I found something missing in Lumia 520. Starsports live streaming video not supported for this phone..  Gyroscope sensor not available.. Magnetic compass sensor not available. But overall I am so happy with this.. I love this.. I had hanging issue in android but now I dont have that issue with Lumia. Thanks. Simply go for Lumia.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product. Very good build quality&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent product. Very Fast Shipping. Very good packing. Excellent deal.&lt;br&gt;Was looking for good Smartphone under Rs. 10000. This phone is an excellent value for money. It has Windows 8 mobile OS which runs very smoothly due to the 1 Ghz processor under the hood.  5 Mega Pixel camera shoots nice shots in daylight. Lack of flash makes the shots in low light a bit grainy and noisy. Good connectivity options with WIFI, GPRS, 3G etc.&lt;br&gt;Overall a very good phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features are superior according to price from others&lt;br&gt;hand sets and your website provides very lowest price then other&lt;br&gt;websites.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good worth of money spent on it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Overall good one, having good features like voice calling, camera quality, GPS &amp;amp; nevigation system, but it hangs on occasionally.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best hardware below 10k budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There are many android smartphones out there from indian manufacturers as well as samsung but they fail to provide a decent experience. Also, I doubt their service.&lt;br&gt;Lumia 520 offers the best hardware and smooth UI @ a very affordable price. The only drawback is the os itself. It doesnt let you do as many things that android allows. Also there are small quirks in the os.&lt;br&gt;If you are a normal user who is not into tweaking and tinkering with ur phone, lumia 520 wont disappoint you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good in the same class of other brands&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Reached with 5 days at my doors..&lt;br&gt;The main draw back is No Front camera and flash....&lt;br&gt;RAM is only 512 MB.&lt;br&gt;Very wood wifi speed. Just Rocking with that.&lt;br&gt;Very good battery back up...&lt;br&gt;Totally NOT BAD......Worthy for the Price range when compared with other brands.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=5</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;awsome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Superb Windows experience in such a low cost.... Better than local mobile shops... I suggested 5 of my friends  now they are so jealous of me thanks to amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Super fast delivery within only one days.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent phone in this price,Everything is ok. its is one of the best enrtry level phone compared same price mobile.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A Perfect mobile under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After a long time, I am seeing Nokia's reliability in this phone. Its as tough as 1100. And smart enough to be a smart phone :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;THIS IS MY 2ND LUMIA&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ALREADY HAVE ONE, BECAUSE I LIKED IT I BOUGHT ANOTHER ONE. BEST ECONOMY CLASS SMART PHONE FOR JUST 7000&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice touch.processor very good,just one problm we have to buy some application which is needed&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good quality i suggested two three friend of mine and they buy this product at the same time nice and worth to buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;In time delivery of Genuine product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The rate of nokia lumia 520 was lowest on Amazon in the market when I place the order. The phone was shipped to me in 4 days. The phone set is new as expected and the box is having all the accessories as mentioned by nokia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phone is with me for nearly 20 days. the touch screen is really very responsive. All the features as mentioned on different sites are working. I am using the phone on Wi-FI. Net surfing is really easy.&lt;br&gt;I can say that the phone is well worth for the money paid.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;true value of money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Looks good, performance good, camera good, speed good, camera button some times create problem, true value of money, I like the smart phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good looking Smart phone received in hand less than a expected date. :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good Smart phone for new users. Better than an android cheapest smart phones.It has the quality of good looking,smart and handy .It is really worth for its money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; I am the regular visitor of Amazon website it provides a clean price for its products , the quality and also the services provided by them is really good and appreciated.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent phone. Total value for money.&lt;br&gt;Amazing touch and camera.exceeded expectations. Much better than any other phone in this category&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia 520 is Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Everything is very nice, Fluid interface,Windows 8 OS,Nokia Radio is awesome&lt;br&gt;I wish in future models battery would be more powerful.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;I Loved It very much&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;What I have to Tell.........................One word answers.........marvellous.....Awesome....Excellent........What I expected it meets the requirements....Go for It you really Like....Day to Day I recognising new things about this phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Frns I suggest u to buy dis phone.&lt;br&gt;as it is d best phone in dis budget...&lt;br&gt;I think u should buy it.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A GOOD MOBILE - VALUE FOR MONEY&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia 520 is a smart phone at low price. Its good for not so tech savvy and those using the phone for routine usage.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone , good battery&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone... Good battery backup being a smartphone.... Awesome UI.... Sometime hangs but less than other smartphones... Best phone in this price range..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Love it, because of a deal and offcourse the windows phone. was using android tablet and felt to have a 1 of windows and chossen 520.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its awesome&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is too good for the price. Flawless performance. Touch is too sensitive. Never get hanged. It will take some time for Android users to get used to Windows 8. Nokia Mix radio is too good. Very bright screen and ok viewing angles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;Not for people who wants lot of apps. The store should have more free Apps.&lt;br&gt;SD Card browsing is not there.&lt;br&gt;Notification app drawer is missing compared to Android.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall Verdict: Go for this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good service &amp;amp; phone too&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;service was very fast &amp;amp; phone is also good at such low price.&lt;br&gt;packing was also very good thanks amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;general feedback&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very poor battery backup and net surfing is very slow, you cant enjoy video online without buffering, nothing is easy to download and some problems like memory card not reading etc&lt;br&gt;overall average phone and in this price you can have lots of choices in the market&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Decent buy for a guy !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Meets the expectations of a typical medium budget smart phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;pros&lt;br&gt;- 8 GB internal memory&lt;br&gt;- excellent touch experience&lt;br&gt;- audio and video playback is good&lt;br&gt;- camera is decent, but no flash&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;cons&lt;br&gt;- poor battery performance&lt;br&gt;- over heating when playing games or when using 3G&lt;br&gt;- limited apps in windows store&lt;br&gt;- no file manager for managing files in SD card&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product is not working properly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Vibrator is not working within 1 month. I will start heating up if internet is used for more than 1 hour. It will hang many times.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=7</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;good one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good smart phone with windows in the budget and useful features. I liked the user interface of windows OS on lumia.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good VFM product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice phone for those who are not too techy, easy interface, Battery last for abut 2-3 days of normal use (NO 3G/2G) and with some WIFI use it lasts for more than a day. Within 8k price range, this is an excellent VFM phone&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROS&lt;br&gt;Excellent call quality, sound. Good built quality. Superb touch response, good display&lt;br&gt;Camera is decent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONS&lt;br&gt;1.one problem is that the signal strength, battery level is not displayed at top always unlke in other phone where these are displayed always at top., in this phone ,u need to slide down to see these details.&lt;br&gt;2.The buttons at bottom are not back lit.&lt;br&gt;3. no secondary camera.&lt;br&gt;4. Since speaker is at backside ,sometimes the phone ring is not audible in noisy areas. wish the speaker was at side/bottom.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520, awesome purchase&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;An amazing smartphone for under 10k. All the apps work on my campus wifi, with proxy.(same not true for android)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;More then Expected&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Design is Eye Catching.&lt;br&gt;Processing speed is very Fast.&lt;br&gt;Super internet speed.&lt;br&gt;Only cons no Flash.&lt;br&gt;Overall Very good smartphone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really good buy! Great phone to have! look is awesome, the sync is great, free movies, songs from Nokia, cameras good, storage is good! Feel in love with it moment i saw it and after using it still in love with it!! Highly recommended!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good... Need to Add Some More Features&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good... Need to Add Some More Features like call recording, sms and call counters etc. Overall cheap and best phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very elegant display.  Very sensitive to touch.  Display is excellent with a very pleasing font.  Battery life is a bit short though.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it's really awesome thanks to amazon and saholic&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very cheap and very nice product. Lumia 520 is a well product under 7k thank you once again for all&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent product from Nokia at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a really good product from Nokia. I believe in "user experience" rather than "spec comparison" and i really love this phone as this is excellent in that aspect. Even though this comes with 512 MB RAM, it is far more faster and smoother to use than some of the other ones I have used with double the RAM, it really lies in the software part and not solely on the spec.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some Pro's-&lt;br&gt;1. Excellent display.. Really this is one of the biggest difference as IPS display feels really good while browsing and reading  :)&lt;br&gt;2. Touch feels so smooth&lt;br&gt;3. Build quality is very good.&lt;br&gt;4. Camera clarity is nice ( needs good lighting as there is no flash)&lt;br&gt;5. Windows 8 is pretty fast. (Also Amber update is already present)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No major con's i have seen so far, but the Apps available are not  huge compared to android,  and the major ones we usually use are in  Nokia/Windows app store for free :). Also the battery holds good for 2 days for moderate usage, but heavy applications/camera reduces it fast.  Also there is no scratch guard when we take it out of the box which is commonly available for most touchscreen phones nowadays.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Pre-installed apps like MS office and outlook are nice. There is 8 GB internal memory (5GB available for personal use) and additional Skydrive(cloud) provided for storage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is a wonderful and good quality phone at this price and highly recommended!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;just love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Love the windows, it is much much better than people thinks.&lt;br&gt;and yup the service of amazon is just outstanding.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=6</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;request&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;many people will buy nokia Lumia 520 if all the sellers reduce the price to 7,500 rupees. I am interested to buy this phone if the price is 7,500 rupees.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia touch screen is a mess&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;- Windows OS is great but it do hung up at times&lt;br&gt;- touch screen comes to a standstill often and key tend to press by itself.&lt;br&gt;- customer care service responded asking a 20 days time for replacing touch scree.&lt;br&gt;I had to know why Nokia dint make it a normal touch screen, who needs a super sensitive touch screen which doesnt work.Those who are planning to buy this mobile please read complete reviews.&lt;br&gt;- the phone specifications and the os is good but the hardware (especially the touch screen) is an utter waste and u will end up in service centres soon enough repairing your mobile.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Prompt delivery of a good quality phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I would rate this phone as one of the best budget smartphones in the market. A really nice phone to have&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The Best u get @ this price...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased it from amazon..and their delivery is amazing..just got it the next day i ordered.&lt;br&gt;coming to the phone..its really awesome,the Os is top class and better compared to Android,the touch sense is really superb and the CAM is perfect...my suggestion is go for this when u wanna buy a phone @ this price range....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome offer&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;thank you for such a wonderful experience with lowest cost ever&lt;br&gt;i got lumia 520 at just 6999 just coz of this site&lt;br&gt;i referred many friends for buying their mobile ,&lt;br&gt;talking about lumia after using for a week i am getting used to windows .&lt;br&gt;gaming experience is awesome&lt;br&gt;camera experience is great&lt;br&gt;u can definately buy lumia if u want to look different in crowd.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;100% value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best in class quality, best in class look, 100% value for money, good operating system, good battery back up. good screen quality&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;amazon delivery is superb&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered it online in amazon and i got the mobile just after two days, i placed the order and the delivery is very good. Loved it a lot and the phone is superb, i got it for the lowest price.&lt;br&gt;The is the best phone in terms of every thing like price, os, camera, screen, memory, packing is excellent, pre installed apps are good,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;over all i would give 5/5 rating&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;also u amazon guys roxxxxxxxxxxxx&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Go for it...no 2nd thought....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its better not to write much.....just wanna say...Go for it ,u cant get anythng better than this if ur budget is upto 12k.... if u wanna spend more ..thn its upto u....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;its really awsome......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone Is superb and no longer will go back to android. Nokia's touch is by far the best I've used. Happy with this purchase. Thanks Amazon!!!! and Best seller also in COD.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awsome..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my first ever purchase on amazon and guys i must tell u that both amazon and Lumia 520 are fantastic..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best buy smart phone at lower mid budget point.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia lumia 520 is the best smartphone at the sub 8k price point.It beats down every android phone at this range in terms of performance, screen quality and built.Full marks to Nokia for this product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Functionality issues&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features, price very good, but functionality of applications there are some issues. Some of the applications don't integrate with the o.s. properly i.e we cannot sent multimedia files through blue tooth. There is problem with pairing also. Attaching files in Whatsapp is also not possible. Truecaller is not fuctioning propertly. Unless these issues are addressed immediately, this phone will lose its popularity. This cannot compete with android phones!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Phone!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bhai ab 7.5k me bachche ki jaan loge kya!!&lt;br&gt;people are saying it doesn't have a flash...only has 512 mb ram...and like! if you are so tech savvy then shell out some more dude...why even bother buying this phone. For others..just go for it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked this phone. kudos to Amazon for delivering it on time.&lt;br&gt;Good windows phone, sturdy build and quality.&lt;br&gt;Very smooth.&lt;br&gt;What I liked so much was the free Office suite they have - Word, Powerpoint and Excel - for free.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But, no profiles for silent, outdoor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good phone for office purposes.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worst experience ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I will never any electronic good from you. the cell phone I gotvwas rusted from within and it stopped working. I went to a local Nokia repair center but they said that there is no warranty on online purchases. I had to buy a new cell phone. Horrible experience. I am going to post this in all consumer forums  and make sure that people dont fall prey to this again.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Bang for the buck!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There isn't much that can be said about this except that you get what you pay for, which is still a lot better than some of Android competition in this price range barring the Moto G. Bought it for a friend and it was intuitive enough for a first-time user like him to dive into and effectively use the phone. Would recommend it for anyone taking the step into smartphones. A capable device indeed and Thank you Amazon for the quick 1-day delivery too! Glad to see someone bringing world-class service to India!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good service from amazon.i always buy from amazon.online shopping is the best way for buying goods.cheap prices.i love it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lumia 520 best in the base model of smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile is best , meets our basic requirements, mails documents&lt;br&gt;works, superb build quality by Nokia, touch, and apps windows 8 every thing is great&lt;br&gt;the to use the device best,&lt;br&gt;to conserve the battery to last for more than two day we have to limit extensive internet and song usage. Other wise it would last for 1 or 1 and half&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Absolute delight to buy the Lumia520.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great product. Great pricing. Happy to be a part of amazon shopping. Thanx a lot.Lokk forward to shop more from amazon !!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Deal for the day&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good deal for that Price. Camera is a concern, rest is OK for that price. Amazon gives good offers for these sort of items.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone within INR 10,000/-&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a very nice phone for a price within INR 10,000/-&lt;br&gt;Looks good, easy to use, has the basic features of a smart phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is a little shortage in good handy apps but windows app store is on a ramp-up now.&lt;br&gt;over all a good one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I am loving it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Yes it does meet my expectation....I purchased it to gift it to my Dad and he is very happy using it&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you Amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best phone ever at this price, everyone whos going with brands like micromax, samsung or any other are wasting m0ney unless u dnt gonna use it... Nokia making the best phones after apple... Its outstanding n never dissapoints you... Thanks amazon fr this deal..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing Amazon!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had order Lumia 520 for my wife's birthday gift n I got this on timely, thanks to Amazon,awa gadget is very sweet n I love to online shopping with Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Deal for windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;For a win phone at odd 7k, Nokia gives in everything what you would expect in a phone.&lt;br&gt;Buy it if you are still getting it under 7k, &amp;amp; you still trust NOKIA&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;windows mobile is far far better than android phones i have already used android but lumia windows phone is amazing.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good phone, features are better than android, all the good apps are available at store..Ultimate phone Nokia has really matched the quality with ecocomy...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you want to have a good phone at the price of around 7,500, then it is strongly recommended. I can assure you guys that no brand can give you that much feature in this price, it has everything  in this price. I have used all Samsung phones under 15000 thousand all were failed compare to this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advantages---  5 mp camera, awesome camera, full hd, has lot's of feature's in camera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  screen touch is smooth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  never hang up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  great battery  back up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  you can play full hd video even  1080 rip ( most of the phone doesn't support in this price)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  Great sound quality&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  stylish desktop which helps to open any application quickly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disadvantage--  no front camera -- This is the only disadvantage I felt in this phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All and all it has everything!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;dissat,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got that mobile and when I open box I found that charger is not working, cant xpect from amazon . Worst service, also I need to go to nokia care to replace my charger.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased Lumia 520 handset @ Oct 22nd 2013. After using 4 months Power on/off button not working.......... Something bad about Nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Honest review by a software Engg&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;HI All,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bought Nokia Lumia 520 on 15 Feb from Gadgets guru.&lt;br&gt;First of all thanks to amazon for great packaging and fast delivery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I used it for more than 20 days and i can rate mobile as 4.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Below are the prons and cos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;=========&lt;br&gt;1) Basic windows phone-good UI if you are not attracted by Android UI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2)Good battery life of more tan 1 day with average usage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3)HD Diplay compared with different basic phones at this range 8k-10k .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4)suffecient 512 MB RAM for decent use and internal 8Gb(user can ger &amp;gt;5Gb) expandable upto 64Gb(I inserted 8 GB) working fine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5) Camera is good in day light-in night you can not get decent pictures since flash is not there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6)Connectivity is good(Wifi,GPS,connecting PC) not tried 3G,2G with GPRS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7)Call quality is good,Audio output(speaker) is also good&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8)you can update Nokia softwares(i updated from Amber to Nokia black) working fine&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;==============&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1)Micro sim enabled-If you are using old type of sim ,you need to cut it in order to insert.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2)Flash is not there for CAM,no secondary cam.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3) Ear phones are of basic nokia type(open type) low output in ear phones,,need to buy another.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4)Volume and lock button need to be pressed with force.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5)Built In FM will not work properly,need to download FM App.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6)song forwarding upto sometime while listening music is difficult. U need to long touch forward button.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7)Battery is of 1430mah only.Appreciable if atleast 1800 provided.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;8)No call recording option.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9)You will got confused once you add multiple mail accounts(it will synchronise all contacts in people).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;like facebook,outlook,gmail all contacts will be saved in people which cause confusion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;10)No suitable Mozilla Firefox,Chrome browser in APPstore, only you can get IE10.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;11)Comparing windows App store vs Android play store is not suitable in Android you can get lot of games and apps of free but in windows you can get only limited free apps or games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you consider pros&amp;gt;cons please go for NOKIA. since it is a Brand--Finally Nokia gives you good value and fits in your hand adds value to you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you consider the mentioned cons are not minor so think before buy,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All the Best,&lt;br&gt;Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Super smart phone at a super cool price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone with top notch features. In begining I was quite skeptical about my purchase but ever since I took this phone out of box and powered it on it changed my view upside down. I am totally amazed looking at the quality features this budget phone offers. I myself am owing a samsung GS3 and purchased Lumia 520 as a gift for my dad and believe me I am more than satisfied with my decision to go for this model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Solid build Quality&lt;br&gt;2. Exceptional good looks&lt;br&gt;3. Top notch hardware&lt;br&gt;4. lag free operation - its way better then Galaxy S3&lt;br&gt;5. Cool interface&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1. No flash - but wait - Camera performance is still awesome - this phone comes with Nokia Smart Cam app whic makes Camera of this phone out of the crowd - its quite good without flash too. Flash could have been useful as a torchlight though ;)&lt;br&gt;2. No file manager - but again I dont see this as a major con since windows OS is designed in a manner that each app can see only file formats that it can support and no other file can be opened by the app. Hence if you want certain file then find it using the related app.&lt;br&gt;3. Nothing else :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I saw people complaining about less RAM but believe me 512MB RAM is more than sufficient for windows OS and every app that I have used so far in this phone runs quite smoothly (I tried some high end games too).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And Regarding FM - it works - Yyes you heard it right - FM WORKS after latest AMBER update.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally - yes its a cool choice - go for it blindly - you wont repent your decision.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Edit: One more con - no separate volume setting for Ringtone/Message Tone/Media (Ganes etc) tone - there is only 1 sound profile for all.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it is meeting my expectations nd i thnk its more than worth ......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is meeting my expectations nd i thnk its more than worth ......nd i boght it frm amazon.in m vry satisfied wit them&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got an amazing deal with amazon for this device. This device performance is quite amazing. 1 Ghz, Dual core is amazing spec for this price. Plus the WP8, is quite optimized and performs exceptionally well.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;amazon rocks, nokia's build quality awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got this at the cheapest possible price ever from amazon. Eligible for cash back as well on the cheapest price! Phone Is superb and no longer will go back to android. Nokia's touch is by far the best I've used. Happy with this purchase. Thanks Amazon!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;hurrrrraaahhhhhhhhhh..........&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nokia branded,faithful&lt;br&gt;windows branded,faithful&lt;br&gt;value for money(the best part about this phone)&lt;br&gt;safe operating system,u can rely on it&lt;br&gt;dimensions same as steve jobs's i-phone 4(almost same and to be true its better then i-phone)&lt;br&gt;go ahead and buy it&lt;br&gt;about amazon--&amp;gt; i used to like "fk" but now i am fan of amazon,better service better packaging,and polite delivery men....hats off&lt;br&gt;i would definitely buy next time from amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Phone for great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;What I liked about this:&lt;br&gt;1. Very smooth touch&lt;br&gt;2. UI is cool&lt;br&gt;3. Screen size is great&lt;br&gt;4. Sound quality is fine&lt;br&gt;5. Nice camera&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And it is a bit confusing as I am an android user previously.&lt;br&gt;But overall happy for the price I paid for this device.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth every penny spent!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At this price you cannot get anything better!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First order with amazon and I got this delivered by amazon directly great service, got this delivered in 2 days.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Windows got all the major apps required,&lt;br&gt;Touch is excellent.&lt;br&gt;Great battery unlike Android you do not need to connect your mobile to PC at office usually I see at my work place.&lt;br&gt;And a Great work phone outlook word excel superb!!!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Flash is something missing but in day light pictures are Good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone and cannot believe the amount of features and great look for price.. Nobody believes I paid less then Rs 10,000 for this one&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the issue is if you want to install an application manually then you need external memory card&lt;br&gt;So purchase memory card also&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Phone In its price..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought from here at 6700(7447+10% cashback)&lt;br&gt;awesome phone ,display,no lags,ultra smooth interface,and nokia...&lt;br&gt;Finally superbb phone in this price .....&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=9</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;I like it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i love its internet speed and updates&lt;br&gt;its camera was super&lt;br&gt;i like its style&lt;br&gt;i suggest this phone to all nokia lumia lovers&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth a buy for 7.7k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;An un compromised built quality by Nokia and a flawless, smooth transition by Microsoft had blended well for this Lumia 520. Completely satisfied for 7.7k worth it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amazon ... you will never get your product on time .. but delay with 4 -5 days .. with the pathetic service of Amazon ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FlipKart is better than this .. wahiyat service provider ....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very happy with this purchase. The phone works really well. Smooth interface and good looks. Very little lag time while switching between screens. Highly recommended!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;service is good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The colorful Lumia devices give a good show The Lumia 520 seamlessly fits itself into the lower end of Nokia's portfolio and supplies a great result in all tests. This is however always considering the retail price . It naturally cannot compete with the..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;googd product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good phone decent futures, value of money, good clarity of the phone, must buy with the budget...will enjoy..it  for sure&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone with good aesthetics&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a good budget smartphone if you are not an android fanboy. Though now 525 seems a good bet but still the phone has got good looks with decent specifications except amount of RAM. Go ahead buy this product if you want a decent smartphone under 8K.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Whatsapp download problems&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am not able to download Whatsapp.&lt;br&gt;My local mobile dealer says its software problem.&lt;br&gt;Wonder how to solve this problem&lt;br&gt;Binay&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Product at agreat Price.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;With Windows 8.1 update, this product will be a true gem &amp;amp; will make up its present shortcomings!! Recommended for first time buyer !!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Proved as product of Nokia in the Basic smartphone segment&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Lower end smart phone in the Basic segment.&lt;br&gt;Touch sensitivity and Build quality is good.&lt;br&gt;Best phone for Windows beginners.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=11</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good phone. has good features which are usable and less number of features which are not really used.&lt;br&gt;does not hurt when dropped for this price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nokia lumia 520 met my expectations and liked it very much....its a superb phone with good apps and games...thanks to amazon.in for bringing it fastly...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool Gadget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A nice smartphone @ &amp;lt;8000 bucks...although i am not a fan of touchscreen smartphones but it got me hooked for the first few days...a good quality phone and i don't have any such issues after using it for almost 8 months !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia lumia 620&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good mobile under 10000. All features are worth it's price. Good camera quality in daylight. Only problem is with not having flash.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good and nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice  and cute phone. There is no lag in processing .very attractive one.it is more good than nokia x. Thanks AMAZON and NOKIA.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The things that I would recommend to Nokia is to enhance the RAM to at least 750 MB and better battery backup.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;review of this product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia lumia 520 has good and besr performance and lowest  cost also in amazon only,not in limia any product in amazon is good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Budget phone. Rigid body.  Good camera for day light use.  Nokia applications good.  sound clarity good. waiting for WP 8.1 update.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia lumia 520 is Simply superb.......its a 512 mb ram phone but still it is very first..I just love it.&lt;br&gt;and the service of Amazon is awesome..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice product in this price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best thing in this mobile u will get is the touch sense and the display is marvelous. processor is also fast&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=13</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Am using this phone from one year and so happy to say that,it is the best thing i used ever,quality pics and fast 1ghz processor making it a great one..am getting a battery back up of 6 hours (3G)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Low Budget Smart Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a best smart phone in this budget. Easy to use. My first smart phone and i am loving it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;product quality is good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;product quality is good. this product is worthy. u cant get good smartphone with this price and that too from a brand like nokia.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased Nokia Lumia 520 before 2 months ago unfortunately its display was broken. Then I visited to Nokia Care they charged me 3950 for the display. I said that it was just 7 days old phone and u charge me half of its cost. Then I called Amazon Customer Care they returned the broken phone and pay my every one paisa. Amazon in the BEST.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my second phone in my family, after using the first lumina520, we were really impressed of the windows so.&lt;br&gt;Worth for the money you spend.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;how is the lumia 520. good and bad ......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the phones pretty good phone. meets all needed expectations. it s nice to have bing as well as office at your fingertips the design of the main screen is epic, tiles and all. there are a few problems though. first and worst, is the setup. being a microsoft phone it is tough to handle.you will need a nokia, microsoft phone, microsoft computer as well as own mail account. if you amke even a slight deviation in your personal details, you will have problems. I KNOW. my age didnt come right, too young, and so i couldnt download anything or any apps. the camera works well, but not in dim or dark areas (no flash). it also doesnt have many neccessities, like voice recorder and so on. the main pain in the ass is the setup, without which you cant do anything. also the music app, noia mix radio, doesnt allow you to download songs. you can only listen to songs and that to with only wi fi or internet or 3g. the phone is excellent from look standards though. overall it is a good phone but has some minor drawbacks.&lt;br&gt;nikhil out.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Real Budget Smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon:&lt;br&gt;- Delivered in time as mentioned.&lt;br&gt;- Product Original.&lt;br&gt;- Packing was good.&lt;br&gt;- Helpful interaction with amazon team :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bought this handset for my Dad at 6999 INR. Using it from 1 month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Positives:&lt;br&gt;- Light weight.&lt;br&gt;- Easy to hold and goes well in your pockets.&lt;br&gt;- Build quality excellent.&lt;br&gt;- Ips display perfect under sunlight.&lt;br&gt;- Sufficient features and applications available.&lt;br&gt;- Battery life very good last 3 -4 days.&lt;br&gt;- Operating system smooth no lag.&lt;br&gt;- Audio quality good.&lt;br&gt;- Voice clarity good.&lt;br&gt;- Camera apps and camera perfect in sunlight but decent performance under low light :(&lt;br&gt;- The most beautiful feature i found is the Kid's Corner. Here, you can create different profile for your kid. And you will be at peace, while your child is trying her hands at your mobile. With this profile, your child can not make any outgoing calls or can not mend with your important files in the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Restrictions:&lt;br&gt;- Front  camera&lt;br&gt;- Flash&lt;br&gt;- 512 mb RAM (few high graphics games lags or not possible to play at present).&lt;br&gt; So it is not disadvantages it is actually restriction of this handset ....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disadvantages:&lt;br&gt; - At 3G mode handset becomes hot and battery drains very fast .&lt;br&gt;- The headset bundled with box are not so good and don't have facility to answer the call from headset.&lt;br&gt;- There is no key to search within mobile, instead there is a key that takes you to the web search engine- Bing.&lt;br&gt;- File manager missing.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;World Class phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;World Class phone at budget price, Lot of features. This would have been a complete product it had got 1GB Ram. So if you ready to spend some more bugs, Simply go for Nokia Lumia 525.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not so happy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia... is a bit disappointing. The phone quality is not good. It does not gives that classy look. The plastic body looks cheap one. Samsung phones are anytime better. Even the windows platform is not easy to use. Go for Android phones only.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lacking basic features&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Like Email reply with attachment&lt;br&gt;can not see Call Duration.&lt;br&gt;Call recording not possible&lt;br&gt;No File Manager&lt;br&gt;requires login even for offline file access like videos and Music&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=12</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;extremely disappointed with product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After i got the product , i found that there was a problem in the phone. it did not switch on.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;loved the phone................&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i swear ... amazon rock!!!!!! i got the phone pretty fast nd it works awsome....&lt;br&gt;loved amazon though ths was my first shopping in amazon..there are no negative featuress till nw and i truly lovd the phone&lt;br&gt;amazon also gives it in very low price.........&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product worth lot&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is the most selling mobile in the market.From this itself is clearly seen that this mobile has lot of advantages over other mobiles for this price&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Perfect buy.  Look wise it is also awesome.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice phone.  Easy to use n handle for senior folks too. It is Great,  look n features wise.&lt;br&gt;Kalpesh Bhanushali&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good camera in thies range smooth ui best to buy ..!&lt;br&gt;honestly i recomand if you want best camera phone in thies range and want to try something different&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone for this Budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like this phone much and meets the expectations I had. Except for the 512 MB RAM and missing Flash for Camera, it serves well in all other areas. Especially for someone switching from Android to Windows, it's a welcome change indeed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Another sore point is the missing equalizer for Music Player. Audio Quality is so flat! Come on Windows, can't you have your own Windows Media Player in your own phones? Otherwise, a very good phone for it's price. A true VFM product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;amazing...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazing phone with this price range ..only thing is RAM. less then 1GB... if they could increased the ram up to 1GB with same price... also need manual on window user guide ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Horrible phone !&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Had trusted amazon but bad experience, phone was sent by univercell and the battery doesnt even stay for 3 hrs..!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great mobile in the budget.looks costly than highly rated phones.good speed,8 gb internal memory,fast ram,good applications.very good camera,big screens, up 64gb expandable memory.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Overall good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good product, quick delivery, good packing. Only disappointment with the phone is battery doesn't last long, have to charge at-least once a day.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=15</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Volume keys are not working&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hi,&lt;br&gt;I purchased Lumia 520 before a month or so.&lt;br&gt;Volume keys are not working whenever song is playing from Music+Videos app.&lt;br&gt;Volume keys are working only for next song.&lt;br&gt;-Jey&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;This is super economical smartphone available on Planet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is the best ever smartphone produced by Nokia in recent years. I am loving it. Nice phone, slim look, super clarity, fast, reliable, nice battery backup, rugged, what else you want from this smartphone. Thanks to Amazon for speedy delivery.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good entry phone from Windows.&lt;br&gt;+++&lt;br&gt;Nice camera.&lt;br&gt;Sufficient apps available&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;---&lt;br&gt;Low RAM&lt;br&gt;Not for gaming.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Value for money phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very bad amazon..........no return.where is my money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;bad site,,no one buy on amAZON&lt;br&gt;duplicte shpng web site .if ane one can buy any prdcts..... very cruel to our state&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very bad product &amp;amp; worst after sales service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought the mobile after trusting Nokia again after a long time, hoped a fresh &amp;amp; good experience with the windows phone. The phone charger went bad after a month, mobile worked till last month. When I took the mobile to Nokia care, they immediately agreed to replace charger as in warranty &amp;amp; sent the mobile to main service center. Now, they come up saying that the mobile cannot be repaired as water logged which I know is not true. So, I would suggest buy local brands rather than these hotshots as they give more &amp;amp; last more in less price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile was selected by my teenage daughter for her and she is happy with her choice. That makes me happy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is not Great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I heard and read big things about its feature but don't see too much. Volume is very low and camera is also not very good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best phone ,best at its price range ,  only concern is it doesnt have front camera and flash dddddd ddd&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;not bad not good..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good mobile..bt very few features...not satishfied with windows phone..i think android is better..&lt;br&gt;no flash in it...and most of applications are paid..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At this price its a nice phone.&lt;br&gt;Cant replace my iPhone. Its good for a second phone.&lt;br&gt;Would love to have some pull down dash...they way its on Andriod and iPhone...&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=10</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 Black&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Having problem setting it up have no proper details on how the set the setting and still in box that is came with one of my worst buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I feel happy of purchasing Nokia Lumia 520 in Amazon.in, the reason behind this is, when I start checking many online stores I found high rates but Amazon displays the low price compared to other, so I recommend Amazon.in as best choice.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;total value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Voice quality is awesome set, is slim and very easy to handle and carry.&lt;br&gt;I like this mobile because of this compatibility with Microsoft office. Using Microsoft onedrive its easy to synchronize file with laptop/desktop.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best price for Budget Smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best price for Budget Smart phone with great features.I am loving it. Recently upgraded to windows phone 8.1 beta, works great!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Online purchase is a quack's prescription&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I always vouched by Nokia &amp;amp; it's battery quality but not any more, or may be it is Amazon's way of draining away all the margin possible by compromising with the original battery &amp;amp; spares, as per my acquaintances in the likewise business.This has ruthlessly crushed the trust we put into Amazon's brand name . These websites are not worth huge investments, all that one can risk to buy is may be a low price T-shirt , for if it is not as good as touted - at least can serve as a dusting cloth.Have Processed for refund, let's see how good an experience is that. Still hopeful that at least the refund will be a measure to nil out the sufferings of buyer's dissonance. Will keep posted.Till then Amazon India - A big disappointment.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is good.....but.....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought lumia 520 from another shop. It is the best phone in this category in terms of display, camera, music etc. But it is very slow when compared to android. And also there is nothing in its app store. But by taking this as whole it is good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good for price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Battery backup is less, stays for a day after minimal usage of internet browsing. build quality and camera is good for the price&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Guys,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Trust me, this is seriously good ... Completly worth to buy ... Go ahead without any hesitation...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheers,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aditya&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;product review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i am satisfied with the product but your ward took 500RS extra so please refund my money as soon as possible&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone used ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If any one interested in buying this phone,used for only 25 days&lt;br&gt;Can contact me or add me on WhatsApp on 07618825160&lt;br&gt;For Rs 7300 with a smiley cover n screenguard free...&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=16</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;not satisfactory&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Beware.....do not purchase from axisbank credit card&lt;br&gt;Cash Back on Credit card purchase is not provided me since oct-2013&lt;br&gt;but there is no support from AMAZON&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Phone under the whole segment !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I choose this phone for better Navigation,but its up to my expectations the built in app Here Drive is awesome,and the touch of the phone is superb ,and Quality of Camera is Really Pretty good (y) but the phone does not have a front camera so its impossible to make a video call.otherwise its an awesome product by Nokia.&lt;br&gt;windows is really more better than Androids.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good phone in this price range.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is amazing and works smoothly without any problems of it getting hanged. Only problem that I would like to point out is that it lacks flash light with the camera.&lt;br&gt;If that doesn't bother you much than go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia after losing the market, have come back well with this phone. Android users might find it difficult with the screens and menus; however it is a windows phone and works best.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Internal memory stands apart and camera works beautifully.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Currently using it and it's  working perfectly..only there is no option to select personalised toned..can some 1 help..otherwise good phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am using nokia lumia 520 since last two weeks and its a good phone. Following are things I liked and disliked&lt;br&gt;Liked&lt;br&gt;- The touch is super and works really good&lt;br&gt;- The UI is clean and easy to use&lt;br&gt;- I never experienced any lag and works really fast&lt;br&gt;- I am loving the speech commands to call and open apps these are really handy.&lt;br&gt;Disliked&lt;br&gt;- My expection about battary does not meet with Nokia, it barely lasts for a day with moderate usage&lt;br&gt;- The headset bundled with box are not so good and dont have facility to answer the call from headset&lt;br&gt;- There is no option to answer call using speech command which I desperately wanted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a decent phone for the price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awsome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Yes i am happy thank you . .. ......  . .&lt;br&gt; . . . . . . .  . .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NOKIA LUMIA 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After ordering 1 st order I order 2nd phone one more member of family.&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon product on economical rates.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;hi very good phone nokia lumia 520 i like  my using to phone , internet good fast...... i like nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Poor battery backup&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;need to create microsoft account.poor battery backup,on sunlight nothing is visible,gps and navigation is good,easy download and high speed net available.the main thing is really poor battery backup,&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=14</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool phone at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When hunting for a new mobile phone, being biased by flood of android based phones in market, in beginning I was bit skeptical about Windows OS. But its just a matter of a couple of days of hands on it, I found it is better than my existing android phone. No hangs, no delays, utter smooth operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People said that there are few apps for Windows, I found that there are lot of options for normal users. May be for app freaks, they may be less!&lt;br&gt;For someone who is addicted to social media apps like facebook, this is the best phone. Facebook is deeply integrated in the OS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Touch is near perfect. Performance is superb which I judged by playing Asphalt 5 game on the device, it runs as charm with full details on! I liked the "Kid's Corner" feature, very useful when you have kids around.&lt;br&gt;Build quality is very good, form factor and screen size are optimum. Feels good to hold in hands. Offline maps feature is decent however you may not find it as informative as google maps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some features may be lacking (like easy interface for enabling, data networks, WiFi, Bluetooth and Airplane mode), but then there is widget for that. It would be better if this widget comes pre-installed in the OS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sound is quite good. Creating and managing playlists is a pain. I am unable to figure out a clean way of doing it yet. But once done that should not bother any user regularly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call quality, voice clarity etc are very good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a very good phone in this price range. Of course quite a good bargain when bought from Amazon as compared to other online stores as well as retailers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Goo phone in 6800&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all thanks to Amazon, for coming in India and giving great service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. I bought this handset in 6800 with 10% axis bank cash back.&lt;br&gt;2. Technical specs, awesome.&lt;br&gt;3. Camera picture quality very good.&lt;br&gt;4. No lag, No hang..Awesome virus free user interface.&lt;br&gt;5. I was a samsung galaxy S advance user, and simply speaking..samsung is rubbish infront of this phone.&lt;br&gt;6. Touch is amazing.&lt;br&gt;7. Battery Life is very Good.&lt;br&gt;8. OS is user friendly.&lt;br&gt;9. Weight is Ok.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dont think much, Go for it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Happy Diwali.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;totally paisa vasool phone!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The price for which I've bought this phone is less than Rs.6800. And, trust me, I'm loving keeping this phone as my secondary phone. The touch response is awesome, switching app is even smoother, using a windows OS is totally different than the Android as I'm using Nexus 4, and I'm loving using this new OS in such a nice phone in this price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now coming on to the services of amazon.in&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have always considered that flipkart has the best services, may it be refunding process, replacement process, cancellation process or delivery time. But this time, amazon.in has played its part after stepping into the world of competition in Indian market. Trust me I'm amazed the way they have started their website by such low prices for almost every product. Their own courier facility is even better than Flipkart that anyone can rely on it without keeping any followup. I must say that other leading websites like Flipkart and Ebay must start thinking upon their new rival now as its gonna be the best in few time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wish you guys all the very best! Kudos!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic phone at budget price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Smooth and best interface..&lt;br&gt;512 MB RAM feels very low but you never notice it..&lt;br&gt;8GB internal memory (you get 5+ GB free) - no other device offers so much in this price range..&lt;br&gt;look and feel - wow!! (windows 8 beats android and iOS comprehensively in this department)&lt;br&gt;touch - brilliant!!&lt;br&gt;build quality - it is a Nokia phone.. you know what they are like..&lt;br&gt;video clarity - very good&lt;br&gt;camera - best in this range (7000 - 10000)..&lt;br&gt;dimensions perfectly suit my hands..&lt;br&gt;been using it for about a month and so far absolutely no complaints..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;negatives: no front camera, flash, apps and games are limited..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bottomline: If you can live without front camera, this is the best phone to buy within Rs. 10k budget!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Though i purchased this before amazon.in was live. I have been using this phone for last 3 months and the experience so far has been really good.&lt;br&gt;The office integration works like a charm. Windows OS is really fast. Looks like nokia has finally got things right with lumia series&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best mobile under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am quite an old fashioned person when it comes to electronic gazettes. I was never fascinated by smartphones, tablets and other touch screen devices and was very happy with my simple basic mobile. It was only accidentally that i gave it a thought to go for a smartphone after i lost my mobile and my techno-savvy friend advised me to go for this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transition from a simplest basic mobile to the Smartphone could never be more easier, thanks to Nokia Lumia 520 and Windows 8.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do not know much technical bits to appraise this mobile, but i can state many of its advantages from a layman's angle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Excellent build quality- I dropped it on a cement road from my bicycle to find it in three pieces. But nothing was damaged.&lt;br&gt;2. For it's primary usage as a phone- Excellent voice quality, speaker phone is at its best. Signal reception is also very good. SMS Interface is very different than regular basic phones and i found it to be quite innovative.&lt;br&gt;3. Screen size of 4' is quite appropriate. It fits in your palm well and goes in the packet very nicely.&lt;br&gt;4. Display quality is excellent. It may not have the best viewing angle though, but for a single viewer, you get the best.&lt;br&gt;5. Windows 8 feels amazing. Very user friendly, desktop kind of interface and positioning of apps could not be more simple.&lt;br&gt;6. It will not be wise to ignore Windows phones thinking that it does not have enough apps. You would find apps for almost all of your needs.&lt;br&gt;7. The most beautiful feature i found is the Kid's Corner. Here, you can create different profile for your kid. And you will be at peace, while your child is trying her hands at your mobile. With this profile, your child can not make any outgoing calls or can not mend with your important files in the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though, there are some limitations as below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. There is no front camera, but what more can you expect in a budget phone.&lt;br&gt;2. No radio. But for me, it doesn't matter. I do have best radio apps downloaded in my phone.&lt;br&gt;3. There is no key to search within mobile, instead there is a key that takes you to the web search engine- Bing. I can't justify a separate key only to search over web.&lt;br&gt;4. Lack of Dual SIM. Don't understand why Nokia does not have this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, i found this to be the best smartphone with a budget below 10K. Go for it even if your budget is more than it. It is worth for each and every paisa!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best starter smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The hardware and the os are top notch and I am really loving the purchase for the price it is being offered.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;For 7.5k good phone and no lag- great useability and I love Here drive and Nokia music. Good integration of all the social app.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone at affordable price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;superb working. No lag at all like android phones. Camera is also of good quality. Internet speed is also too good. No lag in playing HD videos.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is good phone in less price. It includes almost all the features and performance is good. Battery is aslo good.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Faulty Phone....Problems from first week..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The Black Nokia Lumia 520 purchased in November 2013, was perhaps the worst purchase made by me online. The phone right from day one had technical problems with Voice cracking up. I have visited the Nokia store 3 times in the last 4 months (every time the phone has been kept for minimum 7-10 days) and the problem persists. Every time they repair it, the same problem persists. The voice ends up cracking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This whole experience has left a very bad impression in my mind for online Cellphone purchases and I am certain that the handset had a manufacturing defect when it got shipped to me. When I contacted the seller for help, all he offered was that "you should take it up with Nokia".  Please AVOID BUYING THIS ONLINE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Super fluid interface, great phone at a great price. It's a touch slow sometimes due to low memory but more than serves a purpose of a smart phone!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Value for Money Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is one of the best value for Money Smart Phone available in the crowded budget smartphone market today.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Pros:&lt;br&gt;Nokia Brands Assurance with excellent and well established service setup&lt;br&gt;Windows 8 OS which delivers excellent result even with 512 MB RAM. (Thanks to Bottom up approach of Nokia in developing the device in such a way)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons: Cannot shift APPS to SD Card.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a fantastic value buy. Top it with Amazon's regluar Cash Back schemes which makes the deal even better.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia lumps 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really nice phone ....It is super cool and fast...best phone to use with an affordable price. ...thank you Nokia Lumia 520..!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not reliable&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;All products are awesome !! Except pen drive !! When I ordered pen drive in website deal was 16 GB but after purchase I got email stating that it was 8 GB !! It's a irritating factor need reply ASAP&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Windows is better than android  for all features like all apps ,user interface,visual,picture clarity everything is perfect but some features are not availabe.........&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;For those who uses phone as phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Using it for one week. First windows phone after series of android phones.&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Awesome UI. No glitches no hanging.&lt;br&gt;2. Although fitted with a matte screen guard, easy to read in sunlight&lt;br&gt;3. Awesome camera.&lt;br&gt;4. Very good battery back-up. Lasts one and half days with heavy using.&lt;br&gt;5. Very good network reception and good voice clarity.&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1. No swype keyboard. But it is coming in windows 8.1.&lt;br&gt;2. A bit odd to hold and type in one hand due to excess width.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go for it if you need a nice phone to be used as phone mostly.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Works great. Touch is nice. Apps are few though but they are coming quite often now. Satisfied with the product. Value for money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Pleasure to use&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is very good except battery capacity is very low. I have to charge frequently.&lt;br&gt;I like all features, cost low for a windows phone and pleasure to use. I would have given 5 star if at least a minimum of 1800 mAH battery was provided. Micro SIM is to be used, so I have to get a new SIM and could interchange from my other phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice mobile in low price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice Mobile in low price. ..&lt;br&gt;Moderate speed and almost all function are available&lt;br&gt;Difficult to operate for the first time (:-)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=18</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia still the market leader, I like this product, as it full fill all my requirements. It is the best cheapest phone Nokia provide for the users like me.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to AMAZON and Nokia....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It really awesome, cheap and best mobile available at present.&lt;br&gt;I love it&lt;br&gt;I love it&lt;br&gt;I love it&lt;br&gt;I love it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value for money. It meets what I wanted from this device. Nice response, touch, no lagging.. It's just awesome. Cool.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia is any time better than any Samsung phone Or Windows are any day better than android&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good looking phone, Nice screen,good viewing angles.&lt;br&gt;Faster than any android phone within this price range or even above.&lt;br&gt;Compatiable with most of the important apps and I personally think within 1yr or so windows phone will surpass android phones in terms of apps also. Battery is also good.&lt;br&gt;In simple reviewing language total paisa wasool&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;a very good product with solid hardware. sporting window 8.1 as its big brothers make it all the more cool!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best under 9k.....but its sibling 525 is doing the best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best under 9k.....but its sibling 525 is doing the best&lt;br&gt;because of 512 mb ram we need to restart mobile for atleast once in a week apart from this my lumia 520 is doing the best&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;just awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is superb ..... Just looking damn cool in hands....... Lovely product....&lt;br&gt;loved shopping from amazon.in&lt;br&gt;gr8 experience...:)&lt;br&gt;lovely&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Budget SmartPhone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best  phone under 10k .good music,camera,browsing,touch quality.No need to install any external browsers.Internet explorer is exceptionally good.i easily copied contacts from my old phone to Lumia 520 by using Transfer My Data App.  Hangs when signal is week and some times while receiving calls.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Best Apps:&lt;br&gt;Nokia Cam scanner,Photo Funia,Transfer My data.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;average&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its started giving problems after 1-month of usage.. call is being dropped every time i make a call. also the phone started hanging...it heats up when u use it while charging n during multitasking.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;a fantastic gift for ur loved ones&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i gave this mobile to my gf and shez happy a way too happy. best mobile at this price. you gonna love it.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=19</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best valued Windows8 Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Microsoft buys Nokia phone business, and I choose Windows over Android.&lt;br&gt;So much is praised for Nokia Lumia 520 at various review/testing platforms and sites.&lt;br&gt;It is worth buy budget phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;thank amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good so far thank amazon thank for good product &amp;amp; service. Thank again.great price affordable I reccomend. Keyboard is a bit small otherwise&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;LUMIA 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Outstanding performance at this price absolutely lag-free phone and I am very satisfied with the deal with Amazon. The live chat room of Amazon is also very helpful.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it's good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;cute smart phone with low price and use full applications are loaded in it&lt;br&gt;Its very nice and useful to me.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice and Genuin Product and Good Service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked Nokia Lumia 520.&lt;br&gt;It is Fresh piece.&lt;br&gt;And I liked Amazone Service very much.&lt;br&gt;Thank you very much.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing purchasing experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was my first purchase on amazon and price I got still I consider one of the best price I got and best part I got cash back offer also.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product is okay...not bad not great but on this price one of the best looking and touch experience...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i really liked this phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its very smooth, display is good, typing is fast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only issue I faced was while trying to run the VLC media files (.flv), its not running properly. I have yet to find a proper app for it, if it exists&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;V.GOOD&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;VERY GOOD EXP. AMAZON,S VERY FAST &amp;amp; QUICK ONLINE STORE. I LOVE SHOPING FROM IT.&lt;br&gt;&amp;amp; ALSO TELL MY FRIENDS FOR THIS STORE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its the best phone for the price... Nokia maintains its standard... Love it.. Ppl looking for reviews, just buy it..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I LOVE AMAZON !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I GOT MY ORDER IN RIGHT ON TIME. GOOD PACKING AND GOOD SERVICE .I BOUGHT LUMIA 520 BLACK FOR JUST 6999.!!!!&lt;br&gt;THANKS A LOT....&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=17</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia is always a best company.Windows Phones are better than android.I love it&lt;br&gt;The touch of this mobile is really smooth and awesome. Really good mobile by NOKIA.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not so good///&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Go for Samsung Galaxy S Duos instead!  Battery life is not good.  The home screen design is good and I am loyal to Nokia in some ways... but quality and performance of this phone leaves a lot to be desired.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NOKIA LUMIA 520 good windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My experience is being good with it .&lt;br&gt;Like :-&lt;br&gt;1- Screen , graphics , Display is very good .&lt;br&gt;2- Battery backup is good .&lt;br&gt;3- Build quality is good&lt;br&gt;4- sound is clear , camera is good in day&lt;br&gt;5- AND nokia trusted brand&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dislike :-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1- NO FM radio&lt;br&gt;2- No flash light&lt;br&gt;3- Apps availability is poor&lt;br&gt;4- UI little bit difficult to understand Android users&lt;br&gt;5- Single and mini sim&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its exceeded my expectations. I am more than happy to use this and look forward to buy more from amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I Like it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone with amazing features and windows platform gives you great support…&lt;br&gt;five star rating is for Nokia Lumia 520,,,good service by amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Received Product on time and in perfect condition. Excellent customer service. GOod variety of products available and good discounts available on website&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good phone at the price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had been using this phone for about a month now.Initially,I had been hesitant to try out a window phone.I decided to go for it keeping in ming Nokia's track record for making dependable,cost dffective product.Following are my observation.&lt;br&gt;Touch:Very responsive&lt;br&gt;Looks:Average&lt;br&gt;Utility:Userfriendly,once you get used to the interface.&lt;br&gt;3G data speed:Average&lt;br&gt;Browsing with wi-fi:Satisfactory&lt;br&gt;Availability of apps to download:Adequate(Though nothing like Android Apps)&lt;br&gt;Compatiability to different appa:Very good.&lt;br&gt;Camera quality:The 5MP camera is quite impressive and the panorana feature especially works very well outdoors.Only drwback is non availability of flash&lt;br&gt;overall,a dependable,value for money entry level smartphone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumina&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked the phone very much. it is compact and cost effective. Also Amazon gave me a very decent discount of more than 2500/- rupees. it is worth.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A windows phone of Nokia at this price is an excellent deal..will look forward for more purchases. thank you .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;phone is simply superb&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is really amazing product from nokia , if u wanna give a gift then this would be a right option for an affordable price&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=20</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item></items>