<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Total Paisa Vasool&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There could'nt be a better phone for a price range 7500-8000.&lt;br&gt;Not the best phone specs wise, but a really good budget phone.&lt;br&gt;If u are not much of a heavy gamer, i'ed suggest u go in for it.&lt;br&gt;Subway surfer, world at arms, etc. work very well without any lag.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good entry level windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;As with all nokia phones, solid construction and great battery life.  I personally love windows so it is what I wanted.  but considering what you pay if you compare to android phones in the market it is smaller in screen size and probably less features.  great for everyday use as a normal touchscreen phone with smart options. only drawback is micro sim, so you have to get the sim cut and if you are planning to flip to other phones you will have a problem with the sim&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it has issues like srt problem, shortage of app  ,but overall it is very good for low budget mobile .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a good phone with windows starting range..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The performance is good and other features are also good as per its price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;worth buying for this rate.Delivered in time.For those who are camera lovers, it may not be that much good as the flash is not there. But in daylight it is giving nice pics..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I am Satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought the nokia lumia 520 model in mid november. The experience has been trouble free. Despite the fact that the model has hanged on two-three occations. Altogether I am happy and satisfied. :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Unsatisfactory&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The battery backup of the phone was not as expected. Lasts only 18hrs even without using the phone for anything.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is defective peice - not working properlu&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It worked well for 2-3 weeks, battery is getting switched off regularly. it is defective piece. we are loosing confidence level ordering online&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice one untill it FALLS !!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is nice, working butter soft but if it falls, screen down, den u have no other option but to change it even with the small hair line cracks. SAMSUNG phones do work in such cases. Many of my frnds cracked their samsung phone screen but it is still working fine but the case is not same with LUMIA. Better to buy a good protective cover.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bought it from Amazon, nice service, received within the mentioned dates.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent budget phone, awesome voice recognition for Indian accent,better than Siri and Google now since it is local on the phone and does not requires internet. Good touch screen, smooth iPhone like interface experience. It's better than android phones in price range &amp;lt; Rs 20000&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=24</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone; value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have two Windows Phones in the family already, and bought a 520 to upgrade my mom to a smartphone from her old feature phone. I had options in Nokia Asha, cheap Androids, Nokia Lumia 520 and 525.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheap Androids are just that. Cheap. I skipped Asha in favour of the Lumia. While most folks would recommend 525 over 520 because the former has 1 GB RAM instead of 512 MB as in latter, but that's only a factor if you play a lot of games. Some games don't run on 520. I haven't heard of any issue with any apps running on 512 MB phones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My mother would not play games, so I opted for 520, about 2K cheaper than 525. It's a great device, and pretty good build quality for a sub-8K phone. Gets all the latest update, runs all the apps that she needs, and I'm buying a back panel in a different color to give her the variety.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Limitations, listing just in case: 512 MB RAM, no front camera, and no flash with rear camera.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Windows Phone in &amp;lt; 9K range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I baught this for my sister who is completing her graduation and i quote this as the best Windows mobile available below 8.5K range. Screen Size is optimum, meaning its not flaunting big and so can carry it in pockets and operate it with single hand. Touch is really good and Camera quality is decent [looking at the camera of 920 where the autofocus excites us]. It has all those features of extra costly smartphones and processing speed is always good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone to have&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice to have it! But windows getting strucked many times. Still good piece to have......... have a good day. tc&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone to have&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really good phone. 3g internet works fine. Games well played.&lt;br&gt;only battery drains quickly. And fm radio is scrap.&lt;br&gt;nokia black os is better.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent product best thing about this product is to get free official music i always download Bollywood and kids music like rymes etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What i dont like about this product is it dont have flash for taking photo and eventually photos are not so clear in dark.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other wise its excellent mobile touch screen is excellent, business email is also nice.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;delivered in the given time and a great phone but ram is 512 mb so cannot take much load but execpt this all other features are good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I love Windows&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A very handy and light phone in lower segment of smartphone. All Nokia Lumias are responsive with super sensitive touch. Windows at present does not give you option to customize a lot. But it will make you feel for a promising OS. Works like butter even with 512 RAM.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;about lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its really good to work with......&lt;br&gt;but the battery backup time is not as specified....&lt;br&gt;some times it may hangs&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice mobile for the price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;everything was good there won,t be any problems like android like slow because of low ram.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;good mobile for the price under Rs.10,000&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cheap best and budged phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i i i i i i am happy&lt;br&gt;best and good delever with in time&lt;br&gt;very  best  deal with amazon.in&lt;br&gt;thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=21</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone in range below 8k if you want windows&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Go for Samsung Galaxy s duos if you love apps and games. but if you consider windows phone its the best in low end phones&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Budget Phone...Period !!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got this phone for my father and I'm happy with the buy. My father is a first time smartphone user and he's getting used to the functioning of the phone very fast as the interface is very simple and clean. This phone fulfils his requirements perfectly, which are limited to listening music and browsing at the moment. This phone has worked perfectly till date without misbehaving even once.&lt;br&gt;Considering the competition in the market in this price range which included several phones with low end hardware running on sluggish and resource hungry android, this  Windows phone was a logical purchase. With the 8.0 OS becoming more open and uncluttered as compared to the 7.5, the performance is very smooth and the balance between the hardware and the OS is perfect.With the 8.1 update round the corner this beautiful product can only get better.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phone has a rugged and solid feel to it, miles ahead of products dished out by the likes of Samsung in this price range. If you are looking for a phone under 8k you should go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Windows os.nothing in it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia windows mobile.ok product.run by windows os.....amazon is a trend setter in online bussiness.better option is get best mobile if you spend some more amount.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice and cheaper product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice and cheaper product, i recommend Amazon to my friends since the service is excellent and we could get the product soon than we expect&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i am really thankful to  amazon......its really a smart cell phone....now i dont need to buy a camera ....and laptop.................&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone in comparison to its price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Yes high configuration games will not run on this but then you are not buying this for 20000+ , for day today life it will more than serve your purpose.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good deal for this Nokia lumia 520 window mobile phone with 10% cash back through Axis bank debit card purchasing.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;WoW&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I Never like that Nokia lumia ?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But I try to use very fantastic phone&lt;br&gt;I Love Nokia lumia&lt;br&gt;i Very Happy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone but sometimes it hangs up here &amp;amp; there&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Phone  but hangs up in certain situations. May be Nokia needs to develop patches to rectify the situation. Otherwise all is well.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Unique Features&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;SUPERB CAMERA WITH UNIQUE FEATURES AND OFFICIAL LOOK TOO MAKE IT DIFFERENT FROM OTHER CELLS IN ITS CATEGORY. USER FRIENDLY TOO&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=22</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb phone with superb rate,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon always doing amazing :).&lt;br&gt;I have checked in all the online stores and showrooms prize were too high but here really cheat, trust worthy and order processing come service quality always Amazon Amazing.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic....,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awasome mobile f'm nokia....... Good touch, camera is fantastic., overall nice product.  This is my 1st purchase from amazon&lt;br&gt;m very satisfied by its service, packing was amazing , thank u amazon,,  only one suggestion- provide special offers or coupons to reguler customers........&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Average&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia is not as it was five year ago. . .&lt;br&gt;All I say that its average product. . .only plus point is pre installed Office and good camera quality. . rest you miss anroid. . . even you cant find a video player at window store just VLC and that is also paid....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like this product very much. Its smooth and looks trendy. Windows OS rocks for its simplicity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But sometimes phone gets hang but after restart everything runs smooth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyways good phone in this budget.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Decision to purchase LUMIA 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Price is really worth the phone quality :P&lt;br&gt;I booked it for a nearly low range budget in the category of smartphones for around Rs.8000.. But proud to say I'm happy to use this product !! :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;reasonable.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;paisa wasool!! With reference to it's price, definitely worth it. Didn't face a single problem when i bought it.  No defects.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome Touch Experience, Fast Response to Applications,&lt;br&gt;Excellent Product, Worth for Price. I really loved it,&lt;br&gt;Low price and good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A little expensive. as AT&amp;amp;T is giving it at around 4,000/-&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A little expensive. as AT&amp;amp;T is giving it at around 4,000/- The phone itself is good. the features are all there.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchase this phone basically for mailing and navigation purpose and its up to my expectation. Its battery backup is also good and last till evening in which I have some calls, mailing, navigation, others apps and some games also.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;wifi restrictions..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I dislike tis mobile bcoz we can't assign static ip. My office wifi is integrated modem. I cant use d wifi in my office..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=27</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good touch, good working but single SIM, amazon price offered was very very good, no where at this price the same product was available.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good  budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you want the feeling of using Windows phone then go for it as it has everything which you can think for the Win phone.&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;Win8&lt;br&gt;Durable&lt;br&gt;Stylish&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;Strict policies of using with other phones&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very reasonable deal &amp;amp; value for money product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this phone about 3-4 months back and I can say that the product is excellent and absolutely value for money.  Also the deal I got on Amazon was amazing. I will recommend Amazon &amp;amp; Nokia Lumia 520.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;VFM kudos to nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a beauty beast looks really good. touch is ultra smooth. cam is ok ok. UI is awsome. but installing apps is a headache process unlike android. But still its a great mobile at this price...........&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NOKIA LUMIA 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;PROMPT DELIVERY IN VERY GOOD PACKING. WORKING WELL - I AM HAPPY. BOUGHT AGAINST OFFER IN JANUARY 2014 FROM SBI CARDS TO AMAZON.IN - YET TO GET THE DISCOUNT AS PROMISED. HOPE THE MATTER GETS RESOLVED SOON. OTHERWISE AMAZON.IN IS PRICE WISE REASONABLE AND SERVICE WISE VERY GOOD.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia WINDOWS PHONE 8 ROX :D&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Simply it is better than Android and similar to iPhone.&lt;br&gt;still i would recommend Nokia Lumia 525/720/820&lt;br&gt;You ROCK Windows Phone :D&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is amazing ,with in 3days got it.&lt;br&gt;thanks a lot.It is working nicly.I apprciate your efforts.windos phone that too nokia lumia 520.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;value of money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;perfect purchase for this price and configuration also nokia brand is world's renowned.  i purchasing it &amp;amp; it was value of money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value for money. Dropped many times but still didn't get even a scratch......Battery is good....... The only drawback is the camera is not good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;An excellent phone at such a competitive price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am using this phone for 5 months now and quite satisfied with its performance. This is the cheapest phone at such a bargain price with a brand like NOKIA.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=28</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Defect Phone Delivered!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;While communicating with the phone my ear is paining I think there must be some defect. I want my phone to be replaced...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best in Range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No Cons, just Best In Range, cause it is feature packed, very good camera quality, and simply awesome, that's all i have to say&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;This is my first smartphone (Lumia 520) and I am writing this review on the 2nd day of usage.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When I searched for a smartphone I looked for&lt;br&gt;1. Stunning display with good viewing angle&lt;br&gt;2. Smooth touch&lt;br&gt;3. Good AF Camera&lt;br&gt;4. Simple UI&lt;br&gt;5. Office suit&lt;br&gt;6. Long operation without heating up.&lt;br&gt;Lumia 520 has all the features I looked for and it comes under my budget below 8K.&lt;br&gt;Lumia 520 is good for&lt;br&gt;Stunning display&lt;br&gt;Ultra smooth touch&lt;br&gt;No lag&lt;br&gt;Luxury design&lt;br&gt;AF camera&lt;br&gt;Windows OS&lt;br&gt;Nokia brand value&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It's bad for&lt;br&gt;No stop button in music player!!! But u can pause it.&lt;br&gt;Can't remove SD card without removing battery&lt;br&gt;No Gallery/File Manager&lt;br&gt;Camera quality is not good in low light condition&lt;br&gt;No pre-installed apps, games, video, audio, wallpaper.&lt;br&gt;No profile management&lt;br&gt;Difficult call history management. No call duration summary&lt;br&gt;No distinction between Incoming/Outgoing/Missed calls&lt;br&gt;To set a song as ring tone u need an app.&lt;br&gt;To change ur device name, u need a computer&lt;br&gt;Single volume control for all types of sound; ring tone, alarm tone, music player, alerts&lt;br&gt;Can't zoom or pause while recording video&lt;br&gt;Can't delete multiple messages from a thread in one go.&lt;br&gt;Without internet it is nothing&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520 is realiable&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery backup is not good its backup only 5-6 hour,sometimes mobile is hanged when you call, video quality is good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fast and reliable&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Purchased Lumia 520 from Amazon, I am satisfied with the phone....windows phone is very fast and does not lag at all....nokia services are awesome like nokia music, maps, camera apps are good....only drawback I see is that it does not have equalizer and phone gets heated up after heavy use....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;If you are a person who isn't concerned about advanced apps then you can definitely go for it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good budget phone. Good build quality and battery backup!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But the problem is there are only few good/useful apps for windows. You will regret buying this if u compare this with android or iphone apps. I personally found two things ridiculous:&lt;br&gt;(1) No File Manager/Explorer.&lt;br&gt;(2) You should be connected to the internet to install any app.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Final word: If you are a person who isn't concerned about advanced apps then you can definitely go for it. Value for money!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered this phone on sunday and its in my hand on tuesday brand new peice shipped nicely and quickly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;about the phone its really great every thing is great the UI the touch the internet the ram is also good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nokia lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best look in this range, window 8 a new thing for mobile. Best shopping experience with amazon. Internal memory very  good. Screen size good enough. Amazon has very fast and good delivery procedure&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia at lowest price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Premium phone at lowest price.&lt;br&gt;Best phone available at this price. Robust design and best windows platform.(I feel the platform more user friendly like the windows OS in PC we are all familiar with)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Smart phone at its price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was looking for a phone  which is data enabled and shall run the basic application .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nokia 520 has met all my requirement . Moreover the touch is as comparable as a any high end phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=23</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;SMART&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very handy.meets the expectations and also worth the money paid .Colour appropriate,looks sleek  in hand&lt;br&gt;comparitively available at competetive price&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good budget mobile.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Received the mobile at offer price. Excellent so far. Little difficult to start with as the options and settings of a windows mobile are different.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lumia 520 is great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is good - in fact more than i expected. I was sceptical abt Windows phone. but i was proved wrong&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;great! i am loving it.contrast  to all around me using android phone i went for windows because of nokia and very confidently i can say that i am proud of my choice.and how i can forget about amazon it has great service, provides every thing an online buyer requires.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best windows phone at this price....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the phone the next day as requested overnight shipping..the technique of packaging is very good...really good mobile...the interface of some applications are bit confusing but will find it easy later...got the phone for 7700...3G works very good...when battery fully charges it shows 21 hrs..there are lot of free apps&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best VFM Nokia windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Though there are not many free apps available for windows 8 phones, this mobile is still a good purchase if your main usage is to use it as phone. On a good day, taking 2-3 calls lasting 2-3 hrs with little web browsing using wifi and listening to music for about 2 hrs the battery will last for about 2 to 2.5 days. I havent tested the GPS feature yet. Overall good value for money purchase.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone at a good price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Delivered in a timely manner with all box packed accessories and bill. Add on was 500 mb data pack for airtel postpaid customers which I am and hence utilized it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is okay&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The touch is simply superb. The phone is worth its value. The only thing to complain about this its battery. It hardly lasts for half a day.&lt;br&gt;Net users will love this piece, I hope.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia rocks again!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Never understood what d hullaboo for android was, windows works great for me. And nokia has come out with a simply superb budget smartphone. I got it for 7400 from amazon 4 months back, and it is working wonderfully well. Just change d headphones though.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its a good value for money buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i wanted to buy an android but settled for a nokia.the phone is the better than its rivals in almost all the parameters.If you are not a big "app person" ,go for it.Cheap androids are never a wise choice.And it looks way better than phones of a much higher price range.The windows nowadays offers you all the important apps.If u have been an android user , you may miss a certain things.If however you are a first time smartphone buyer, you will be more than happy.Only problem is the camera which shoots excellent in daylight, however due to the absence of flash ,clicking pictures in low light is not a satisfactory experience. music and sounds,memory n speed are great.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=25</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Price !!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Worth it !!! Good Model Best in class model !!! .. I like the Black one model .. Pefect choice !!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Offering&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it under Rs.7000 with 10% Axis Bank Card offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phone is great in touch, display, camera and call quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only drawback i felt is fast battery discharging rate even in Airplane mode.  I think this bug will be solved in future updates.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;one of the best smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;superb phone in this price range.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;camera quality and touch are superb.&lt;br&gt;only a flash light for camera and ram to be improved are required.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NICE PRODUCT FROM NOKIA&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;NICE LOOKING, FANTASTIC DESIGN... NO FRONT CAMERA AND FLASH FOR REAR CAMERA IS A BIG DRAWBACK. SOMETIMES PHONE GETS SWITCHED OFF BY ITSELF. NO SOLUTIONS FROM NOKIA CARE YET. DIFFICULTIES ARE FACED WHILE CLEARING PHONE MEMORY. NO DIRECT OPTIONS TO SEND ITEMS FROM PHONE MEMORY TO SD CARD...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;i have a big prblm&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;in bill no record of a battery no , service centre man told me if u want a repalce ur battery than give me a bill with a battery no ......&lt;br&gt;if any one see than please give me a new bill with ma battery no&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Windows phone rocks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Have been using it since my purchase and have never had a problem with it hanging up.I needed a basic phone with a lot of battery power and this does help a lot when you are a frequent traveler.I am happy with the phone and the camera,i am not a kind of tech guy so wont be able to comment on tech part,but if you want a basic phone on which you want to listen to music,play games and talk endlessly this is it!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good phone at this price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a very good product.&lt;br&gt;Very good packing quality from amazon.&lt;br&gt;value for money product from nokia.&lt;br&gt;good performance.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good handset value for money I I I I I I I I i I I I I I i&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Wonderfull phone. Very much economicall and the best. High internet speed. A problem is that apps and videos cannot be shared.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Value for Money phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's got everything in a small package, good battery, good camera, email and chat. what else would one ask for? Paisa vasool gadget. well done nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=26</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Sup-b&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Low Prize And More Expensive Nokia Lumia (520) in&lt;br&gt;Nokia Lumia (520) Mobile Phone is A Nice And Sup-b Quality And  .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Never Purchase Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was a big mistake of me to purchase Nokia 520. It is not having any feature. Moreover, it not like other nokia set, which catch good signal, good battery life. I would not recommend other to purchase this product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nokia review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is jus awesome .. but i m getting one problem .. updsating problem .. it showing microsoft account un available&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Package for the money you spend&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good performance, battery life, display for the money you spend on it. If you spend the same money on a mid range android phone or a lesser known brand android phone then you wont get half this performance.&lt;br&gt;No hype and only performance about this phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Did not expect this from Amazon!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been cheated by amazon.. I purchased the mobile using Axis bank where there was 10% cash back.&lt;br&gt;And now I hear that you should not have used Netbanking.. This is cheap from amazon.. Lost trust...(sic)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good value for money!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought it when the price was around 7.5k, for my not so tech-savvy mother.&lt;br&gt;Received in perfect condition, 3 days after ordering. Solid packaging.&lt;br&gt;Must say, it is an excellent value for money, at this price point there is no android device that has similiar specs, or more importantly this kind of lag-free performance.&lt;br&gt;Apart from a few minor oddities in the OS , this mobile was perfect transition from Android.&lt;br&gt;Build quality is solid, screen resolution/quality is more than acceptable. Loudspeaker and earpiece quality and loudness was decent. Camera was good for the price.&lt;br&gt;Overall, I'll definitely recommend this cellphone, if your looking to skip android for lag issues.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The only flaw is the battery life. I bought it for my father who has to make calls very frequently. And he doesn't tire of complaining about the battery life. Though I did some research and found out that it's more of an OS issue, so hopefully this too should get sorted out.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;worth for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone for reasonable cost&lt;br&gt;1. speed is good.&lt;br&gt;2. camera quality is ok.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;drawbacks&lt;br&gt;512 mb ram,  temple run and subway surf games will not run on this device.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;phone not working fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone was a gift and was opened later than 10 days from the date of delivery.&lt;br&gt;the phone did not accept any micro sim from the time of the unboxing, it only showed like the sim is not present.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good for elderly as well&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered this for my dad who finds it difficult to read small texts.&lt;br&gt;He is very much comfortable with this device.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=29</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value for money!!&lt;br&gt;Awesome phone at an exceptional price,strikes a perfect balance between performance and normal usage. Excellent product for the youth.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;awesome experience with Lumia. it's so nice handset and the windows 8 was superb in hand keep it up 5 star from my side&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;One Thumb Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like this phone, we can easily operate whole phone from one thumb only.&lt;br&gt;In starting i don't felt windows 8 OS as user friendly as android, but after some time every thing got normal.&lt;br&gt;In terms of hardware, I felt nokia is the best but OS is not much friendly as android.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Battery getting discharged quickly. Crack on the screen.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am having problem and taken up the matter with Nokia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battery back up very low and discharges quickly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The screen cracked.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope Nokia attends to our complaint and replaces with original part and accessory.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Simply best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;cheapest windows 8 phone with all the exciting features you want. Its been more than two month I am using it and working fine.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There are many good points about it.&lt;br&gt;1. Money worthy&lt;br&gt;2. Touch and display is as good as Nokia reknowned for.&lt;br&gt;3. If your budget is within 10k and choice in between windows and android, then it's reasonably fair choice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons.&lt;br&gt;1. Ram (512MB)&lt;br&gt;2. Performance deteriorate but very rare.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;is it on warranty period ,nokia lumia 520?&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Sir,&lt;br&gt;I want to know that nokia lumia 520, which is  already i get by amazon.in online purchasing site, it is on warrenty period or not ?&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;m2n&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it's good appearance , batteries is ok, weight is ok , it's cheap, windows phone is not bad , i love it.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is best in this price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this phone 2 weeks back and it is just amazing in this price range.&lt;br&gt;Few of best features the phone has :&lt;br&gt;4 inch of IPS LCD touch&lt;br&gt;5 MP camera, believe me it is far better than 5 MP camera of other cellphones.&lt;br&gt;Great features of Windows 8 OS.&lt;br&gt;Great use of MS office products in cellphone and sync into your laptop.&lt;br&gt;512 RAM&lt;br&gt;8 GB of phone memory&lt;br&gt;1 GHz processor&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would just say, I was using Samsung Galaxy series Android phone and when I experienced Lumia 520, I have no words to compare, it's  just awesome. Go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Coolest Phone Below 10000&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia 520 is an ingeniously designed and crafted phone useful for both official, social and personal purposes. A very good phone surely in the segment of mobiles below 10000, And of course beats android phones with its amazing features.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A fully customer integrated with a full high net speed. Good Gaming experience and a very good internal memory of 8 GB..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=30</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It okay not bad less  price compare to other mobiles....but nokia lumia 625,620 they are good i guess compare to the lumia 520.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very satisfied with my purchase decision, this phone is really 'value for money'. In this range I can't find a better option than Lumia 520&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product... But not great.....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought this mobile a month ago in amazon...&lt;br&gt;No doubt it's a great phone in the price range with such hardware specs...&lt;br&gt;But it is now a big diasappointment with 1GB RAM restriction....&lt;br&gt;The microsoft is now concentrating phones with only more than 1gb ram...&lt;br&gt;Games like Temple Run 2, Asphalt, Minion rush can be played on only 1gb ram... though played it has some lag...&lt;br&gt;The new Nokia Beamer app is now available only for 1gb ram...&lt;br&gt;There are almost all apps in windows phone but compared to android, but it misses some useful apps like yupp tv(doesn't function well), AbhiBus useful at times....&lt;br&gt;Some of the apps haven't been created for windows phone....&lt;br&gt;  So, don't try to buy this mobile anymore... There are almost half sales of Lumia 520 in all windows phone sales globally... and you can get this mobile anywhere.....&lt;br&gt;Buy only if the price is not more than 7.5k range...&lt;br&gt;You can otherwise check for the alternatives like Lumia 525 or samsung galaxy s duos 2 (S7582) which is now available  for 10k....&lt;br&gt;You can buy any of this mobiles when these prices are slashed by 10% to 20% in 3 to 6 months if your budget is limited.......&lt;br&gt;Dont ever imagine to buy the 512mb ram lumia phones like 520, 620, 625 &amp;amp; 720......&lt;br&gt;Buy only Lumia 525,if you are windows phone lover, even if your budget is more to have value for your money, Otherwise go for L920 or L1020.........&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best budget smart phone in the market&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i was looking for a smart phone from a reputable manufacturer and loaded with decent specs.. this phone met all this and more so within my budget. best feature is the offline navigation..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great price , good delivery speed&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got Lumia 520 at â‚¹.7049 , Brand new, with vat paid bill. Actually black color is good. Now the Lumia 525 is released but price difference is above 3k , so L520 is super bargain.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best product at the right price point&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was struggling to choose between XOLO Q700 and LUMIA 520. Finally, when it was given for the lowest price, I couldn't resist but to go for LUMIA 520. I don't have any regrets and my experience on Windows Phone is very good till now.&lt;br&gt;Good design, built (both software &amp;amp; hardware). Kudos to Nokia team.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice and very smart :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Smart and affordable device. The amount you pay is worth.&lt;br&gt;Beautiful video quality as well. The display we get in this cost is really good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice fluid phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The os is awesome&lt;br&gt;..it is jst so fast...da snapdragon processor is da best...bettr dan mediatek processors...overall lumia experience is good...better dan an android stop and start experience..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;just awesome...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's an awesome  phone .... from the "king of brand" ... You just love it ....when you have it .....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good product. Amazon service was great. Product is working well. Atleast uptil yet. Nokia lumia is a wonderful phone. You should look forward to it.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=35</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;NOTHING GR8&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;BOUGHT AFTER READING REVIEWS BUT A BIT DISAPPOINTED..MANY SMALL SMALL COMMON FEATURES MISSING WHICH R THERE IN EARLIER MODELS ALSO....I WOULD SUGGEST TO GO FOR AN ANDROID MOBILE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best smart phone at 8K - No one in the market can give&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;"A brilliant phone for the price - this is the entry level device Windows Phone was made for."  Go for it :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice but&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;while purchasing this product i have an offer like, if i select this product then i will get the 20 paytm cash on my paytm account&lt;br&gt;but i didnt get this offer.&lt;br&gt;m really unhappy in this service.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NICE PHONE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;NICE PHONE AT THIS PRICE..... BRANDED PHONE NICE AND SMOOTH TOUCH, CLEARITY ALSO VERY GOOD ALL HD VIDEO PLAYED FROM YOUTUBE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Overall Budget Friendly. Best in Quality, Performance, Life long phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:Carl Zeiss lens, shoot 720p video with 30fps, Free Nokia Music and Mix Radio, Xbox Live Hub, Kid's Corner, Microsoft Office suits, Live tile icons, Browsing/Surfing very fast &amp;amp; smooth. Super-Sensitive touch, Micro-SIM card slot.&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;Missing features like Front Camera, LED Flash, Compass, NFC chip, HDMI port, File Explorer, Graphic Equalizer, Antivirus not available in App Store. Battery Backup, Limited Apps.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best hardware by nokia. Good battery backup when compared to android phones. All features are working properly. Best budget smart phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;can't  get better product than this in 8k.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its completely awesome phn....it has everything good except front camera . So who ever is lookng for windows phn @ low budget go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;pacca, not expensive, best body design, ips touch is good, windows 8 in mobile is awesome, no hanging, best clarity, more than worth the price, very useful for official and college uses. gr8 to use.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;big screen ,&lt;br&gt;fast processor ,&lt;br&gt;easy to use ,&lt;br&gt;with super fast internet .&lt;br&gt;i love this phone .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;One of the best phones i have used&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Simply superb...Meets all my needs and expectations. The only thing is no flash in camera. that is the only thing that is miss...apart from that it is awesome...&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=33</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Slavery to the OS&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using this phone for a fortnight now. I have found that the interface great considering that i have just moved into the smartphone world from the Symbian environment. I am not a tech expert. But let me list out some issues that i have had with the phone.&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1. No file manager - if you want to access your memory card, you have to connect it to your computer.&lt;br&gt;2. You cant send files via bluetooth to friends and you'll have no clue where the received files are until you connect to a computer.&lt;br&gt;3. The phone will discard files if they are not in compatible formats.&lt;br&gt;4. There is no easy way to access certain settings like wifi and data options.&lt;br&gt;5. The phone does behave weirdly now and then (reboots and or exits from apps suddenly).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. it is light weight.&lt;br&gt;2. The interface is smooth&lt;br&gt;3. Voice clarity is great.&lt;br&gt;4. The camera is neat&lt;br&gt;5. The touch is awesome.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bottom line: If you don't mind being a slave to the OS and letting it decide what you do with the phone and how you do it, then go for this. It is cheap and feature rich.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth for what it is&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I've found this phone to be reasonably worth for what we pay. I previously owned an Android phone and that was a last moment deicison over a Windows phone. And the idea of owning a WP has now fulfilled. I liked this phone for what it is. Everything about this phone is good except for couple of things for now - (1) camera picture clarity could have been better though not disappointing, and (2) should have a way to group videos in kid's corner (does not look good to have hundreds of video tiles on the home screen for kid's corner as scrolling them would be time-consuming). I'm still in the process of exploring the phone - no regrets so far, and (3) playing FM without headset could have been implemented (for now, I'm using a headset with little piece of wire and without the actual earphones so that it acts as an antenna and turning the speaker on).&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent product... value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best cellphone you can get at this price... if you are not fond of android .. go for it. Its fast , light and perfect in your hand , when you want to use it with one hand. Best features here maps and nokia music.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;No notification bar/ quick settings changing options&lt;br&gt;No personalised themes&lt;br&gt;Lack of apps and games on windows store compared to android or ios&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i was able to meet my expectations. good service from amazon and i am happy with it. nokia lumia 520 is good to use&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money - through and through&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was looking to purchase a simple smartphone on a tight budget. Amongst most options in this range, the Lumia 520 is by far the leader of the pack. Priced at around 7.9k, the laptop is well balanced with features and performance . Would definitely recommend this to students, and professionals who have a sub 10k budget.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Tip: the black model comes with a fabric like finish to the back plate which I think isn't available on the other models where the back plate is matte. Making them quite slippery.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Small Budget Good smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;In smart phone price range, Nokia Lumia 520 is good phone except it has battery issue as well as memory card compatibility issue.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good mobile with good features in this price range.. Flash is the only one missing part else rest all good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone but has some drawback&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone screen is not tough like any other Nokia phone. So be careful when you drop it. My glass is broken. The Here maps and drives are really good. GPS + GLONASS combination is too good. The Windows apps store has good number of apps but not like Googles Play store.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very nice phone at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a very nice phone at this price. I got it at 7000rs and also I got cash back of 700 in the month of Dec'2013.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fragile glass case&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The glass broke on the first day itself while trying to assemble the phone .... A big disappointment ! Not intuitive if you haven't used A Windows phone earlier.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=31</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Absolutely worth every penny .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If someone is looking for a new phone then this is it to go for.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a value fr money phone. With good color screen, sound is also nice. Battery last my a full day with calling and music listening.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you dont want Android and Wanna Try something new .. Look no further than WP8 . Using it along my Galaxy S4 .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is the best phone under 10 k and even u can compare it with phones of 15000 range.. it also feels good in your hand.. lots of app are there and most amazing thing in windows8 that it does'nt hang. touch is very very good..i'll rate it 10 out of 5  :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a wonderful phone and I am happy to buy it, Anyone can purchase the only drawback is no flash&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good in this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;window is totally different from android and other.its very good. one bad thing is all the apps in payable in windows store.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Loved it....... Nokia phones are much better than any other... ... .. ... ... ... Buy it without a singe thought&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Ausome product which i have found in lowest rate.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ausome product which i have found in lowest rate. Hey.. Thanks to Amazon which gives me awesome product on time which they are commited&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good in Bugdet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is very good and fast, but sound quality in headphone not so good, also sometime app crash in phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good one product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;hello amazon team,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i beleave it's my best one purchase from your site, cheap and best, keep your services up,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thanks&lt;br&gt;vinay&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=34</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money in 7000/-&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;music lover care full before buy its don't have equalizer! or ordinary music quality. overall its good phone for around 7000/-&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;got defective piece. checked recently.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;got defective piece. checked recently.  roaming here and there to nokia care.Dont know what to do now. simply trying to change my phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool Thing to have and amazon as usual great delivey&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am having the problem with the camera Key and also the regarding the Date day n timing.The calender is having some problem.Otherwise As its Nokia Its Good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;phone with all options for 7k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone and lowest price when compared to all other online stores . . .. . . . . .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone for the Price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i have purchased this phone from saholic store wid free insurance. phone is just un-belivable in performance. here are my findings so far,&lt;br&gt;1. camera is mind blowing 5mp digital camera with hd captureing, video recording is 720 hd.&lt;br&gt;2. second to none for internet speed at this price range, store has uc browser, internet exlorer is just teribly faster.&lt;br&gt;3. perform 10 tasks at a single time.&lt;br&gt;4. store had HD games (better than android)&lt;br&gt;5. nokia mix radio is innovative app which helps u to dwnld songs, and play dem. better music player than inbiuilt one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nothing to talk about the mobile as it is fantastic low priced smart phone.&lt;br&gt;Amazon is simply superb as the price is matched by no other e-tailer.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iy is a fab product and best thing is that it not  crased until now,onely one thing is bad some games ar not working&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a fab product and best thing is that it not  crased until now,onely one thing is bad some games ar not working&lt;br&gt;and thanks  to amazon for its  delivery ðŸ˜‡ðŸ˜‡ðŸ˜‡ðŸ˜‡ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸðŸðŸ&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Does good Justice for the Price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good product for its price... Nokia being a trusted brand over year I sont need to say anythibg much about its reliability and durability. ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazon gave lowest price in the market!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;We thanks to amazon providing this item with an unbelievable pricing!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lowest in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thanks Amazon for wonderful experience.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Everything I wanted.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am not a tech wizard. i wanted a smart phone. Android or windows. I would not want. I had bad experience with Samsung in the past and found Nokia to be reliable , so I went for  this one. I find it very handy and all my requirements are fulfilled. I want routine apps, e-readers from Kindle, e-readers from flip cart and all those small things and they are all possible with this one. Easy inter-phase. What it doesn't have? usual things like archiving message and all those little irritants that Nokia is now becoming famous for. This is present in other Nokia phones. If you want to forward a message, you don't have a log to pick up number from there. Why these idiots at Nokia give up what they already have?&lt;br&gt;All in all good value for money. And I saved net 1,000 rupees by bying online. Very prompt in executing the order&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=32</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good and price worth product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good and price worth product. Windows looks great but it doesn't have all features which are available in Andriod.&lt;br&gt;Amazon service is good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;One of the best phones available at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best thing about this phone is that there is no lag in its performance when multitasking. it has a nice and clear display with great touch response. I would suggest to go for this phone instead of android phones available in this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;AWESOME BUDGET SMART PHONE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia has finally learned to release "budget smart phones" to Indian market after a very long time.&lt;br&gt;Compared to other cell phone manufacturers,Nokia adhere to QC superbly even in entry level phones &amp;amp; budget smart phones.&lt;br&gt;Initially bit difficult to get started with windows phone but once you have a hold on it you will never feel like going back to Android etc.&lt;br&gt;Speaker is in the bottom left corner which gets covered as we hold the phone but not an issue we can still hear the sound.&lt;br&gt;Never hangs that's something superb about windows phones.&lt;br&gt;Got it from Amazon within two days.&lt;br&gt;Go ahead and grab one.&lt;br&gt;WAY TO GO NOKIA...............&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i have used this for past month and find this one of the best low budget smart phone for starters who uses windows for first time&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Works like charm!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Except that camera which is without flash the handset works excellent, no hang nothing!&lt;br&gt;I just love it. awesome product!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best phone in this range.all is gud in this phone except the RAM....so sometimes phone will hang if u start so many applications and watching videos on youtubes is just awesome without any buffering.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its little bit slow..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a nice phone ... but it is a little bit slow to perform...!! 1GB ram is required.. and Windows Application have some limitations..!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;MInd Blowing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awsome best services  and thank full to amazon who has provide me in cheap rate again thanks to amazon .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Satisfied with service.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This was my first buy from amazon. I was perticularly reluctant to buy a mobile costing thousands of rupees fearing a exchange headache etc. but!!! It was all the way smooth! Till today i disnt find a reason to visit even Nokia! I am fully satisfied with Amazon's delivery system timings plus maintenance of high and verified product quality.eapecially bought this phone for 7.5k so great price. Flawless performance n gud battery n display..m satisfied with what i spent.&lt;br&gt;I am assured with you guys now.will but many more..may be an Apple product in near future..&lt;br&gt;Thanks amazon for being in India!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;waaao its amazing experience ...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super sensetive touch screen. with classic future . camera result is little down but its good . over all good one.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=36</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone :-)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone for this price.Excellent display and touch.&lt;br&gt;Only problem is that there is no file manager as it is a windows phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia when compared with Samsung S duos is Substandard&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all let me tell u that the "Transfer my Data" is not working. Tried to contact Nokia, the man there gave a vague reply. Still it is not working. Camera is not giving clear pictures. To take a snap it is taking too much time. To function as a phone it is good. All other things average only. To save a number is time consuming. Too many operations to save a number&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome mobile..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I just love eveything in this phone..Its style,look,features,compatibility everything is perfect..luv it..;)infact delivry n packaging was too good..ovearlly jhakaass..thnx amazon.;)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Quality Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This product fulfill my requirement. Fast downloading and touching sensitivity is really good and much more also great game exp...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awsome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is beyond my expectation. In this price range, I think this is the best smartphone. I bought it almost a month ago. Till now did not face any problem with it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I am so happy with amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon.com is really helpful and there product is 100% genuine.granted&lt;br&gt;so i am very happy with amazon Thank you. Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I recommend this product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product received was excellent.  I recommend this product.  Also, I got the product within two days from the date of order.  My regards to Amazon team.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Utility is the core&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone absolutely offers lot more utilities than what i payed for that. I bought it for only 7K in GOSF. Now i am feeling like buying another to gift my brother.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great windows phone in price range.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great looks, Great features and decent battery life is the main features of this phone. Only missing is some useful application likes app. locker , memory booster. some games.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Meets Expectations&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;As we know, Amazon is World leader in Ecommerce and found it in real. Packaging was good along with service.. Thumps Up for Amazon..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=37</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best starter smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Doesnt have all the bells and whistles but get the job done. and at a fraction of the price. silky smooth user interface.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Forget the specs. just use it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone Lumia 520.....its fast,reliable,and much more capable of competes with android market. As having great battery back up its first phone of Nokia i so liked......but some problems to lumia 520 that Microsoft not convinced to transfer video through Bluetooth. Is os it self can not make detect to memory card storages. Overall its good to having phone like apple. Nice,greater than any android in its price...!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good for those not looking to run graphic intensive games&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a pretty good deal for those who are not too much into gaming and lokoing for good camera with HD recording at low price. I was initially impressed with the performance but then when started testing it with some games the lag showed up. I like it and would be really good for any demographic not interesting on performance draining games. Camera+songs+small games and day long battery, this phone's the way to go (Y)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it is awesome..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is wonderful as there is o hanging problem(specially) at this range. thanks it is good experience for me .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a good phone , response time is good and moreover you get a phone which is worth the money you pay&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Need to work more...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia and Microsoft has tried a great...&lt;br&gt;but still need some more work to be done on lumia series...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However, overall a good phone...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;GO FOR IT.....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;BEST OF THE BEST....all good and best product delivered....no words to express my happiness it's the best phone i have ever used...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Product at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phones in windows model at this price,it could be better if it had flash other than that everything is ok&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice phone..best phone as compare to other smart phone..using since last one month ...all the facility are available which is there in smartphone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone in minimum Budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice to use this phone. battery backup is good.&lt;br&gt;Some more free  apps are required like android.&lt;br&gt;Anyway, user friendly phone with win 8 OS.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=38</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing !!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its simply super, really worth the money you pay, amazing!!! It's very sleek, handy and it's got a great battery back up even if the 3G is on.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is worth the price. Nokia has done a great job.&lt;br&gt;Nokia Lumia has offered me great features.&lt;br&gt;deserves 5/5 :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sameer sapre&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone in this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;file manager is not that effective yeah but yes smooth functioning phone! hang (due to less frames per sec) some time while playing temple run!&lt;br&gt;Overall: average but as compared to phones in this range lumia 520 has done a terrific job!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Wonderful phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really very good to use. i loved it. only thing is not getting enough windows app compare to android phones. Dont think we go for this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing smart phone, best value for money within the 7-8k range of phones. Am a Windows phone user since last 2+ yrs and i still love it. Serves all my utility requirements - browsing, office mails,  personal mails,doc,manage/edit xls,ppt, pdf files, facebook, whatsapp, smart edu apps for my kid, et al. Value adds also include free nokia music (best feature of the phone) and the free skydrive backup.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You can even change  the outer shell easily to match your day. You could get the shells at Rs 300-350 from amazon in a range of bright colors..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go for it!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nokia is good in battery&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good piece with a long battery life at cheaper price. I wish to buy another piece from amazon..different brand&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Performance of lumia 520 is very good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Performance is very good,design is ok, processor speed is also very good. I am happy with this product. suggest to buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great for the price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone for the price.  Good even for GPS alone.  If you like your gadgets, it is no Galaxy S4 but it is a great second phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Camera quality is good.&lt;br&gt;touch quality also good.&lt;br&gt;mobile size is convenient to handle.&lt;br&gt;when playing games and when browsing it generates more heat.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Osm!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I just Loved It and Thanks Amazon! for making me get this at affordable price and less than anywhere else&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=39</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;not this model, overall windows mobile is not best for me.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Disadvantage in windows mobile:&lt;br&gt;1. Custom field in contact is not possible (even if u use Google account).&lt;br&gt;2. You cann't attach files in a mail (only image can be attached).&lt;br&gt;3. If u forward a mail which has attachment, the attachment won't go.&lt;br&gt;4. No custom ringtone for messages.&lt;br&gt;5. Home screen is not effective.&lt;br&gt;6. less apps (compared to Android)&lt;br&gt;7. If u want create an App, u need min Win7 PC.&lt;br&gt;8. This model doesn't have flash for camera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advantages&lt;br&gt;1. Good battery life.&lt;br&gt;2. Nice camera quality.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nokia lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No file manager, difficult 2 use Bluetooth sharing bt excluding these things lumia 520 is value for money n affordable. Feel good experience while using n entirely nice phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Smoothness and quality, at low price..!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One always has a doubt while going in to buying a phone for under 10k, whether or not it be good. But you dont need that with this one. This one's a killer. From the dual core processor providing the buttersmooth performance of the UI, to the UI itself, to the other aspects of hardware like the camera or the display quality, you feel it dont let you down, and to get all that in under 10k. I dunno if anyone can ask for more, given the price. Coming to the camera, it is great, though it lacks the flash. Personally, I'm not a big fan of using flash in photos, as I like them in natural lighting. The native camera app is just ok, but the nokia smart cam app is really good. The 4" display is one you'll fall in love with, but I hear the display is a bit washed up when compared with those of 620 or 720. But who is comparing that much. You cant have everything on a phone under 10k. Plus, the windows phone UI, it also gets some time to get used to if you are coming from android or something. But you will get over the latency in a couple of hours.&lt;br&gt;So I say, if you are looking for a phone in under 10k, dont think twice, just go for it..!! :-)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good one for window phone lovers&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;some time hanging problem otherwise good one at least on that prise.&lt;br&gt;file maneger missing (not proper secquence).....&lt;br&gt;go for it or not its your choise&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent value for money smartphone.......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Android, iOS, Windows Phone, BB10.......&lt;br&gt;millions of apps, megapixel cameras, GBs of memory, HD, Full HD screens....&lt;br&gt;tired of all these tech jargons???&lt;br&gt;No need to pay attention on these when you have a limited budget as you can't expect much from lower price points but exactly this is the point where this mobile satisfies all your smartphone needs while not stealing your money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Achievements:&lt;br&gt;#1 Best selling windows phone device worldwide.&lt;br&gt;Holds more than 30% of windows phone market alone.&lt;br&gt;The phone which helped Nokia to gain it's lost ground.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1.Price: Now you can't expect more at 7000-8000 INR.&lt;br&gt;2.Fluid OS: you won't believe how smooth it performs with fully loaded 32 GB memory card&lt;br&gt;3. Nice build quality, won't let you down among smartphone crowd.&lt;br&gt;4. Exchangeable covers.&lt;br&gt;5. and of course it's a Nokia phone&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:(You can count them but they are not cons since price is bottom low for a decent performer smartphone)&lt;br&gt;1. No flash&lt;br&gt;2. No windows key lights (means less fancy phone)&lt;br&gt;3. No front facing camera.&lt;br&gt;4. Display lacking Nokia's CBD tech.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a phone for first time smartphone owners, backup phone for iPhone, Galaxy, Xperia Owners.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;price worthy phone to buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i love its design, sleekness and style.&lt;br&gt;Hardware specifications are good at this price, no other big brand is offering 5MP camera with HD recording.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb by nokia and amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Superb mobile I love it what a os by microsoft and what a product by nokia with grt price by amazon u should defenetly take this one&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone With Long Battery Life&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Camera is more then good enough. nice battery life.&lt;br&gt;But As Compare to android windows apps is not so good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SUPERB SMARTPHONE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like the every feature of this mobile,but some odds sharing the videos outside the photos folder is not getting possible and games like templerun2 and subway-surfers are not yet released so...they need to rectify those issues apart from that eveyrthing is awesome like video recording,touch-ability,camera,.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good mobile at good price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very happy with my purchase. Mobile is good and screen resolution , camera everything is good.  Only cons is it works with micro sim.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=40</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item></items>