<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;cute little lumia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I wanted to try the windows phone 8 device and this was the best I can get as its the cheapest Win8 phone out there. After using it for a few days, I would say if u wana try soimething new this can take care of all the basic features of a smartphone(except for a few misses). Battery performance is ok(lasts a full day on normal to heavy use). Graphics are ok(dnt expect much from a 9k device) althoug it runs temple-run without much glitches(yes their are a few but can be ignored). The monotonous nature of UI is something that you'll definitely get bored off after a few days of use. Overall a good device at this price point and should be considered by those looking for something new(specially people switching from basic phones to their first smartphone).&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very use full item perfect genuine product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very use full item&lt;br&gt;perfect genuine productvery use full item&lt;br&gt;perfect genuine productvery use full item&lt;br&gt;perfect genuine productvery use full item&lt;br&gt;perfect genuine product&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;a good windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery lasts for three days if the phone is not used for gaming. build quality is good.  resolution of the screen is satisfactory.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth the price!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;Affordable.&lt;br&gt;Decent bundled apps.&lt;br&gt;Expandable storage.&lt;br&gt;Swappable battery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;Poor call quality&lt;br&gt;No Flash&lt;br&gt;Weird sensor problems.&lt;br&gt;Poor speaker&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fit for price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I wanted to explore a smart phone and touch screen mobile for the first time, as I was using Nokia N79 for the past few years. Being a software developer with micorsoft .NET platform, I wanted to see how Windows 8 OS was in a smartphone. So I chose Nokia lumia 520 as its low end but has most of the features I wanted.&lt;br&gt;Overall I am happy with the mobile. Performance of the mobile is very good (games, multi taking, net browsing speed).&lt;br&gt;The biggest disadvantages are Battery life (comes to around 5 hours for heavy usage and 8-9 hrs for normal workday usage), poor camera indoors (outdoors its decent enough), lack of options for apps.&lt;br&gt;Since I am used to charging mobile once every 2 days with nokia N79, charging mobile twice a day seemed tedious. But every other smart phone using friend said all phones perform no more than same.&lt;br&gt;Its very long time issue that options in apps are very less in windows market. It has improved in the past 1 yr. Temple run, rail rush, dhoom 3 are available and perform very well. Also in social network side, whatsapp, wechat, facebook messenger are available.&lt;br&gt;Camera can used in situations where you don't have any other camera. Else it would be better to take photos in better phones and get it through Bluetooth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall I would give 3/5 for the phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the product is up to my expectation an it is having all the features and working properly&lt;br&gt;thank you for providing the product for a such reduced price&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;windows phone works best, opens all office files seamlessly and never hangs unlike android which hangs twice a day atleast&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best in this range ..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super phone .. awseome features that u look in a smartphone.. excellent touch and good camera (however flash is missing but then who wants to become a professional photographer :D)..  only 1 shortcoming i find is still developing app store for windows mobiles ...last but not the least ..super delivery by amazon .. i ordered it by COD on 4th dec and got it on 7th ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Superb working....I love it....Budget mobile...Excellent featured smartphone....I recommend all to buy and fulfil ur dreeams of smartphone for less price...&lt;br&gt;Thanks a lot amazon.in...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone not working properly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone has got some issues,i dont know if those issue could be rectified by nokia care itself.It gets hanged very often.Camera does not work properly.I doubt if the product give to me is a genuine one.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=46</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Don't Buy Mobile/Electronic in Online&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hi All,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product is delivered on time but there are so many issues with the Mobile, got it from Amazon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some of the issues I found till now:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1) This item is fulfilled by Amazon and seller should be SAHOLIC but my mobile is delivered from some other seller Spice India Pvt. Ltd. I don't understand why the seller is changed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2) Phone is getting switched off very frequently even though I don't use any big aplications or games and this making me to think twice before buying anything in online. Anyway I got the experience with this mobile and I am not going to buy anything online in my life time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3) Head phones are changed. These headphone looks like the real one from Nokia but it is not. Head phones sound clarity is worst compared with the mobile head phones got it from stores.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4) Mobile should be certified by SAR and it should be attached backside(panel) of the mobile. But these mobiles are not SAR certified that means they are not selling the products which are certified. That's why they are giving for lower cost than stores.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There are so many reasons for not getting certification, for example.&lt;br&gt;a) Product is failed in End to End Testing.&lt;br&gt;b) Product didn't fulfil the requirements.&lt;br&gt;etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am thinking to return this mobile and I hope Amazon will return my money back.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Awesome look&lt;br&gt;2. Great Speed&lt;br&gt;3. Good grip to hold&lt;br&gt;4. Camera is good&lt;br&gt;5. Great Sound Quality and Video Quality&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1. No Flash - but not required for often&lt;br&gt;2. No Front cam&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its working good  but  there  is  some  OS issue ,,duplicate Music/Video/Photo are  showing  on  SD Card , its  not  a  big  prblm ,, when  os  update  will  come it  will  be  slove.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera 5mp , video recording better than Captured Picture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;camera Features r too  good Auto Focus , Cinemagraph,Smart Camera ,CamScaner ,CamCard , bulid built-in QR Reader , Text Scan  ,App work great.&lt;br&gt; And Instagram Also avlbl For Windows Phone 8.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money redefined ...!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great value for money.. and far better than android phones in the same price range.&lt;br&gt;Highly recommended for those who are first time or budget-Conscious Smartphone buyers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value for money, the product is in perfect working condition and comes with original bill and nice sealed pack fully&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Windows on a budget!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is great for the price! It has only a 1Ghz processor but it handles Windows 8 very smoothly. It requires a micro Sim card.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4 inch screen size i feel is the perfect size for a screen. I tried a 4.5 inch screen phone but it was too cumbersome to type or to use in general.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has all the connectivity options one would need in India.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The feel and build quality of the phone are very impressive. It feels fantastic to use it, built like a tank.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The camera is decent, no flash though.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battery lasts me more than a day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen is not so great but its okay for the price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;lack of dual sim option is the major flaw in this phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro's&lt;br&gt;Cheap&lt;br&gt;great features&lt;br&gt;lovely quality&lt;br&gt;good battery life&lt;br&gt;great looks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Con's&lt;br&gt;Single sim&lt;br&gt;No flash&lt;br&gt;Decent screen&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Once again great service by amazon. A great phone and value for money below 10k range&lt;br&gt;solid build with a beautiful interface. Love the mobile.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There was a problem with the product,and the problem with the connectivity as the network drops abruptly in between.I am about to go to nokia store and check with the problem.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Random restart problem&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My Nokia Lumia 520 randomly restarts itself while I am trying to unlock the phone. Is there any way to fix the issue ?&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i m thankful to Amazon who supply my phone at very low price among all the online store&lt;br&gt;thank  you&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=44</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;its best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its best phone according to its price and in my budget every thing is fabulous just I request to plz also provide a memory card plz and a littel bit prob is battery backup other wise its best and your deliveryboy mr. Deepak is also a good person he explanin me every thing about product and deliver product on tatha me&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Perfect&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The Best anyone can get .... go for it now ... Amazon.in is the only online shopping website u can trust with .... nothing else just amazon ... Love u guys ... thank you again ....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone is very good...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a very good Phone, And i am very happy after purchased this phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And I like my exp with Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;PLUS:&lt;br&gt;1. Price - you cant get another smartphone with the 520's specs, and the reliability of MS/Nokia, at this price (BTW when I bought it, Amazon had the lowest price among all India e-sellers)&lt;br&gt;2. Easy to use - doesn't take much long to figure out the interface, and navigate your way around. I migrated from BB with apprehension - but its been smooth riding so far.&lt;br&gt;3. Very responsive touch-screen. For a first-time touch user like me, it has been easy to 'learn' how to type without physical/tactile keys.&lt;br&gt;4. Text prediction is pretty good. Word suggestion, as you type along a message/email is quite intuitive (impressive!)&lt;br&gt;5. Call quality - good&lt;br&gt;6. Readability (indoors and outdoors) - good&lt;br&gt;7. Like all Nokia phones, this one is tough, and solidly built.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MINUS:&lt;br&gt;1. Battery - let no one fool you - no touch-screen smartphone will give you juice to last beyond the day. I would rate myself a moderate user, but I need to re-plug in by 6 pm. So if you are a heavy user, look for a power pack as an additional buy, or look elsewhere (NOKIA: why didn't you give a bigger batter?)&lt;br&gt;2. Doesn't come with a microSD card. You will have to pay extra for that, so fact that in while making a buy decision.&lt;br&gt;3. Practically useless Search/Bing 'button' - we wouldn't have missed it MS. Please stop trying to push your service through a 'dedicated button'.&lt;br&gt;4. No lit-up 'notifications' for new messages/mails/missed calls. So you have no way of knowing if there are some mails/messages waiting for your attention, unless you unlock the screen and periodically check.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;COMMENTS:&lt;br&gt;1. As far as I can see, there is no 'phone-book' in the 520. All your contacts reside in Google/Hotmail etc, not locally. So what happens if any of those services crash one day? Where's the back-up? If anyone has an answer to that, please post here, and enlighten us.&lt;br&gt;2. Nokia could have put a 'pulsating' lit-up notification option for missed calls, new messages/mails/posts. Maybe the Windows logo at the bottom of the phone could have been an LED that could pulse to draw your attention. Sadly that feature is not there in the 520.&lt;br&gt;3. All the 3 'buttons' at the bottom of the phone (BACK, WINDOWS/OPTION, SEARCH/BING) are not back-lit. So if you are using your 520 in the dark, you have to 'feel your way around' (!). It would have been a nice touch to back-light the touch buttons (pun intended!).&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Some Issues with Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Initially when i bought it from Amazon it was awesome..&lt;br&gt;But now i got a problem with camera button, and sometimes when i get a call, this phone gets hanged.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;i like it..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it looks great. touch sensitivity is very good. battery too works well. comparatively less user friendly against android device..overall a good package for my budget and use..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best device under 10k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you want to buy a device under 10k, Android is a direct no-no. In fact 18k+ android phones are worth going for. Lumia 520 is the only (under 10k)smartphone which will work perfectly well. HIGHLY RECOMENDED&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;low price and unexpected features..... too good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its really good .......very low price and higher version what all we need ................................I hope amazon return my cash back offer price money&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;no one can beat this, no hangs, superb camera quality better than samsung 8mp, superb graphics, touch, go for it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;loved service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i bought this for Rs6999.......&lt;br&gt;at that time market price of 520 was Rs8600.....&lt;br&gt;so it was a grt prfit 4 me.....&lt;br&gt;so i lykd it vry much......&lt;br&gt;we get fresh products frm amazon....... so i love 2 buy products frm amazon.in............ &amp;lt;3&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=45</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Budget Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Till now bought best budget phone and Windows OS is rocking :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just need to improve Windows App store like Android :P&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great widows phone.Good screen resolution and touchscreen.Good in all departments&lt;br&gt;No front cam and Flash is a minus point.Over all value for Money Phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;+Great value for money&lt;br&gt;+Dual core 1GHz processor&lt;br&gt;+Great quality of screen (of size 4")&lt;br&gt;+Decent camera in this range&lt;br&gt;+Decent battery&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;-Camera button on the unit I got sucks huge time. It became too hard to press after two weeks of delivery.&lt;br&gt;-WP platform not for those looking for Android goodnes&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money redifined&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good features at affordable cost.Buy it without any hesitation.Would recommend it for any person who is planning to buy a decent smartphone within price range below 10000.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Value Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Value Phone for 7.5 k. All good features in this phone are available which is needed bit hard on windows initially but later it is good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Now amazon is selling this for 8300 on 5th Dec while my friends have purchased it for 6800.&lt;br&gt;After the launch of Lumia 525 the price of 520 will further go down and 525 has better RAM where you can play games with ease.&lt;br&gt;Don't go for this phone at 8000&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;undoubtedly awesome mobile with low price in Amazon.in&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;purchased for my brother, still it is awesome with no delay.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nokia and Amazon rocks!!!&lt;br&gt;-Packing was also good, I always purchase good product from Amazon.in.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it's Good Deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am using it and happy about the deal which I made with you.&lt;br&gt;It's worth for my money.&lt;br&gt;thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;beautiful worthy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;beautiful product ..i ill love to buy another one..full hd videoplay back..a fone at 7500 range..no android will do that&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all I would like to thanks Amazon for giving such an amazing offer during Diwali. This phone is worth the penny for those who wish to buy windows mobile from a brand like Nokia.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=48</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;video chat on skype possible even without a front camera. this was not possible on Android phones without a front camera. Unlimited music downloads for 3 months is an awesome feature. 'Here Drive' app for gps navigation is by far the most accurate navigation tool I have used, found it easier (and more accurate) to use than Google navigation.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Broken item and FM is not working&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I received the item with broken volume key and FM was also not working. Please check it before you purchase.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;gone with the brand Nokia., But should have thought it runs Windows OS&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Undoubtedly useless interface especially when it comes to the basic functionality of calling, sending SMS, managing contacts and groups etc. .. Though i was using android phone, i went in to this phone because of Nokia branding. But the Windows OS is really pathetic. I think Windows is trying to make business with its half cooked stuff baked in!!! My money is wasted in this gadget. I have changed many mobiles but never seen such a pathetic user experience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. setup wizard is not obedient. - during the wizard setup, i made a custom setting not to use mobile data connection. I don't see any wifi settings wizard also. But int he end of setup, i get a message that some apps are getting updated. i have no clue from where.&lt;br&gt;2. Cannot have a local contacts. It will always sync with Microsoft account. No way to delete multiple entries. Even if i delete the entries in Hotmail from my desktop, it is not reflecting on the phone people. I have no clue from where all it syncs up when i have only one account configured and that too is Microsoft.&lt;br&gt;3. If i have a contact with multiple phone entries, and you got a missed call, you have no clue if the call is from his mobile or home or work. No number is displayed. Clicking on the call log, it takes me to the contact page. from there, i can't text to a particular mobile. Lumia decides to which number it will text the sms.&lt;br&gt;4. No much apps.!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I made a big mistake by buying this phone and i advise don't buy this phone and end up with very limited functionality. Useless interface especially when it is urgent.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone for this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone for this price.&lt;br&gt;ram 512 mb drawback. For games it is slow. It require at least 1 gb&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NOKIA REVIEW&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is wonderful phone , value for  money , i think person is fulish who use android base phone , A lot of mis understanding is create for witndows based phone in market . i suggest every body , please dont go in market report . this phone is very good . it batary backup its technolody Its camera , sound system every this is upto the mark.  further i must appretiated amazon system &amp;amp; couriour service . my phone is seal pack &amp;amp; enclosing vat bill perfectely . no issue . nokia &amp;amp; amezon both are best. just go ahead .fot his phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone in best price..:-)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is user friendly, but needs to fix some bugs on OS.&lt;br&gt;The OS crashes sometimes hope this will get fixed in next update, overall its very nice phone.&lt;br&gt;On-time delivery by Amazon as promised :-)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Low cost , fully loaded mobile..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;excellent display , battery backup is nice..&lt;br&gt;phone get hang frequently..&lt;br&gt;buttons need to be improved.&lt;br&gt;expecting more updated and stable os from microsoft.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone. Delivery superfast. Kudos to Amazon!! I would suggest whoever is thinking of purchasing a superb smartphone in less than 10K, this is the phone you are looking for. Very user friendly and easy to navigate.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;THIS IS THE THING&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Say what you will Windows phones are better than Android. Yes. Spiritually, ecumenically, grammatically and technically better than Android. If you are bored of lagging,if you are bored of the same user interface, if you you are bored of seeing the same phone everywhere, if you want a better user friendly experience, if you would like a good camera in a budget smartphone, if you would want to make a sane decision on spending your money (and  later be proud of that decision) GO FOR THIS PHONE. I won't go into technical details and count all the pros and cons as you will find that in almost all the reviews. I am writing as a normal consumer to another consumer with full responsibility and devotion. Don't want to believe me? Don't. Sulk on your "Lagaroid".&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone with this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;lumia 520 is great phone. BATTERY backup is very good. internet speed is very good. Internet speed is also very fast. phone never hangs.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=43</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Liked it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Wanted to go for new OS and had good experience in this mobile. Camera, Display, Speed are excellent. Some shortcut options are not available. menu style is not attracting.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;possibly the best smatphone at this price :-)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hey everyone,&lt;br&gt;I recently bought lumia 520 from AMAZON and to be frank this phone is more than worth the money u pay ...,&lt;br&gt;The features i liked about this phone are:&lt;br&gt;*super sensitive screen(Better than higher end phones of other companies)&lt;br&gt;*camera which clicks better shots in well lit conditions&lt;br&gt;*the more stable windows 8 OS&lt;br&gt;*good battery life&lt;br&gt;*it is slimmer than it looks&lt;br&gt;*awesome video clarity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONS:&lt;br&gt;*less apps compared to IOS and ANDROID(though almost all popular apps are free ;))&lt;br&gt;*earphones cud be betta(though it sounds too good with other earphones)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;so what are you waiting for , blindly go for this one guyz :)&lt;br&gt;its simply awesome&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Love Lumia 520 (black)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The offer price was tempting (7550). It was a decision i cherish. I bought it. Lumia 520 is a good performing phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;smooth as butter&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;just loving the interface..........and the smoothness of this wonderfull windows phone......no regret after buying this......i love my lumia 520......5 star&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A mixed bag&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great price&lt;br&gt;Great display&lt;br&gt;Good Camera&lt;br&gt;Good Sound quality&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Terrible battery will last almost 7 - 8 hours without any data usage&lt;br&gt;The camera lacks a flash and the camera UI settings are complex.&lt;br&gt;The UI is a bit confused and will take time to get familiarize.&lt;br&gt;The OS hangs on lock screen some times and have to remove the battery to make the device back on&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Windows Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice windows phone in low price range with nice battery and display qualities, we can see clearly Nokia's expertise in making phones even in low price reange.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;HIGH SPEED DELIVERY AND HIGH SPEED MOBILE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;ITS VERY PLEASURE TO SAY THAT ITS AMAZING PHONE AT 7670.AMAZING BATTERY,HIGH SENSIVITY TOUCHING,NO MORE HANGING LIKE SAMSUNG MOBILES,HIGH QUALITY CAMERA AT 5 MP, THE ONLY ABSENCE IS THAT FRONT CAM AND CAMERA FLASH.THE HEAD PHONE IS NOT GET A HIGH BASS OR A STERIO SOUND JUST AN ORDINARY SOUND.BUT GOOD CLARITY AND A CLEAR VOICE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best smart hpone with windows on starting budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's a decent mobile in smart phone era and it has a windows os which performs good. rating os 4.5 out of 5.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product,compare with price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Windows will definitely win the game in long term,moreover, Nokia has given a product which is elegant and  royal. its an perfect phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice Phone and best price. I think online shopping is far more better than actually going to a retail outlet.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=42</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery life is most dissappointing, gud for browsing, i like the rest of the thing are ok with this model,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone, unbelievable price!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my very first windows phone.  I love its responsiveness and speed.  Though it is small on many parameters compared to its more illustrious seniors (620, 720, 920  etc), its performance is wonderful.  And at the price it is available, it is much better than higher priced phones.  I don't need many apps and other functions and so I think this is the phone for me.  This phone has made me a 'windows fan'!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Did not like this windows phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Only good thing which I saw was MS Office. Other than that it is very difficult to use. Not user friendly. The first foolish thing was that it does not say how to make a micro sim from a normal mini sim which all mobile connections give. One small note with one sentence would have been sufficient. The call log is hopeless.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;decnt phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Decent phone and a good change from ios and androids.. An entry level phone, drawback is the less no of apps available.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;phone is excellent but the battery life is too bad have to charge twice or thrice a day&lt;br&gt;great job by nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good delevery of ,product is new.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good delevery of ,product is new.very good delevery of ,product is new.very good delevery of ,product is new.very good delevery of ,product is new.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;1st time Experience with Amazon &amp;amp; Its awsome !!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have Ordered the Mobile on 25th and on 28th Nov 2013 i have getting it in well package and on time as per their commitment.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Hardware defects&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Had to return the product as the ear piece turned bad in 10 days. I was lucky I took the 'Fulfilled by Amazon' product S there were no hassles with the return and refund.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best phone under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was looking for a smartphone under 10k and I was on a tight budget. Started my research and soon realized that cheap android phones are a waste of money and one should buy higher or medium range phones to get a good android experience. I didn't mind experimenting and soon Lumia 520 caught my eye. It had the best screen on any phone less that 10k, reasonable memory and reasonably good appstore. All the major apps are there in Windows appstore also and those were enough for me. But the RAM was only 512MB, but then I knew I am not gonna install each and every app. Flipkart suddenly stopped servicing my area and hence I ordered through Amazon. The delivery was extremely quick and that detailed review of the delivery is given separately. The phone just the right size. It is super fast with nice clean UI and I was able to install all the major apps I wanted. Like Whatsapp, Facebook, Evernote, TuneIn radio etc. I would definitely recommend this phone to everyone on a tight budget. A comparable android phone (It has 1GB RAM though) I found was Sony Xperia M. But it costs 5k more and hence the decision to buy this was a no brainer.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Every thing is ok but something is missing like video file can't be share through blutooth, background downloading not possible, exit from app or close apps very difficult.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=41</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money redefined :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros : -&lt;br&gt;• Thinner than expected and also feels good in hands&lt;br&gt;• Super Camera does a good job, a lot of innovative and improved lenses to choose from.&lt;br&gt;• Silky smooth UI which never hangs even continous long use&lt;br&gt;• Highly perfect responsive touch, works even with gloves on&lt;br&gt;• Games never hang or lag while playing continuously&lt;br&gt;• Offline maps with Nokia Here and here drive works smoothly&lt;br&gt;• Nokia music lets you download all latest and old songs direct to the phone and also online play&lt;br&gt;• Full MS office suit.&lt;br&gt;• Build quality is awesome with a mat finish on its back which gives a firm grip.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:-&lt;br&gt;• Comparatively less apps that android. But almost all required apps are present in store.&lt;br&gt;• No High end gaming due to the 512 ram limitation.&lt;br&gt;.No Bluetooth sharing for the files stored in memory card&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the price, this phone is too good to resist. The colors on the screen appears very sharp and real. I really cant think of any other phone which can give you these features even above 12k.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For those who are still thinking about the number of apps, one quick info - only Microsoft and Apple checks every apps before its put In the store. Android has lots and lots of apps, but most of them are buggy and useless, they either drain out your battery or consume all the resources which results in poor performance. Every app in windows store is verified for its quality and you can be sure, it wont slow down your phone. In android if you install a few apps, the phone will start slowing down.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Back to Nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Likes:&lt;br&gt;1. Performance at its best&lt;br&gt;2. The user interface (Windows 8 tiles)&lt;br&gt;3. Ease of operation (Windows v/s Linux based phones)&lt;br&gt;4. Themes (Ofcource the colorful shells which are simple to replace)&lt;br&gt;5. App ecosystem (Very useful and free apps like MS Office, Nokia Music etc.)&lt;br&gt;6. Windows My phone Service (Data backup on cloud and lost phone service)&lt;br&gt;7. Kid's Corner (Separate home screen for kids)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dislikes:&lt;br&gt;1. Requires Micro SIM (No additional slot for regular SIM)&lt;br&gt;2. Menu options grouping (Like HTC Manila had single window for switching on/off GSM, GPRS/Data, Bluetooth, Wi-Fi connections and Flight Mode)&lt;br&gt;3. Simple touch controls are missing ( Viz. volume adjustment, Call answering requires two operations - slide-up and answer / ignore)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion: My first mobile was Nokia 5110 and I passionately owned Nokia 6220 till the keypad is wornout. I'm very happy to switch back to Nokia after using HTC and BlackBerry phones. No doubt - This variant of Lumia series is a great value for money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review Phone- Nokia Lumie 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good phone as of now. Hope it is an Original phone. Currently the phone is working fine. Thnx&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;As expected:Superb budget smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A great windows 8 phone at such a low price.Very sensitive and classic touch.Screen gets smudgy very quickly,however I love this phone.&lt;br&gt;Good customer service from Amazon.By far the best customer service experience I have ever had.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool Phone from Nokia!!!!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The usability of the phone is awesome ... The touch is superb. The display resolution is as it should be. Its a best buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review of Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am using this phone for more than a month.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Buttery smooth UI which never hangs.&lt;br&gt;2. Ultra responsive touch.&lt;br&gt;3. Call quality is good.&lt;br&gt;4. Works fast for internet browsing using both wifi and 3G.&lt;br&gt;5. Offline GPS navigation using Here drive is great and has saved me several times.&lt;br&gt;6. Preinstalled apps Big flix and Nokia music store are great  and useful.&lt;br&gt;7. Build quality is good.&lt;br&gt;8. Camera does a good job even in low light.&lt;br&gt;9. Value for Money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1. Poor battery as it drains fast and hardly lasts a day for web browsing / games.&lt;br&gt;2. Cant play temple run.. hangs.. good for games like inspree etc.&lt;br&gt;3. No front camera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a good phone and value for money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone for best price!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought it in offer just for 7499/-&lt;br&gt;Camera and music quality is good&lt;br&gt;Windows OS with superb with all the required apps&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very pleased by the service provided by amazon. It was great shopping with amazon. I enjoyed it. :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a phone below 10K. Good back up of battery. Only drawback is apps are less for windows phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It was nice to prucahse from amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Valued for money and Phone is working fine,Compared with other sites its in my budget.Really have to say value for money..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=47</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;love you nokia....u r the only king in market...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;again nokia proved ......best fone at best price....very much better than samsung and other chinese......lot of hang problem....fake body....fake looks.....&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but nokia 520.....awesome everthing....must buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good quality average phone in its category&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I would give 3 stars to this product&lt;br&gt;The look and finish of the phone is good. Touch response is good&lt;br&gt;However windows 8 OS is not as user friendly as Android&lt;br&gt;The user interface is dull and doesn't allow much customization.&lt;br&gt;Camera features are good, but image quality is average&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is true Windows phone at the reasonable cost!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is very nice moble and True windows phone at the reasonable cost. So any one can buy this mobile and enjoy!.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome blossom&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its the best phone is this price range....every one should buy it...services of amazon.in are awesome.on time and perfect packaging&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this is budget wala phone, which i purchased in 7500k only, n just flash for camera is missin rest all is good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It works so good.It's touch sensivity,camera quality,Browsing speed in a word is awesome.Thaks amazon for giving me the best quality windows phone.......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;big disappointment no audio equaliser ! rest ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;BAD:&lt;br&gt;weak battery&lt;br&gt;camera without flash&lt;br&gt;age old music player without equaliser&lt;br&gt;bad earphones&lt;br&gt;bad phone case, no gloss,gets detached easily&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;GOOD:&lt;br&gt;windows 8 refreshing&lt;br&gt;good apps frm nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520 worth buying&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone. Full value for money.&lt;br&gt;you can't ask for more in this range. Camera, sound, screen resolution  and most importantly the speed, simply awesome&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone in the price tag given&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;good performance&lt;br&gt;great multitasking&lt;br&gt;sleek design and cheap in price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;cons&lt;br&gt;lacking few mandatory features like file manager, full SD support&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Absolute value for money phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;like - price, full features, fantastic battery life, easy and smooth interface&lt;br&gt;dislike - no flash, have to pay for Whatsapp!!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=49</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Wonderful&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Wonderful product from Nokia.. Excellent User Interface and performance is great.. Touch screen is wonderful. Enough number of apps are available. Hope we can get more apps in future.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Some quiries&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Dear Amazon,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  1. Please let me know how to download some videos and audios like YOUTUBE videos.&lt;br&gt;  2. I couldn't able to view or download the Microsoft Excel sheet, Word and PPT through gmail account, so please tell me  how&lt;br&gt;  to do those things, except above doubts remaining all facilities in Nokia lumia 520.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  Thanking you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The performance of the product is upto my expectation.The item is user friendly and battery back up is very good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Prompt service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Cheapest price I got at Amazon.&lt;br&gt;Service was fast and prompt.&lt;br&gt;Packaging was also excellent.&lt;br&gt;I really like this phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;product not upto the mark&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Camea result not upto the mark.&lt;br&gt;Unsatisfied with camera result.not supporting many applications like in Anroid OS.&lt;br&gt;Flash is required.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;battery probs...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery is the best thing in nokia ... but its draining soon ... it lasts only for a max of two days ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very nice product at good price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;simply superb - the packing was very well done with all its accessories including its warranty.  I just loved it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome!! budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Suits all your needs. Stands up to the expectation.&lt;br&gt;A phone @ this price and with such a large screen, definitely not to be missed.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;product is original&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it at cheapest price.  Phone is 100% original. Got before deliiver&lt;br&gt;date. Packing was good. Don't hesitate go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone to choose. No need to  go for samsung or other phones as this will meet all your requirements.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=52</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best in class&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia as always showing commitment to quality offering best in class battery life with least charging time n max discharge time.&lt;br&gt;Faster browsing with even 2G makes it rise to the top.&lt;br&gt;Its value for money.&lt;br&gt;Go for it..&lt;br&gt;Amazing....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best budget phone for first time smart phone users&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Used this smart phone for the first time and purchased it from amazon.in.&lt;br&gt;Contains all the basic features of any smartphone including 3G network, nice touch screen, windows 8, etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;only drawback is its low battery of 1430 mAH which prevents it from sustaining for more than one day and that too if internet, bluetooth etc are kept on only during usage.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome!!!!Very Happy with My Purchase&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It has been over a month now with my Nokia Lumia 520. The experience of Windows 8 phone is totally different from Android. It is a no nonsense phone. It has never hanged. The UI is initially difficult to understand however you will start loving it gradually. Here Maps works offline too and that is the major plus point of this phone. With certain useful apps you can customize the phones according to your need. I am very satisfied with my purchase and recommend everyone to go with this Phone if you are budget is close to 8K.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;exceptional&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its awesome..tnq amazon for d fascinating offers...i have already booked another one for my relative ..... I am very thankful to amazon.in😊😊😊😊😊💖💖💖💖&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;i am using it and i dint face any problem&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;outstanding phone specially touch and camera.....&lt;br&gt;under 10000 rupees phone this phone is best choice...&lt;br&gt;and 4 inch display makes it perfect to use ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone with great features and within a good price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was afraid to get a windows phn .. but this phn totally changed my mind regarding the windows phone..&lt;br&gt;great looks.. slim and light... if u want a smart phone for a start this is the best choice you'll ever make..&lt;br&gt;happy to get NOKIA LUMIA 520&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone and good to be with the hand. more over i really great to buy from the amazon also works cool&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Pros and consequences of Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;PROs:&lt;br&gt;Its been 3 months i am using Nokia Lumia 520 i bought at rs 7500/-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;with in 10000 rs budget it is good phoone to buy&lt;br&gt;1.looks smooth,good and 4 inch screen suites hand perfect&lt;br&gt;2.internal memory : 8gb is good to install more apps&lt;br&gt;3.camera 5mp with absolute clarity&lt;br&gt;4.battery life (no need of talking nokia battery )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;1.all apps are available but need to buuy in xbox&lt;br&gt;2.micro sim&lt;br&gt;3.no flash and front cam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;  ram is 512 mb but no lagging&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520,its  amazing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i bought this Nokia Lumia phone on 1st November, and i feel very good, this phone is working fine and they delivered in time&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thats way i suggested to my friends, i only booked to my other friends on Amazon.com&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you Amazon......................By......V Raja&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best in its category&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Advantages:&lt;br&gt;1) The user interface is very good&lt;br&gt;2) Internal memory of 8GB is best at this price&lt;br&gt;3) Camera clarity is good&lt;br&gt;4) Vast number of applications available in nokia store&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disadvantages:&lt;br&gt;1) Battery backup is not upto mark&lt;br&gt;2) Gets heated up easily&lt;br&gt;3) 1GHz processor would have been an icing on the cake&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall its worth ur money.... Just go for it....&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=53</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;it is nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I would recommend this product this product to Microsoft Fans and also for people with windows 8 laptop or Tab&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;fast, good, easy to use, full featured smart, window mobile phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is nice and have all required features, overall very good experience.. (Just flash is na, will do without)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fits perfect.. Comfortable to use.. Quality is better... The product is not awesome but it is somewhat worth enough for the price...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is good value for the money. It has all the features of smartphone like GPS, 3G etc ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is GOood&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is very nice and good to use than other heavy mobiles.It has all functions of all big mobiles.&lt;br&gt;thank..u&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent Amazon service, delivery was prompt, delivery guy was helpful&lt;br&gt;Mobile works great, don't believe on rumours. Every negative feedback that I heard about it was fake. Go for it blindly, if its available in less than 7k.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good product and best price.. I am searched in all online stores, the lowest price was in amazon. it is a good deal..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 250  through Amazon from Univercell:&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon service is good. You can improve the packing with a brief packing case.&lt;br&gt;Service information and follow up and delivery was very prompt and very speedy.&lt;br&gt;But,I have to go to an ATM to provide cash at 17.00 hrs with the help of delivery boy...&lt;br&gt;better  a card swiping machine tobe provided(like others e-shops to the delivery men.&lt;br&gt;The product Nokia Lumia 520 I have received is very nice and the Amazon supplier&lt;br&gt;rate is very cheaper comparing other suppliers of this product and I am using&lt;br&gt;it since then without any problems...Nokia is Nokia no challenge.....happy to have it!&lt;br&gt;Thank you Amazon.in, keep it up and wish u a good trade future to the e-trade.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Satisfied with my Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my first buy from Amazon.in and i am really impressed from Amazon. They met the expected time of delivery. I was amazed to get a call early morning around 7:30 AM about my address and around 8:30AM i got my Lumia. It was nicely packed with bubble pack (looks new packaging from Amazon).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now come to Lumia 520..the mobile is very good, touch, looks everything is perfect..Only drawback i feel there is very less customization you can do with Microsoft OS..(like changing of style of home screen, customization of icons,scroll in homecreen..file manager, live wallpaper.. etc). But if you need a decent device not for gaming and other high fundoo stuff then this is best..But still i feel Android is better then windows os..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would strongly recommend this phone..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice device&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The device is superb, received seal pack box, Love the new windows 8 operating system. The look &amp;amp; features of mobile is great. The various camera lenses offered by Nokia is superb. Overall the best phone at such a low price.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=50</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;great product ... good value for money spent and looks elegant ...I didn't find any problems with the phone .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best in its range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is a perfect treat in its price range. With supercool touch, you can have yourself gliding through the experience. The Nokia Drive application is awesome. The phone functions well without any complaints of hanging contrary to most of the Android phones. The camera is fine in day light, but without a flash it wont be able to capture the best in night.&lt;br&gt;PS: The Amazon deal added to its beauty.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product excellent service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very Good product, reasonable price and excellent service. Received within one week from the date of order. Nicely packed .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have bought this phone for my dad.. and he really loved it...&lt;br&gt;This is the cheapest on all site and i highly recommend to go for it..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon Store is Cheaper than all online store.&lt;br&gt;It is awesome mobile.&lt;br&gt;Great windows mobile.&lt;br&gt;*** Value for money ***&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best entry segment phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got the phone during diwali with an excellent price. quite fast for all generic apps. Though some Apps are missing in comparison to Android serves to my purpose. good battery back up generally full day+few hours with 1-2 hrs of talking and 1hr browsing. Free nokia music store is an advantage. Delivered next day to order..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The phone is very good for its cost&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is really nice, it got really good UI,Touch is good, and Wi-Fi is fatser than its counterparts from Samsung.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;1.This is best Windows phone at this range&lt;br&gt;2.Windows is far better than Android&lt;br&gt;3.Battery life , browsing, Social networking ,Office and Email apps are even better than android&lt;br&gt;4.For tight budget for go 520 unless i recommend to buy 720&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;super phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;this full fills all my requirements.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thanks to Microsoft and Nokia for giving great phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks amazon for the offer.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;amazing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazon brings amazing,For the price, this phone is too good to resist. It has got everything to win your heart. The colours on the screen appears very sharp and real. I really cant think of any other phone which can give you these features&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=55</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;pretty satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;overall very satisfied with lumia 520&lt;br&gt;cons: cant send video in whtsapp , apps are not as good as in android, bluetooth connection is littl complicated, and equilizer is not there ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;My first smartphone has changed my life&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Im writing this review on my Lumia 520 and Im glad Amazon India was a part of this experience. Though the offer I used to buy this phone is no more, but I love my phone and my friends are fans as well. Looking forward to getting more AMAZONG offers!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cells' good but its all screw tempered&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is working in good condition and everything's good. A couple of week before I notice while I'm inserting my SD card that marks on its all screws and I'm 100% sure its all there while i receive the product.&lt;br&gt;Now I'm afraid if nokia doesn't accept it under warranty. Really bad :( :(&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;As per expectations from AMAZON.com&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;SuperLike!!!&lt;br&gt;Awesome phone.Great on performance and great on features. I would recommend this phone over any android phone of same range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SLEEK AND STYLISH&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The youngest member of NOKIA LUMIA family and by far the most reasonable product by Nokia.&lt;br&gt;Fast processor, Windows 8, great camera and great graphics.&lt;br&gt;This is a complete package for those who want lumia in their hands and not spend much.&lt;br&gt;Kudos.!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is just osm with all configuration and stuff. i recommend this to all. very good working and functions&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I am very satisfied with LUMIA 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my first purchase from Amazon and i am really satisfied with the services and with the product.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks Amazon...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Sudeep Bhatt is happy now&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Iam very happy to purchase lumia 520.its a very good phone having best quality camera and other features with a pleasant experience of windows phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone in this budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent phone in this budget.  Nice touch, excellent camera, windows os, excellent quality of wi-fi, good number of apps etc..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;only con is : no front cam.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got the product I wanted at the best price.....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was looking for it as &amp;amp; got it at the price I was not expecting. It was simply amazing.......&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=54</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice smartphone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia with windows system. Good combination of brands.&lt;br&gt;Looks stylish as well as elegent.&lt;br&gt;Goes with casual, official, sporty all requirements.&lt;br&gt;Good aid for people who are constantly travelling.&lt;br&gt;Nice sturdy body &amp;amp; looks.&lt;br&gt;Windows OS not easy to use??? Its a myth!!!!&lt;br&gt;Less battery life though. Need to recharge almost everyday with just moderate use.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent budget mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Highly recommended.enjoying windows mobile in Nokia phone. Value for money.touch screen is very responsive with good quality camera. Missing front camera for video calls.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone in my life&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best phone in my life. best windows phone.  ...........Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)  best , mobile . nokia . 520. best&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worth Buying !!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;1. Awesome touch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.Battery is little bit concern.&lt;br&gt;2.Poor file Management&lt;br&gt;3. No flash in camera&lt;br&gt;4.Sometimes it will get switched off automatically.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Really Love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Real quick delivery. well packaged(it matters more than you think)&lt;br&gt;About the product&lt;br&gt;Pro's&lt;br&gt;1.The 1 GHz Dualcore Processor makes the phone quite fast.&lt;br&gt;2.Its really light weight.&lt;br&gt;3.Very sturdy, it feel down like 5-10 times till now and only a minor scratch. Actually surprised the screen did not get damaged because its not gorilla glass.&lt;br&gt;4.Windows Phone 8 with the Lumia Black update makes things very very good.&lt;br&gt;5.The battery life is very good too. im not an avid user but i get approx 1.5-2 days which is very good&lt;br&gt;Con's&lt;br&gt;1.The camera is just average being a 5mp but i have seen better 5mp cameras&lt;br&gt;2.Lack of flash.(no need to expand on this)&lt;br&gt;3.Lack of a front camera, no problems faced due to the lack of it but wont hurt to have one.&lt;br&gt;3.The 512mb ram is not sufficient all the time. Whatsapp randomly crashes,and phone lags sometimes. but only sometimes.&lt;br&gt;4.To remove sim card/memory card we have to remove the battery&lt;br&gt;5.Although memory card slot is provided all the apps install onto phone memory but this is going to be addressed by Microsoft in the coming updates, so dont have to worry about that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verdict: Great phone for a even greater price, few shortcomings but what the heck every phone has a few shortcomings.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;another good product from nokia in mid segment.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a best mob in its category. Futures are also good &amp;amp; net surfing awesome.&lt;br&gt;service provided by amazon is too good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best buy for this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Whether its a entry level Windows phone but for sure it does a smart task that a person really needs.&lt;br&gt;I loved its all features.There is nothing that lags as I hear from many people except user isn't a game freak.&lt;br&gt;In short it's a computer in your palm having Win8..&lt;br&gt;Enjoy..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone @ best price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Like it very much.... It's different. Best camera, best features, performance and totaly good phone at right price.  And also good service by amazon, great and good experience with amazon.......... 😊&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very gud looking with good speed of performance&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I gave this much rating because some times it's getting stocked, so i need to restart it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have recommended to many of my friends to buy it and two of them has bought it...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;jyotsana&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the phone is very good but there is a problem how to share video or how to select collar tune.&lt;br&gt;if you help me this problem i''ll appreciate you,its humble request.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regards&lt;br&gt;jyotsana&lt;br&gt;9891213860&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=51</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Working&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have taken Lumia 520 on 29th oct 13 and it is working good until now..... Low cost and best efficiency&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good, Nokia satisfied me again with good user friendly one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good, Nokia satisfied me again with good user friendly one, First week experience is good.. Feel got the right one&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lumia 520 a smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good and smart phone.easy to operate and understand app&lt;br&gt;Battery is withstanding for one day.overall lumia520 is a good phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review of Nokia Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My previous phone was BlackBerry and I decided to switch to Windows Lumia 520. What a performance, suddenly I find myself in fast lane. Feature loaded and with long life battery, it is real worth the money spent...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good spec ... really smooth experince&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia 520 is awesome..and really very fast as compared to any other phones in this range.&lt;br&gt;windows experimce is great:P :).. But RAM is littlebit low ... So u maycan go lumia525 which is going to releases soon.&lt;br&gt;... :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;getting switched off frequently&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i bought this product one month ago. i got this problem of getting switched off frequently since from the first day. Also it does not read my micro SD card. now i am going to replace this. this problem might be due  to loose battery i think because after 2-3 days when i put a small piece of paper to tighten the battery,afterward i worked fine but still memory card problem is there.&lt;br&gt;  So choose this at your own risk, if you get ideal product then this phone is good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Battery life not to the expectation&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The configurations are good. But the battery back up is very bad,it will be down  in 9hrs even if i do not use the set for talking or internet purpose. i need some help in this regard. Hope AMZON will give me some gidance regarding this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superhub.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Processar &amp;amp; RAM. Camera &amp;amp; Video HD Quality . Becomes Heat while using the Internet,  i can recommed for entry level user.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;really smart&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good but battery drains quickly .it has good features for a low price rs 7500/.over all it is really a smartphone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Altogether a nice phone w.r.t. to performance great for gaming, doesn't hang if compared any other os&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shortcomings:&lt;br&gt;1. No vibration mode&lt;br&gt;2.FM Radio not available&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=56</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;520 Absolute Review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia 520 - A good Price Mobile&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its a entry level smart phone  - Good Resolution/Build/Battery Back Up etc&lt;br&gt;Cons : No Quality Pictures on Low light(Very Good in Day Light)&lt;br&gt;  No apps when others enjoying with android&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia 520 is great but you have a pc and internet to download the apps for him but it is a required to Lumia but its performance is so good and amazon buy in very low price so get it now and the tiles are very superb it is very simple to got the app and they give info of ot&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Phone at cheaper price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile Nokia Lumia 520 is awesome and I bought at cheaper from the market rate from Amazon and its working absolutely fine.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Paisa wasool phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like the phone very much " it is a Paisa wasool phone". Also when you buy it from Amazon its a awesome experience the price you find the best in market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;There is 1 disadvantage of this phone that is no file manager in this phone. If you have to do any changes in your SD Card data so you have connect this phone with PC. But other wise phone is awesome &amp;amp; i will recommend to all.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The Best product, Best service from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia 520 is an awesome phone at this price range, go for it eye closed. !!!&lt;br&gt;For few, only dis-advantage is the no-flash, no front camera if you can  live with this, rest is all good. !!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Received the phone in 2 days of placing order. packing is well taken care by amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice price compare to other sites.&lt;br&gt;Mobile is very smooth , worth for the price.&lt;br&gt;Go for it when u wanna a low budjet smart phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its not user friendly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bluetooth is not working properly, and additionally camera is also not upto that level of expectation, i expect more from this&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Defective and worst&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Zoomin Camera was the seller from which I have bought this item. But from 10th day ( of the delivery of product) onwards, this product started to show a lot of problems/ issues.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I would like to suggest you not to go for this seller - "Zoom in Camera stores"&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good useful&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery level is not as usual in Nokia phones, will take time to assess  that one, after using for sometime&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good service............&lt;br&gt;would look for further purchase ...&lt;br&gt; good product....&lt;br&gt;user interface inconvenience with software...&lt;br&gt;less apps&lt;br&gt;worth paying money ...&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=57</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Review of Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best Windows phone for that price ...I got it at a discount price for Rs 7000 only..Thank you Amazon hoping more such offers in future like christmas offers new year offers ;)(Temple run 1 will stop after continuous 15mins of game by heating up the device except that no problem till now)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone for 7K..&lt;br&gt;The touch is awesome, switching app is smoother, using windows OS is totally different than the Android. Like it,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Defective product delivered&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Unfortunately i ordered this for my Mother as her first touch phone, but the phone arrived defective ,&lt;br&gt;with loose back cover&lt;br&gt;issue with battery not seating properly&lt;br&gt;phone switching off frequently&lt;br&gt;phone not switching on, taking too long&lt;br&gt;and the regular windows usability problems&lt;br&gt;and by the time i found out , the replacement window 10 days is over&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fine working, good offer, Cheaper price, really happy on this purchase. thank you for best ever offer from amazon .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget mobile ka boss&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am fully satisfied with the product. Window phone is the best.. OS is like butter. Go for it. Perfect.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice phone....worth to invest....Nokia has really make this to compete with Samsung, Sony or Micromax.....&lt;br&gt;Buy and use this to believe....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The expectations at the price point were modest and it has materialized as a decent handset.&lt;br&gt;One does rue the lower battery life, lack of flash, relatively poor camera etc but on the whole a satisfying phone. The 8 gigs of internal memory certainly gets one going. WP8 also is quite a nice interface though file management is complicated.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thumbs up overall.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Right Buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good mobile but with some cons...&lt;br&gt;Haptic feedback(and we cant disable it I think) is irritating,&lt;br&gt;and it doesn't have compass in it its hard to find directions...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Anyone migrating to the Windows ecosystem should try this low priced phone before buying a flagship device. Good buy at this price point.&lt;br&gt;The one thing I didn't like was the lack of a front facing camera.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its very good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good product in reasonable price.. i will rate their performance as 5 stars . their service is amazing... :) i will command this to others also. hope this services will continue in future as well....:)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=59</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;A good phone and can be recomended&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;As I recived the product from Amazon,1st thing i need to mention is packaging. I can award a 5 star for their packaging. Amazon should start their own logistics. Now If i come to the phone it,s a good fone for Windows 8 users as you register for a microsoft account and connect your emails faceboos and twitter account with it It will get sync'd automatically. Now afer the introduction of Windows phone 8 and easy PC and Phone sync its great to use.I am using this for past 1 month and I am happy with the performence And one thing I must say is the touch sensitivity . I have used i pad and Iphones before andI have never seen such a good touch sesitivity even in any android phone renging 15K.You can even sync your itunes librery with your windows phone&lt;br&gt;Now I must say about few con's of the phone . Battery of the Lumia 520 is what I can say is oned of the worst i have ever seen, If you gonna use your phone randomly with data,phones as well as with data over wifi your battery life is maximum 6-8 hours. I am not complaining as this is very common among the smartphones. Headphone as always provided by by nokia with such a good phone is worst I have ever met. The phone get over heated whenyou charge it or use data.And nokia saying it's not a problem.&lt;br&gt;Overll i can say that cons are less and can be adjustable and one can surely go Windows at such a low price Its a multitaskingphone with MS office Xbox music and games and many more,but a bit less apps on windows store but again I cn say that,s not a issue because less apps means less harrasment to your phone.&lt;br&gt;Last but not the list i didnt play games in my phone so I am nott gonna review against the gaming experiance of the phone,but few of my friends using windows phone says that it's much better than a same budjet android.&lt;br&gt;So that'ls all And i am gonna recommand this to my next buyers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;too good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got it on time. Within two days.&lt;br&gt;its nice thing from nokia.&lt;br&gt;and good service by amazon.&lt;br&gt;thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Bang for the buck&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am new to Windows phone (I am an Android user)&amp;amp; trust me this phone handles great.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The snapdragon S4 dual core chip along with 512 MB RAM makes the user experience smooth &amp;amp; lag free. Camera is decent &amp;amp; can shoot 720p videos, pic quality is again decent, though lack of flash is disappointing. Since its a budget phone the omissions aren't surprising.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With the latest update the FM radio has been enabled. The windows store has all necessary apps though the collection is shady compared to the play-store (android) &amp;amp; the app-store (Iphone)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phone is definitely a looker, the 4 inch screen isn't too big nor small &amp;amp; just fits the bill. Watching videos &amp;amp; pics are hassle free &amp;amp; the screen supports vibrant colours along with good contrast &amp;amp; viewing angles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For its price there is no better alternative than the lumia 520.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The deal I received was very good. value for money. The delivery was best and the phone is also working fine. However found few problems in phone like its hangs suddenly then u need to remove the battery and then restart, you can not attach file through phone on the gmail, the searching of names in contacts is bit slow. The software very fast. Overall it is good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;GREAT PHONE WITH GREAT OFFER FROM AMAZON&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;VERY NICE PHONE IN THIS PRICE. REALLY A VALUE PACKED PHONE  FROM NOKIA WITH WINDOW 8 AND OTHER GREAT FEATURE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best in this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Well packed and Timely delievery from amazon.&lt;br&gt;Not so big, not so small screen size, good camera quality and rest all things are standard.&lt;br&gt;Build quality of phone is good. My verdict is BUY if you are looking for a phone less than 8-9k.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Average&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;packaging, price and delivery are top notch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mobile is ok for the price, I am finding windows is not that user friendly after switching from an android phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Small missing things:&lt;br&gt;No flash&lt;br&gt;Very less applications, even the apps which are free in adroid are paid one in windows.&lt;br&gt;In Whatsapp you cannot send MP3 songs.&lt;br&gt;No file manager.&lt;br&gt;You cannot make a song as ringtone without connecting laptop or ringtone maker app.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Having said all these, mobile hangs quite often so had to remove the battery for restart.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;In one Word it's Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After reading so many reviews of Windows Phone , where people complain regarding missing features of this OS, in lack of knowledge, and no place to answer them, I thought to Right this review to kill the wrong myth spreading regarding windows phones and Nokia Lumia:-&lt;br&gt;#You can share Photos, videos, Music via Bluetooth. (Caution- The option is only visible only if the phone is connected to a device via BT. Connect first in settings and then try to share).&lt;br&gt;#Multiple file sharing is only available for pics for now. You can select as many photos u want and send them in one go via BT. Music/videos are sent one by one.&lt;br&gt;#To save Battery, read the tips in Nokia Care app which comes preinstalled in phone. Also there are many helpful tips there.&lt;br&gt;#Gmail is working perfectly fine on windows phone. Even if Google turn off Active sync in july, Microsoft will update the client with new meathod to sync. But, its been adviced that you make your Microsoft Live account (outlook) as main account and try to shift your work to it. Moreover, Outlook service is far more better than Gmail. Try it.&lt;br&gt;#Apps are coming. We now have Temple Run 1 in WP store, so its sure we will get updates from that developer. Moreover, as WP is gaining popularity, developers are surely taking this platform seriously &amp;amp; coming with more great apps for it. And saying buy an android for now till apps come on wp will not solve problem. Buy more windows phones, sooner you will get more new apps.&lt;br&gt;#No words on instagram for WP yet. But looking at Nokia's #2instawithlove campaign. its not far when we will see instagram for windowsphone. BTW, an app called instagraph is coming which allow to share pics on instagram.&lt;br&gt;#Please don't ask for any more Music Player. We have many (few names include Tune wiki, Lyrics, Mixtapes, Album Flow, TuneIn, AUPEO, Soundtracker, etc) but Nokia Music is ultimate, try it, and you will never ask for any other player again.&lt;br&gt;#You can of course Fast forward/Reverse Songs/videos. Not by seek bar, but by long pressing Next/previous buttons. Remember, if you can't find any option, try Longpressing, it always turns out useful.&lt;br&gt;#To download youtube videos, Try Metrotube.&lt;br&gt;# One more thing I would like to clear before you buy this phone &amp;amp; post bad reviews, that if you thinking to use this phone as your Pendrive to carry unsupported data (yes, many of users complain that they can't transfer unsupported files to WP to carry them on phone itself), then mind it, it can't do that, Microsoft is very serious regarding quality and security in Windows Phones. Moreover, if you can't live without downloading pirated apps/movies/music from illeagal sites (though we have Nokia Music &amp;amp; Free Movie Streaming apps) on your phone itself, then Keep Away! Its a WINDOWS PHONE, piracy is strictly not allowed. And regarding FREE APPS, ofcourse there are many in store. Moreover, you can download almost all paid apps/Games on Trial. To do so, just go to any paid app, see if its available on trial, "TRY" option will be there on bottom left of screen. That trial app/game would be downloaded for free, &amp;amp; would be either Fully functional but ad supported, or would be usable for limited time (but its rare) or will have Some advanced Features/Levels Restricted. In the latter case, you can use free app till its limit, &amp;amp; if u like, then buy it. SORRY, NO METHOD TO DOWNLOAD THE PAID VERSION FOR FREE!! U know, NO PIRACY...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;smooth touch, good speed, good battery life...good camera but flash is missing..overall good phone..and best deal..got it for rs. 6300&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;fine..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One problem i am facing is it restarts on its own sometimes.. Other than that it is ok&lt;br&gt;..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;worth the price&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=60</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent lumia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;font &amp;amp; display are marvellous!! internet speed is highly appreciated. i like the o.s. of lumia.purchase &amp;amp; forget . superb!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Yeah, Its good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;All says that windows phones are not good to buy....its hard to use... and all that... But I think this windows 8 phone is too good to its perfomance, results, perfect photos and video display, good apps and games with no errors. Speed is damn good and smooth with no stuck and hanging problems...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I will give minus one star because its have no inbuilt file manager with all file controls...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A nice Smartphone at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all this is a nokia product so i have full faith on its durability. This phone is quite attractive and display is awesome.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very much satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the service and the tracking and packagging almost every thing is perfect from amazon... will definitely buy from amazon again. waiting for good deals..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At Rs.7000, the Nokia Lumia 520 offers great value for money. I don't think the Windows Mobile operating system is powerful enough on more expensive handsets, but this phone just doesn't feel like a sub 10k hardware. If all you are looking for is a smartphone which can do Email, Whatsapp and average camera, then you can'y go wrong with the 520. I feel that this is a much better handset at 7k compared to what other manufacturers like Samsung, Micromax and Karbonn have to offer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Perfect phone for your mom/dad or as an emergency phone for yourself.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is the cheapest Windows mobile, but is no way less than other compentators .&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got it for just Rs.7000 only on Amazon. Its a good looking small but full featured phone in this price range of an excellent reputted company.&lt;br&gt;Nokia ka bahorasa with Windows... :-)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A Good Buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's been more than 20 days i have been using this mobile and found it good but not great upto my expectations. The major cons are 1) you can't explore the files in your sd card other than songs,videos,and pictures and there is no good app in the market for file exploration,folder edit,move options.&lt;br&gt; 2) the battery drains unexpectedly.&lt;br&gt; 3) songs downloaded from other than nokia music can not be transferred to the music folder.&lt;br&gt; 4) u can't use internet while calling as I could have used in nokia 5230,but I knw most of the mobiles don't support this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But when you look at the price,I don't think any mobile will be better than this.I bought it for ₹6,999.&lt;br&gt;If microsoft could provide good file explorer,I think it will be a great pro for this mobile.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice product easy to use and i expecting more deal like this . packing is good and the shipment  time super keep going&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent for Price tag of Rs 7780&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Lumia is going to become No.1 in Next 1 year . Excellent phone, with good quality. I had samsung galaxy young before which came for just 1 year 1 month, after that motherboard stopped working. I had to throw that phone. Lumia looks itself says that it will last longer. There is no lagging like android phones in the same price tag. Interface is really cool. In one word to describe, awesome phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent choice at this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;+ Excellent touch&lt;br&gt;+ Very good display&lt;br&gt;+ Well build&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;- Limited apps in Windows app store (not a fault of the phone, but if you are considering a shift to Windows)&lt;br&gt;- No front cam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall very less flaws, excellent choice at this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y?pageNumber=58</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item></items>