<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best mobile under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am quite an old fashioned person when it comes to electronic gazettes. I was never fascinated by smartphones, tablets and other touch screen devices and was very happy with my simple basic mobile. It was only accidentally that i gave it a thought to go for a smartphone after i lost my mobile and my techno-savvy friend advised me to go for this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transition from a simplest basic mobile to the Smartphone could never be more easier, thanks to Nokia Lumia 520 and Windows 8.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do not know much technical bits to appraise this mobile, but i can state many of its advantages from a layman's angle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Excellent build quality- I dropped it on a cement road from my bicycle to find it in three pieces. But nothing was damaged.&lt;br&gt;2. For it's primary usage as a phone- Excellent voice quality, speaker phone is at its best. Signal reception is also very good. SMS Interface is very different than regular basic phones and i found it to be quite innovative.&lt;br&gt;3. Screen size of 4' is quite appropriate. It fits in your palm well and goes in the packet very nicely.&lt;br&gt;4. Display quality is excellent. It may not have the best viewing angle though, but for a single viewer, you get the best.&lt;br&gt;5. Windows 8 feels amazing. Very user friendly, desktop kind of interface and positioning of apps could not be more simple.&lt;br&gt;6. It will not be wise to ignore Windows phones thinking that it does not have enough apps. You would find apps for almost all of your needs.&lt;br&gt;7. The most beautiful feature i found is the Kid's Corner. Here, you can create different profile for your kid. And you will be at peace, while your child is trying her hands at your mobile. With this profile, your child can not make any outgoing calls or can not mend with your important files in the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though, there are some limitations as below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. There is no front camera, but what more can you expect in a budget phone.&lt;br&gt;2. No radio. But for me, it doesn't matter. I do have best radio apps downloaded in my phone.&lt;br&gt;3. There is no key to search within mobile, instead there is a key that takes you to the web search engine- Bing. I can't justify a separate key only to search over web.&lt;br&gt;4. Lack of Dual SIM. Don't understand why Nokia does not have this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, i found this to be the best smartphone with a budget below 10K. Go for it even if your budget is more than it. It is worth for each and every paisa!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Total value for Money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Windows phone 8 is awesome and a refreshing change from Android. As regarding apps, essential apps are available and there are some  games such as Dredd &amp;amp; Zombies, Reaper, royal revolt, etc. Temple run is running without a glitch, but its true that it have way less apps &amp;amp; games than the android or iOS.&lt;br&gt;The hardware is robust with Dual core processor and 512 MB RAM. The phone's interface is pretty straight forward and never lagged even after i have installed 100s of apps.&lt;br&gt;The only downside is battery performance is a little below par with almost a day with light to moderate usage. If you do heavy usage like 3G browsing, Videos or Gaming it hardly lasts for 4 hours.&lt;br&gt;Overall it's a decent smartphone experience under 8K, thanks to Nokia's strong spec and Microsoft WP8. Buy it, you will love it...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great product from Nokia!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really it is worth the value for your money.  Purchased last month. I like the color very much. Go for it!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good value for money smartphone from nokia...camera is excellent...if u want a branded smartphone in this range go for this....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good phone in this price range...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i am really satisfied with this as it is having all the features a smartphone can,,, best camera in tis price range and the touch is ultra sensitive...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is really a recommended budget smartphone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 520 is really a recommended budget smartphone. Just look at this product frequently. Sometimes amazon sells it at a very low price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Major disadvantage&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hangs more frequently. Gets heated when running on 3G. over all performance is good. I like it.Thank you nokia lumia 520&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;OUTSTANDING&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;ITS VERY PLEASURE TO SAY THAT ITS AMAZING PHONE AT 7670.AMAZING BATTERY,HIGH SENSIVITY TOUCHING,NO MORE HANGING LIKE SAMSUNG MOBILES,HIGH QUALITY CAMERA AT 5 MP, THE ONLY ABSENCE IS THAT FRONT CAM AND CAMERA FLASH.THE HEAD PHONE IS NOT GET A HIGH BASS OR A STERIO SOUND JUST AN ORDINARY SOUND.BUT GOOD CLARITY AND A CLEAR VOICE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;Very easy to set up and use&lt;br&gt;Has WIndows Office version. Except that it has limited features. But you can read all your documents very easily on it&lt;br&gt;Direct connectivity to your PC. No cloud nonsense to deal with, at least in transferring photos and documents&lt;br&gt;Decent collection of apps. At least I got what I wanted&lt;br&gt;All the Nokia Apps are wonderful - Nokia Mix Radio is brilliant. The apps for photography are superb. Data transfer from other phones is decent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;Battery is terrible&lt;br&gt;Sync with MS Live can be confusing with all the various accounts MS has (live, Hotmail, Outlook,,,,)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazon beats with price and delivery yet again!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No point in writing about 520. One of the best mobiles. Needed for my Mom, so did not bother to buy 525. Extra RAM of no use.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Love the Nokia Music feature.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon yet again beat every other online store with price and delivery. Thanks!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CM4W5OQ</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Red)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;do not buy from vendor  GadgetsGuru.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;when i open package i saw finger prints on mobile and small lines over screen ,i ignored that but when i switch on the mobile there is a small scratch on screen which is reflecting a light ,this is very poor services and am sure this vendor cheated me ..they know already this product is defective ..this is my last time am purchasing from amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice, solid built a decent processor, G8 display 5inch phone, touch very nice, audio superb and loudspeaker is also good...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;thumbs down&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Third class phone *like driving Honda with nano's engine*!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dont buy this phone, your life will be in mess.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bye&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I would rate it as 4&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent phone. Screen is too good. But many of the apps do not get downloaded. Camera is superb. Speed is also very good. Overall I would definitely recommend this phone. thanks and regards. Subramanian&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone for normal use&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;hey guys got this phone for my mom recently.its pretty good.whatsapp doesnt work but whatsapp+ works fine.just download its apk and your good to go.all basic games like temple run oz and fruit ninja working ok.display is decent and the nokia modified android is surprisingly fast.only thing i feel missing is home screen functionality.i havent tried any heavy gaming yet..rear camera is decent in normal lighting.secondary camera is also ok..overall for rs 10.5k its a good buy for normal usage...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awsome one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was using more than 15 Days. Simple say na It's nice platform of nokia, They are well researched and did the X platform&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NO WHATSAPP :(&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;cannot update whatsapp, so its not working :(&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;google play store will not work, we've to depend on '1mobile store'&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excelent 1&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;as compare to other smart phones nokia xl has a great battery backup as well as the screen size given on this is awesome the features are excelent within the price range. its nice 1 to go with the quality of nokia as well as excelent features, just1 thing i find less is the primary camera should have been more powerfull.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;not good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazon service  is not good they provide defective material to customer. Before 2 days I purchased  Nokia XL from  amazon.in but camera flash not working and I am trying to contact them but I don't get any customer care number on their  site. In Comprising other online shopping website given there customer care number.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Go go for Nokia XL&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The experience with Nokia earlier was that when it falls , it breaks down in 3 pieces and they can be assembled back in less than 30 sec.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wanted to move in branded of repute for the smart phone.. This was priced very well and then EMI based instant process of mere 900 or so was too compelling to take immediate decision&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lastly the comfort of Nokia Service . The best one they have in Ameerpet, Hyderabad. This Nokia XL was bought on the day of launch. So it came with Swedish one.. One request the Service Centre person also transferred the data&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That was the best joy.. One feels heavy .. the kids freak out in the game.. I just use for SMS and checking the FB and Email.. All those fancy Aps scare me. Go for Nokia XL.. Do remember buy the cover for a mere Rs 500 or so from the Amazon.. Fits in snugly.  That one is from Hong Kong..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Most surprising was the web site that Amazon would take 3 days delivery. Next day it was there in before noon with no extra charges for courier. Wow !!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_0 " title="2.8 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2.8 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00IXD0B8W</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia XL (Black, Dual SIM)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool phone at this price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When hunting for a new mobile phone, being biased by flood of android based phones in market, in beginning I was bit skeptical about Windows OS. But its just a matter of a couple of days of hands on it, I found it is better than my existing android phone. No hangs, no delays, utter smooth operation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;People said that there are few apps for Windows, I found that there are lot of options for normal users. May be for app freaks, they may be less!&lt;br&gt;For someone who is addicted to social media apps like facebook, this is the best phone. Facebook is deeply integrated in the OS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Touch is near perfect. Performance is superb which I judged by playing Asphalt 5 game on the device, it runs as charm with full details on! I liked the "Kid's Corner" feature, very useful when you have kids around.&lt;br&gt;Build quality is very good, form factor and screen size are optimum. Feels good to hold in hands. Offline maps feature is decent however you may not find it as informative as google maps.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Some features may be lacking (like easy interface for enabling, data networks, WiFi, Bluetooth and Airplane mode), but then there is widget for that. It would be better if this widget comes pre-installed in the OS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Sound is quite good. Creating and managing playlists is a pain. I am unable to figure out a clean way of doing it yet. But once done that should not bother any user regularly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call quality, voice clarity etc are very good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall a very good phone in this price range. Of course quite a good bargain when bought from Amazon as compared to other online stores as well as retailers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Goo phone in 6800&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all thanks to Amazon, for coming in India and giving great service.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. I bought this handset in 6800 with 10% axis bank cash back.&lt;br&gt;2. Technical specs, awesome.&lt;br&gt;3. Camera picture quality very good.&lt;br&gt;4. No lag, No hang..Awesome virus free user interface.&lt;br&gt;5. I was a samsung galaxy S advance user, and simply speaking..samsung is rubbish infront of this phone.&lt;br&gt;6. Touch is amazing.&lt;br&gt;7. Battery Life is very Good.&lt;br&gt;8. OS is user friendly.&lt;br&gt;9. Weight is Ok.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dont think much, Go for it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Happy Diwali.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;totally paisa vasool phone!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The price for which I've bought this phone is less than Rs.6800. And, trust me, I'm loving keeping this phone as my secondary phone. The touch response is awesome, switching app is even smoother, using a windows OS is totally different than the Android as I'm using Nexus 4, and I'm loving using this new OS in such a nice phone in this price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now coming on to the services of amazon.in&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have always considered that flipkart has the best services, may it be refunding process, replacement process, cancellation process or delivery time. But this time, amazon.in has played its part after stepping into the world of competition in Indian market. Trust me I'm amazed the way they have started their website by such low prices for almost every product. Their own courier facility is even better than Flipkart that anyone can rely on it without keeping any followup. I must say that other leading websites like Flipkart and Ebay must start thinking upon their new rival now as its gonna be the best in few time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wish you guys all the very best! Kudos!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Fantastic phone at budget price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Smooth and best interface..&lt;br&gt;512 MB RAM feels very low but you never notice it..&lt;br&gt;8GB internal memory (you get 5+ GB free) - no other device offers so much in this price range..&lt;br&gt;look and feel - wow!! (windows 8 beats android and iOS comprehensively in this department)&lt;br&gt;touch - brilliant!!&lt;br&gt;build quality - it is a Nokia phone.. you know what they are like..&lt;br&gt;video clarity - very good&lt;br&gt;camera - best in this range (7000 - 10000)..&lt;br&gt;dimensions perfectly suit my hands..&lt;br&gt;been using it for about a month and so far absolutely no complaints..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;negatives: no front camera, flash, apps and games are limited..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bottomline: If you can live without front camera, this is the best phone to buy within Rs. 10k budget!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Though i purchased this before amazon.in was live. I have been using this phone for last 3 months and the experience so far has been really good.&lt;br&gt;The office integration works like a charm. Windows OS is really fast. Looks like nokia has finally got things right with lumia series&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best mobile under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am quite an old fashioned person when it comes to electronic gazettes. I was never fascinated by smartphones, tablets and other touch screen devices and was very happy with my simple basic mobile. It was only accidentally that i gave it a thought to go for a smartphone after i lost my mobile and my techno-savvy friend advised me to go for this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transition from a simplest basic mobile to the Smartphone could never be more easier, thanks to Nokia Lumia 520 and Windows 8.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do not know much technical bits to appraise this mobile, but i can state many of its advantages from a layman's angle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Excellent build quality- I dropped it on a cement road from my bicycle to find it in three pieces. But nothing was damaged.&lt;br&gt;2. For it's primary usage as a phone- Excellent voice quality, speaker phone is at its best. Signal reception is also very good. SMS Interface is very different than regular basic phones and i found it to be quite innovative.&lt;br&gt;3. Screen size of 4' is quite appropriate. It fits in your palm well and goes in the packet very nicely.&lt;br&gt;4. Display quality is excellent. It may not have the best viewing angle though, but for a single viewer, you get the best.&lt;br&gt;5. Windows 8 feels amazing. Very user friendly, desktop kind of interface and positioning of apps could not be more simple.&lt;br&gt;6. It will not be wise to ignore Windows phones thinking that it does not have enough apps. You would find apps for almost all of your needs.&lt;br&gt;7. The most beautiful feature i found is the Kid's Corner. Here, you can create different profile for your kid. And you will be at peace, while your child is trying her hands at your mobile. With this profile, your child can not make any outgoing calls or can not mend with your important files in the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though, there are some limitations as below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. There is no front camera, but what more can you expect in a budget phone.&lt;br&gt;2. No radio. But for me, it doesn't matter. I do have best radio apps downloaded in my phone.&lt;br&gt;3. There is no key to search within mobile, instead there is a key that takes you to the web search engine- Bing. I can't justify a separate key only to search over web.&lt;br&gt;4. Lack of Dual SIM. Don't understand why Nokia does not have this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, i found this to be the best smartphone with a budget below 10K. Go for it even if your budget is more than it. It is worth for each and every paisa!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best starter smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The hardware and the os are top notch and I am really loving the purchase for the price it is being offered.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;dissat,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got that mobile and when I open box I found that charger is not working, cant xpect from amazon . Worst service, also I need to go to nokia care to replace my charger.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Lumia 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased Lumia 520 handset @ Oct 22nd 2013. After using 4 months Power on/off button not working.......... Something bad about Nokia&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;For 7.5k good phone and no lag- great useability and I love Here drive and Nokia music. Good integration of all the social app.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LO8Y</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;AWESOME&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using this phone for past 3 months, Till now I have no complaints at all. For this price u wont get any other better phone. I'l summarize some cons most users would feel.&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;* No LED notification light&lt;br&gt;* No flash&lt;br&gt;* No secondary camera&lt;br&gt;* No WiFi direct (Could be available on win 8.1 update)&lt;br&gt;* Battery backup is not great (maximum 2 days on average use)&lt;br&gt;* No backlignt on capacitive buttons but there is haptic feedback&lt;br&gt;* Need an SD card for app installation from PC ( There has been some rumors that only class 6 or more SD cards will be supported after 8.1 update)&lt;br&gt;* Readability under sunlight is not great, U'l find it hard under direct sunlight&lt;br&gt;* No file explorer app available&lt;br&gt;* Limited Bluetooth functionality.&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;* Super awesome touch response&lt;br&gt;* Vibrant display&lt;br&gt;* Awesome performance&lt;br&gt;* Zero lag&lt;br&gt;* Plenty of apps are available&lt;br&gt;* Awesome camera and associated apps&lt;br&gt;* Super awesome call quality&lt;br&gt;* Elegant design&lt;br&gt;* Almost all games are supported, thanks to 1 GB RAM&lt;br&gt;* Windows 8.1 update would support file explorers, notification panel and more&lt;br&gt;* Cortana is awesome (Except for battery drain) though its gonna be available in US only for some time.&lt;br&gt;* Windows 8.1 Developer preview(Unofficial windows 8.1 update, can contain bugs, update voids your warranty) is available for every one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a good phone and with lot of good features. It is good to use windows . touch is quite good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Full Value Of Money by Nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The Very Good Phone By Nokia. Very Impressive Look and also nice Quality. RAM is also good amount in this Price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It has one major problem with mail sending.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Whiile replying to any mail you can not attach file except pictures. Mean u can not attach word, excel, text etc.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Pretty good mobile in this price range!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent windows phone in this range. Awesome phone. 1gb ram simply powerful phone. Very sleek and glossy smoothy finish. simply superb&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;lovable mobile phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;pros: compact and pocketable, wonderful touch screen, user interface is easy, very fresh and lively than android phones, not many applications to boast of, but all essential apps are there, nokia music is free for 3 months and you will get some good music from the nokia store, but the music file format is a little different than the usual MP3, economical price, easy connectivity, internet experience is fairly good and so is the gaming. Camera is good under day light and the music experience is great.&lt;br&gt;cons: feel a little flimsy without a protective cover, no front camera and no flash for the primary camera, some problems with managing the files, especially the music files.&lt;br&gt;overall, a great buy for me as I like it very much, right now.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good windows phome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good windows phone....nokia music store and other apps are also very good... Very handy...camera somewhat average...battery backup normal...at last very good service by Amazon india&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;feeling happy with amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good product and  superb delevry frm amazon&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;good camera,sound,n internal memory 4gb&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;got this @ best price 8999&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;very happy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;525&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;awesome phone for a range of 10k&lt;br&gt;apps arent much but still increasing in in WP8&lt;br&gt;doesnt lag even a bit&lt;br&gt;worth the investment&lt;br&gt;better than 520 anyday&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Finally a clutter breaker!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First things first...&lt;br&gt;-Have been locked to Symbian (&amp;amp; Nokia N8) since my tryst with mobility began and my brush with Android has been limited to Micromax Funbook.&lt;br&gt;-I am not an avid social net-worker nor do i use mobile email facility to use&lt;br&gt;-Have a  soft-corner for Nokia brand&lt;br&gt;-Was looking for an ideal gift for sub 10000 for s/o who needed to be initiated to the world of 'present day' technology &amp;amp; also to expect a WOW-y expression from the recipient&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After weighing various options (limited to Sony &amp;amp; Nokia as was not at all interested to add to the ubiquitous Samsung population) zeroed in on lumia brand; with lumia 520 &amp;amp; 525 making the grade. Superior battery &amp;amp; memory tilted the scale in 525s BLACK favour. (I am glad it did as I feel so happy to watch my li'l ones aiding their 'action heroes' negotiate challenges thrown at them with ease &amp;amp; definitely without hiccups.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reasons for buying Lumia 525 Black:&lt;br&gt;- Found windows to be non-intrusive. I say this because I have heard several of my colleagues complaining about Google's penchant for collating/culling infomation from various sources viz emails, facebook etc &amp;amp; putting it right there in your contacts without knowing whether the bonafide owner really finds this useful.&lt;br&gt;- Decent looking, elegant (not eye catching), NOT FLASHY (no chrome plating or silver borders here), silent worker.&lt;br&gt;- Had been a great fan of Nokia's DRIVE, NOKIA Music &amp;amp; NOKIA Maps. As an avid runner &amp;amp; driving entusiast, mapping my speed at different terrains &amp;amp; finding routes have been greatly eased since I owned an N8.  My son is hooked to NOKIA maps too.&lt;br&gt;- Looked like a perfect gift for a person uninitiated to the ever expanding technological  world of  mobility. (I was not disappointed at all)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Experience post buying:&lt;br&gt;- No issues with Windows OS. Albeit, we find it more intuitive, smooth, hiccup free &amp;amp; simple.&lt;br&gt;- Completely satisfied.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One aspect which every buyer of the phone should know before-hand which I was unaware of:&lt;br&gt;The ALARM function of the phone works only with phone in ON condition. I found out after having missed my running schedule once. Now its almost a fortnight since the phone found its way into our lives, we have made peace with this aspect although we do miss the feature as there are very bright chances that unwarranted phone calls jolts u out of sleep in the middle of the night. (We had the habit of switching off our mobiles before closing for the day).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Final word...&lt;br&gt;Health conscious people looking for sub 10000 phones, having passion for the outdoors, wanting to break the clutter &amp;amp; not apprehensive of embracing a new platform can readily take the plunge. The journey would be joyful &amp;amp; you will surely have lots of fun &amp;amp; pleasant surprises along the way.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So...&lt;br&gt;Readers should now know who the recipient of this gift was...&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="3.9 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.9 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00HRUQ2L2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 525 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Just a few clarifications&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;People complaining about this being a waste of money.&lt;br&gt;Firstly the price was high at the time of launch. That is the case with every new product.&lt;br&gt;Now it has been priced reasonably.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Few reasons the price is higher that Lumia 720:&lt;br&gt;â€¢Full HD (1080p) video recording on Lumia 625 as opposed to HD (720p) on Lumia 720.&lt;br&gt;â€¢PureMotion screen with 60Hz refresh rate (found otherwise only on the 920,925 and 1020). (It does lack ClearBlack display though. And also Glance Screen feature isn't supported.)&lt;br&gt;â€¢Nokia Music subscription is for 6 months with Lumia 625 and 3 months on Lumia 720.&lt;br&gt;â€¢Lumia 625 is 4G ready, Lumia 720 supports only 3.5G at the most.&lt;br&gt;â€¢Lumia 625 has a faster processor (1.2ghz dual-core) than Lumia 720 (1ghz dual-core). This results in smoother overall performance.&lt;br&gt;â€¢Lumia 625 comes with Nokia Amber update pre-installed and BlueTooth 4.0 pre-enabled.&lt;br&gt;â€¢(Most obvious point) the screen on Lumia 625 is larger than that on Lumia 720.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And yes, Lumia 625 has FM radio. Some people have wrong info.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yes, the Lumia 720 has better cameras and supports wireless charging, but you need to understand that a product can only provide you so much in the price you pay for it. And no product is perfect. There are always some people who may not like the product. But at least please don't misguide others.&lt;br&gt;So next time, before cursing anything and questioning some company's commitment, please do your research properly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Love this phone.. Shahrukh loves them and so do I&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing phone by Nokia... Premium look... Big screen and strong... Will not break easily like other smartphones such as samsung and Micromax.....windows live tiles are awesome and fast... Plus not virus issues like Android...nokia has best camera&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Why Windows Phone &amp;amp; Why Lumia 625&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My friends are having Nexus4, Nexus 5, S4, Note2, Samsung Grand Duo... I am the only person who used Samsung Omnia w for last 2 years. Once I broke its display twice I am forced to replace my mobile. I had a huge debate with almost all of my friends to choose android.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The reason I stick with Windows phone is.. It does what I ask for. Metro UI responds quick and charm. It never hangs. It never slows down after few months of usage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I had to face two big questions with my friends...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;one is.. android gives customization:  Yes. Once you customize with different mods, upgrades to your handset. You can feel heating, lag in ui and ofcourse it is boring.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;second., android has huge number of apps: Yes. Windows store has 150,000 apps and only morons will install more.. more .. more apps. all popular apps in ios,android are also available in window. I saw facebook messenger app.. which works very good. skype, teamviewer, bulk sms, one note (which is amazing), office (excel improved a lot and ui is way way better now).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally., Its about which device I should choose.&lt;br&gt;I have a personal policy of.. Never spend more than 16000 for a handset.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have a track of record like.,&lt;br&gt;dropped mobile more than 20-25 times a year.&lt;br&gt;Had my mobile bitten by my lab puppy&lt;br&gt;Had throwed and smashed on wall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So, I dont want to risk my money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I watch videos much in mobile. So I needed a 5inch screen.&lt;br&gt;I want to read Tamil text (Windows 8 supports Tamil reading on mobile).&lt;br&gt;I want to have gorilla glass to have good quality screen&lt;br&gt;I want expandable mem.. (most devices does it).. as i take lots of pics and videos&lt;br&gt;It fits in my budget&lt;br&gt;It is most recent model in lumia family in this range.&lt;br&gt;I saw many reviews on youtube with gaming ( i wont play much) to show its 512mb ram's stunning performance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I recommend it to everybody who is spending money below 10K in cheap android. &amp;amp; also buying android for no reason.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;13000 is a very good cost for this mobile and you will enjoy using window phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone..love the large screen&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Just love this phone with large screen and live window tiles...I highly recommend anyone considering a smartphone to buy this one...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;An average phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I've been an iOS fan all my life. Decided to shift to windows phone for a change.&lt;br&gt;Pros&lt;br&gt;Very responsive touch, no lag like android.&lt;br&gt;Good screen much better than HD screens of xolo and micromax in my opinion.&lt;br&gt;Good battery life.&lt;br&gt;No heating problems.&lt;br&gt;HD Video.&lt;br&gt;Good Camera.&lt;br&gt;Very big screen.&lt;br&gt;Build quality far superior to any android phone in that range be it samsung or xperia or lenovo or micromax. The phone is solid and built like a tank.&lt;br&gt;Cons&lt;br&gt;Really poor ecosystem. Very few apps are available. Those available are too bad vis-a-vis android or iOS.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verdict&lt;br&gt;Good phone for money, solid built, nice colours and decent camera. If you are like me and want a smart phone with office suite, facebook and twitter little bit of gaming look no further.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ps. After 12 hours of use the phone just died on me. The touch became unresponsive. Returned it free of cost and got a replacement lumia. It runs just fine.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best of nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Realty its a gud mobile guys, for range of 13000 rupees and the working speed us also great, its Os is quit complicated, but better than android, and( Samsung).box it doesn't hang much&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At the time I have booked my mobile in amazon it is just only 13300 with in two days I got mobile on my hand , nice mobile some people are saying there is hanging problem in nokia Lumia 625  I think they wont close their application properly after the use..&lt;br&gt;nice choice for the moneyðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Most Trusted Online Store AMAZON&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am quote satisfied with Nokia Lumia 625. Thank you very much Amazon for providing me such a nice phone at such a low rate&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Loving now windows phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good battery back up, screen clarity, gorilla glass, smooth touch and very good camera with auto focus. . . .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The way its mentioned.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am looking for Nokia Lumia 625 on various stores, but due to clean billing and good price differentiation force me to buy from amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.1 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.1 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00EOPJEYK</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 625 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb Phablet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered this mobile and its reaches within 4 days of order, very nice phablet but price is more.&lt;br&gt;so i suggest it, but below at 17,000/- rs.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Super Mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have buy this mobile from Amazon . I got a seal pack packet without any defect and i like it so much.really it is good mobile.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I am so happy to buy it from amazon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Super Phone by Nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing service by Amazon and Super phone by Nokia just loved it Resolution, Smooth Touch, Gaming, Battery, AWESOME.. LOVED IT.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Battery Backup, Very smooth functionalities all games are working good. But some games make phone hot in upper section&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Dream Phablet for Windows Lovers&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia Lumia 1320, a 6 inch midrange phablet with a 720P Display. Its bigger brother,Nokia 1520 has a 1080P display and costs higher.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Built Quality and Display ##&lt;br&gt;The built quality of the device is quite good - poly carbonate plastic. Since this is huge device,there is a chance for this device to slip out of your hand as the back panel lacks grip.&lt;br&gt;720P - 720 x 1280 pixels, 6.0 inches (~245 ppi pixel density)&lt;br&gt;The display isnt exactly a stunner,but not bad.The viewing angles of this display are great.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Processor,GPU and Ram ##&lt;br&gt;Dual-core 1.7 GHz Qualcomm Snapdragon S4 , Adreno 305 GPU and 1 GB Ram. - Not the most powerful combination,but more than good enough to run Windows 8 UI without any lags.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Camera ##&lt;br&gt;Nokia opted to cut costs by opting for a 5MP shooter which performs quite well outdoors with good light. Dont expect great camera performance you often see on many other Nokia Lumia high end version.Images are good enough for your social networking sharing needs though. The front camera is a VGA one,which is very grainy and noisy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The camera app included is the default one seen in Windows,however you can download the powerful Nokia Camera App from the store.It has the ability to tweak manual settings like shutter speed, ISO, white balance, focus mode and exposure.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Battery ## [ Non - Removable ]&lt;br&gt;Nokia made the right decision to ship this with a huge battery.The 3,400mAh battery can very easily last more than a day with moderate use.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Storage ##&lt;br&gt;8GB Internal,but there is a microsd card slot supporting up to 64GB.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Verdict ##&lt;br&gt;Overall a good Nokia Phablet but considering the specs it comes with,this is priced a little high.I feel like they should have priced this around 17K. If you are a windows lover ,looking for a Windows Phablet with a huge screen and a huge battery,look no where else,this is the right device. But If you are an Android user,then you can find devices with better internals and camera for the price though.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Enjoying it!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got exactly what I needed!  A big screen, affordable windows phone!  Watching movies, youtube videos is great fun now.  I am also more at ease reading mails and editing office documents, although I do agree that microsoft did not bother to take advantage of the big screen like other android phones have.  Battery lasts for more than two days for me, with moderate usage.  I have been using this phone for the last 2 weeks and I should say I am very happy with the product!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Lumia Phablet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought it from another vendor not from Amazon.in&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regarding the Phablet-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simple, not to many controls like Android. Don't consider this as a complaint: I was really fed up of managing a small device with too many controls and feels super slow once the applications are loaded. So used to reset it every 6 months! Can't comment on performance of Lumia, but from my known acquaintances, Windows phone does not have such problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;UI is fresh and easy to navigate. Not a palm top computer like any Samsung Note.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;No theme concept in Lumia other than coloring. Trendy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Touch is responsive, at least 10% better than Android.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Widgets are just icons to the actual control page &amp;lt; this actually not a good idea :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MISSING my HTC Desire optical track ball! ... was really an added advantage while typing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speaker ear piece hole just on the edge, bit uncomfortable for long duration calls. Voice clarity is natural and brilliant! Volume is little lower side.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For me it is a Phone, ebook reader, a hand held device with better usability.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battery. Simply awesome! lasting for 2-3 days with medium usage. Only Edge connection checked so far. Because it is enough for my need. Quite sure on HSDPA networks this will last anything more than 1.5 days! 0 - 100% charging in 2.5hrs!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Screen display: IMO, what else we could expect from such a small device. It is HD display, 245ppi! Not able to identify any pixels.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera: If somebody wants to replace their Handy Cam or DSLR, this is not for them. But enough for occasional scene capture.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Design: slim. A case is recommend for more grip, because it is a 6" phone. Plastic looks bit cheap quality, but it is Nokia!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Storage: this is important. Out of 8GB internal memory 2.5 already allocated for OS! ... and 1.5 for other applications, so totally it was close to 4GB remaining when I got the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Music: This is another incredible feature in Lumia 1320. Just one word, awesome! Use a Sony or Sennheiser headphone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Data: Supports Edge and HSDPA+, but not LTA.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;amazing phone, go for it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Love the phone for its neat interface n very satisfying battery life. For all people complaining about lesser apps on windows, let me tell you that there are enough apps to make your life easy. However, I can hardly wait for the 8.1 release, the reviews are just inspiring!! Btw I was using an android earlier and i'm just loving this phone for its fluid interface.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;features may not be that attractive.... but nokia is nokia...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought it from amazon for 18k... All and all its a good phone..... Battery life is just awesome.... Camera, though 5 MP only, clicks very decent photos...... Everything is good except for a few things like:&lt;br&gt;it sometimes gets noticably heated while charging.&lt;br&gt;Worst thing is that it has no lights on its lower buttons...&lt;br&gt;A bit heavy... But it actually gives a gud feel to me...!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;u wont be disappointed if u buy it...!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NIce smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;For windows lover this is the best phone in affordable price you can have. So go ahead and make it yours&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.0 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.0 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00GAPPY0A</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 1320 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Best mobile under 10K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am quite an old fashioned person when it comes to electronic gazettes. I was never fascinated by smartphones, tablets and other touch screen devices and was very happy with my simple basic mobile. It was only accidentally that i gave it a thought to go for a smartphone after i lost my mobile and my techno-savvy friend advised me to go for this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The transition from a simplest basic mobile to the Smartphone could never be more easier, thanks to Nokia Lumia 520 and Windows 8.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I do not know much technical bits to appraise this mobile, but i can state many of its advantages from a layman's angle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Excellent build quality- I dropped it on a cement road from my bicycle to find it in three pieces. But nothing was damaged.&lt;br&gt;2. For it's primary usage as a phone- Excellent voice quality, speaker phone is at its best. Signal reception is also very good. SMS Interface is very different than regular basic phones and i found it to be quite innovative.&lt;br&gt;3. Screen size of 4' is quite appropriate. It fits in your palm well and goes in the packet very nicely.&lt;br&gt;4. Display quality is excellent. It may not have the best viewing angle though, but for a single viewer, you get the best.&lt;br&gt;5. Windows 8 feels amazing. Very user friendly, desktop kind of interface and positioning of apps could not be more simple.&lt;br&gt;6. It will not be wise to ignore Windows phones thinking that it does not have enough apps. You would find apps for almost all of your needs.&lt;br&gt;7. The most beautiful feature i found is the Kid's Corner. Here, you can create different profile for your kid. And you will be at peace, while your child is trying her hands at your mobile. With this profile, your child can not make any outgoing calls or can not mend with your important files in the phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Though, there are some limitations as below.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. There is no front camera, but what more can you expect in a budget phone.&lt;br&gt;2. No radio. But for me, it doesn't matter. I do have best radio apps downloaded in my phone.&lt;br&gt;3. There is no key to search within mobile, instead there is a key that takes you to the web search engine- Bing. I can't justify a separate key only to search over web.&lt;br&gt;4. Lack of Dual SIM. Don't understand why Nokia does not have this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall, i found this to be the best smartphone with a budget below 10K. Go for it even if your budget is more than it. It is worth for each and every paisa!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good product......terrible service providers (Yehbazaar &amp;amp; Amazon.in)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered a Cyan(blue) mobile...... Yehbazaar sent me a white one (cheaper than cyan) and to my extreme surprise, abused my sensibilities on the phone. After proving the mistake......there was no apology or remorse either from Amazon nor Yehbazaar. Infact the service provider sent a new invoice(for white) telling me I should not have opened the package. Amazon did not even have the decency to try and correct the situation and till date I have received no communication from them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phone meanwhile is the only saving grace in this whole murky and disgusting episode. Avoid Amazon, but buy Nokia!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome and bowsome~!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;GREAT PHONE:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Nokia Lumia 520 i bought from amazon is unbeatable! the value, cost and performances are equally admirable!&lt;br&gt;And i really like the service offered by amazon, i mean they are reliable and trustworthy in safe-guard and delivery of products.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;pros:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Nokia inbuilt map (HERE map) &amp;amp; inbuilt driving app(HERE drive) are amazing gifts. AKA wherever you drive or travel to, the GPS navigation in HERE drive app will show you exact route, location, direction, distance, speed and everything!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Touch, sensitivity and processing speed are shockingly fast and lucid as compare to many smart phones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. As Nokia phones are famous for its durability and rock-solid hardware quality, Nokia Lumia 520 is tough!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Availability of compatible MS Office is bonus for office person.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Nokia music store is bust for music lovers, listen anything and download anytime!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;6. Nokia smart cam, panorama view, creative studio, cinemagraph are impressive tools for your picture editing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;7. Web integration &amp;amp; User interface is also remarkably simple and clean!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;cons:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Smart phones consumes more battery but its durability is not so great as i expect form Nokia.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Non-availability of Flash might irked if you want to take picture in less/no light area!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. App availability is not so great as compare to Android phones but everything is upto mark!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Non-availability of button light might lead your friend's Android phone one step smarter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Audio customization and ear-phone set are quite annoying!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;P.S : Since this is a economical budget phone! we can't be expecting more than what we deserve. what i experienced from Nokia Lumia 520, i'm incredibly satisfied with features, price and everything!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;HOPE THIS WILL HELP YOU&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best budjeted smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Incredible 4 inch mobile mobile at this rsnge.&lt;br&gt;camera quality superb just adjust it to night mode , you can connect it to your pc directly for mass storage no need of zune software.&lt;br&gt;And amazon service te best&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;buy this folks!!!!!!! even if your budget is more than this!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;8gb internal memory!!!more than that of any of the samsungs till 18k! Cute tiles, superb touchscreen, lots of hd wp games, office, skydrive and lots more. This is the phone which is actualy SMART.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its okeyish&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bought it for my dad. Touch works smoothly and is really fast but it hangs a lot and also as it is windows not much cool apps as in android. Better go for android.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good and easy to use&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this is somewhat lighter than previous lumia 520. and yeah battery backup is very worst. so anyone who is interested in windows and fed up with android its a best option&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Unhappy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile phone turns off automatically. I didn't wanted to return it, according to me returning a product is a hassle. I'm dealing with it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good basic smart phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like this phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera quality is good, although flash is not there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phone navigation is good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One limitation is that there is no file browser.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So far, the phone never hung. But micro SIM is issue. Actually I spoilt my mini SIM, when it was tried to as as micro-sim.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;go 4 it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After updating my Lumia to 8.1, it seems better than android, loving it. Top games like asphalt, real steel works flawlessly. The new tile mechanism is cool in 8.1&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.4 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.4 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CE2LUKQ</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Lumia 520 (Cyan)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Still Not up to the mark!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice finish and weightless! But you can connect to wifi only with simple infrastructure. After using Micromax, I feel this one is very slow! For everything to open it takes 2 seconds. It tests my patience everytime :-/&lt;br&gt;You can buy better featured mobiles in Micromax at the same price! Won't recommend this for Teens! :-)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;average quality phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I think, Nokia will never improve. This S40 OS phone, which comes with the old S40 OS says it. The basic OS has not been improved and all the change we can see is in some applications.&lt;br&gt;I am a big QWERTY lover and i am not willing to purchase a Blackberry phone. So, this was my only option. Totally disappointed by experiencing the old OS once again.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone for the price.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very pleased with the phone and great service from amazon again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the price range upto Rs 4800 this is one of the few nokia devices that has wifi! The feedback from the qwerty keypad is good. The plastic quality could be improved, although the build feels very sturdy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro's&lt;br&gt;wifi&lt;br&gt;dual sim&lt;br&gt;3g&lt;br&gt;qwerty keypad&lt;br&gt;sturdy build quality&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Con's&lt;br&gt;poor plastic quality&lt;br&gt;poor camera&lt;br&gt;UI lags a bit&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good basic phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Basic Phone with whatsapp and Nokia browser.This is a best phone if you requirements in messaging,calling.&lt;br&gt;not supporting 3G so speed will b slow.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;5/5&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone and great services by amazon.. love amazon.. excellent stuff&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would refer to all my frnds&lt;br&gt;Awesome&lt;br&gt;Great&lt;br&gt;Would come back for more&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice set!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Well, its a good phone. Got it for my dad .Certainly, he is happy. So I give the product 5stars. Amazing service by amazon . Pleasure shopping here. Keep up the good work.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia 201 is very nice one to use  , but its audio quality and loudness is very bad. So don't buy if you want to hear music.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A Functional Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone serves all the basic purposes. Though it has several good features such as Whatsapp and other great apps but the operation is very slow.&lt;br&gt;Battery backup is poor and even normal use does not give more than 36 hours of stand by.&lt;br&gt;My suggestion will to add a few thousand more and buy Moto E.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good budget phone. So, you can make a better choice to buy it. It supports the main applications in trend etc.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;wonderful phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;such a wonderful phone really I like it awesome functions the keypad is good to type nokia has really introduce some good phones&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00DQ4D2N4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia Asha 210 (Dual SIM, Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Quick dispatch, same as described.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Quick dispatch, same as described.&lt;br&gt;Very pleased with the order. I always order from Amazon.in and love it. 5 stars.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased this for my mom. She liked her new mobile as it weighs less and easy to use. Job done.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;the product had software issues.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;from the day i got the product it was frequently showing insert sim on its display, it got solved after doing a software change from nokia care.Never expected any issues on a fresh product, but faced issue.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excelent Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got this for my mom on her birthday .&lt;br&gt;Its very handy and light weight product having good product Quality .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Watsapp stopped working within 2 months since it doesnt allow to update to next version and annoying pop ups&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this mobile just because it supported Watsapp and Facebook app in it. But the watsapp stopped working since am not able to update it to next version.&lt;br&gt;The most annoying thing with this mobile is that it keeps popping to select the preferred network  for data even though i dont intend to  use internet. am ok if it pops twice or thrice a day.. but this rubbish mobile constantly pops it every now and then i unlock the mobile..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nokia 206 is a very good phone.I bought a white one but now i am worried about keeping it clean.&lt;br&gt;screen is good,works fast enough. Battery supplied is of 1200 Mah. CameraCamera takes clean picture(very good considering it's 1.3mp sensor.&lt;br&gt;It has a lot of app and games installed. Many of them are useless to me,sadly i cannot uninstall them.&lt;br&gt;Overall, very good buy at this price,big screen,looks good in your hand.It has got whats app too.&lt;br&gt;Speaker is loud and clear.Sound through earpiece is also clear and audible.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;you will be satisified with the features considering the budget,&lt;br&gt;Pros:battery, big screen, whatsapp,easy to handle,voice clarity&lt;br&gt;Cons: volume keys&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my second phone (i lost the 1st one) and i still love this one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Stylish design&lt;br&gt;2. Simple to use.&lt;br&gt;3. Browsing can be done&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good experience from amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good headset my relatives are really happy with the headset. But sc card should also be provided with the phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Dependable Nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good compact phone with basic required features. It has pre-installed social media softwares.  My dad is loving this gift. Thanks&lt;br&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00BJDSJTG</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia 206 (Dual SIM, White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;cheater not refund ed my money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon is cheater I ordered phone from amzon 3 times I received hardware issue I realised handeset back to amzon its been 20 days I&lt;br&gt;Have not got my amount back 0f 7024&lt;br&gt;Frnds just wanted share beware shopping from&lt;br&gt;Amzon .your money is not safe or you might received defective product&lt;br&gt;I am launching an FIR against amzon&lt;br&gt;Rest things police will do.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Distictively Nokia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Kept the Nokia standard in all areas. Style, performance and friendliness. Feature packed ,gives you a feeling of being sophisticated and durable.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A great investment&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered this phone on April 12th, 2014 at around 10 pm for my mother and it was delivered in a nice, sturdy package on April 13th, 2014 at 12 noon. Firstly, what I'd like to highlight is the utter superiority of the phone when compared to others in the same price range, especially the Android Phones. As you may have seen, Android requires a lot of hardware and due to this, low budget Android phones costing below Rs 10,000/- frequently hang and have a very bad user experience. It's been more than 15 days using this phone and my mother has not complained about any of these, although this may also be a result of the extensive customizations that Nokia / Microsoft has done to this particular flavor of Android. A welcome experience though, has been Fastlane, which shows you everything you need in one place. Call quality is good and the dual sim feature is an added plus, considering that dual sim phones of competitors cost a lot more. And as usual, the touch sensitivity is quite good as well. Lastly, please bear in mind that since this is not "official Google Android", you won't have access to the Google Play Store, but it is possible to use a concept of side loading to install apps from Google Play into this phone (search for this on Youtube). Overall, a great decision to buy the phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia X is ROCK&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone has all the facility which is required to available for a phone. With the given price &amp;amp; Brand name this phone is worth at all for common people who value for there money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Easy contact transfer, easy to handle and all application is user frendly.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;worth price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the price was fair,  cant get cheaper than 6800 for it.  an excellent phone.  only thing i find -ve is that it gets slow once you download a couple of apps&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Sufficient replacement for my Windows Phone 520&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I did not expect too much and I'm surprised. Full setup including Owncloud link to Calendar and Contacts was done in 30 minutes. Mail accounts run, Wi-Fi connect works, and the device can be used as a telephone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hardware looks promising. Stable frame build around the phone. Nice idea to have the bumper directly around the screen. New more square look is nice.&lt;br&gt;Performance is ok, hope it will last the whole lifetime. My other Androids always got slower with time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Not able to buy the Nokia X in Germany a few weeks ago, I decided to buy it in India and let it bring to Germany by a peer. I'm happy that I have done it, it is worth the money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I can't understand the low ratings here. It is a cheap phone with enough resources to do what I expected it would do.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pro:&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Quick enough to browse, mail, and do calls.&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Dual Sim&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Battery capacity with 1500 mAh quite good&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Display resolution with WVGA (800 x 480) is ok&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Allows other App Stores&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Preinstalled apps are removable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Con:&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Color choice is harming my eyes. (the pink)&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Inbox is not remembering show all inbox&lt;br&gt;â€¢ Browser does not allow deleting preset bookmarks and new ones (or Iâ€™m too stupid to find ;o) )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[update 2014-04-23]&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After replacing some of the stock apps like calendar, contacts, browser with others I'm more than happy. This was really easy, just installing them from other markets and deactivate or deinstall the others. Everything works. Still slower than the HTC One, but the phone was 5times more expensive.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;great mobile. features are very good but always due to sending of item by post the handling is very poor.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nokia x&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Product is good,&lt;br&gt;But there is no guarantee or user guide given which is like purchasing ur items from grey market.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good but could be better....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The nokia's entry into the android scenario is definitlely assuring but has to go a long way on the fronts of usability and convenience. The phone build is plastic and the screen clarity is just ok. No lags or glitches but the absense of dedicated google apps could be a turnoff. The calendar fuction and sync could be better. Have been using it for one month, no serious issues till now.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It was a good phone until Moto E was not launched&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I wanted to buy a dual sim branded phone for my dad, I was happy to receive what Nokia offered until Moto E was not launched. I wish I had waited for one more month for Moto E.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If I just forget Moto E then it's really a cool phone to hangout with.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_0 " title="3.0 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.0 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00IKC5HQC</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Nokia X (Dual SIM, Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Phone but do not buy it from the person who sold it on Amazon!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone is great, but I felt cheated, as the phone came used! The pack opened, and I have complained about it, just short of sending it back, to the seller.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon did a great job of it! So I love to buy things from them. Samsung S5 is a good phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Every thing is a charm but sound quality is really a disappointment.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Every thing is a charm but the sound quality is really a disappointment.&lt;br&gt;The phone is loaded with lots of feature and sensors.&lt;br&gt;But the single speaker at back produces noisy and low volume sound with almost no bass.&lt;br&gt;It really annoys one if listening to music&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Slim... Light Weight... Awesome camera quality...&lt;br&gt;People worrying about Exynos Processor.... Jus go for it.... doesnt matter if its not snapdragon 801 , it performs pretty well.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Price is higher than features&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;WHAT IS NEW HERE&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.Sturdy &amp;amp; Stronger&lt;br&gt;Samsung Galaxy S5 comes with dust and water resistant feature that will protect your smartphone from getting damaged from rain, sand and dust. So plan an adventure trip and carry your handy companion along in water or sand without worrying about any damages.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2.Camera&lt;br&gt;Click high quality pictures faster with Samsung Galaxy S5 that boasts Auto &amp;amp; Selective Focus that lets you capture all important movements and main subject without missing on the action. Edit images, record and view HD videos, create a beautiful picture collage and share them instantly with your loved ones in just a click. Its 16.0MP rear camera with functions like Face detection, HDR(rich tone), Virtual tour shoot will help you to do it all. The smart device also offers super-fast 4G and Wi-Fi connectivity for seamless internet browsing and instant data sharing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Smarter Power &amp;amp; Security Management&lt;br&gt;Your smartphone should be smart enough to provide you sufficient battery backup, right? With Samsung Galaxy S5 you donâ€™t have to worry at all as it is actually smart in providing a smarter power management that relatively saves the phoneâ€™s battery life with its â€œPower Saving Modeâ€ and also features an Ultra Power Saving Mode that extends the battery life by switching your smartphoneâ€™s screen to black &amp;amp; white mode and switches off all unnecessary running Apps that consumes more battery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4.Personal Health Tracker&lt;br&gt;Samsung Galaxy S5 will help you to maintain a healthy lifestyle and will keep you fit. With its Gen-X Apps like Heart-rate scanner and fitness tracker this smartphone will smartly help you to keep a constant track of your fitness routines and health conditions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;PROS:&lt;br&gt;a. GREAT MUSIC,&lt;br&gt;b. SCREEN RESOLUTION&lt;br&gt;c. INNOVATIVE FEATURES LIKE HEART BEAT SCANNER,FINGER PRINT SCANNER etc&lt;br&gt;d. CAMERA IS GREAT&lt;br&gt;e. BETTER CONNECTIVITY THAN S4&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CONS:&lt;br&gt;a.PRICE IS HIGHER.&lt;br&gt;b.SAMSUNG NEWS PAGE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good deal&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon Delivery was prompt.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Has issues with the Basic s/w of S5 had to call the Samsung Support team who promptly sent a person at home to change the settings and upgrade s/w&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Over priced&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a nice &amp;amp; beautiful phone but over priced. The price is not justified in comparison of other makes premium phones.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Brilliant.....!!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone.... Excellent screen...  Dont think just go for it....worth every penny... Fun to watch HD movies and games on its beautiful screen...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best phone at good prise&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best phone avilable in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It has all features...&lt;br&gt;best features are-&lt;br&gt;#Water resistance with removable battery..so in future you can buy a extra battery and chamge it ur self&lt;br&gt;#Ultra power saving mode&lt;br&gt;#Full hd amoled dispaly 5.1&lt;br&gt;#Finger print scanner.. which is very fast and accurate&lt;br&gt;#fast autofocus 16mp camera&lt;br&gt;#Samsung services (service centers and resale value) better then other&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Rest all features are avilable&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I never want to buy a costly phone but for its features I purchased. On a very low prise 40k  with 5k  coupen so now I have 2 extra headset and sview flip cover..&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00JB6RT8K</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S5 (Charcoal Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone with good features at this price.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased this phone after research of phones in market. I found it is a good choice after using it for one month. I can get good battery backup after setting inbuilt battery saving function. I got 2 days battery backup for my average use. Screen quality is decent and the sound quality too. I like the quality of  Sound through headphone, it's amazing. No lags in general games like Subway surfers, Temple run2, etc if battery saving is off. Battery saving mode reduces game performance. Overall it's a good choice over Sony xperia M &amp;amp; LG L7 II dual P715. I think it's worth to buy because of Good display, Ram 1GB, Internal memory 8Gb and good performance.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;OK mobile at this price, has some battery related issues&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery issues -  gets switched off, doesn't get charged properly etc.etc. Otherwise Ok performance. Don't buy from Next Online, very poor after sales response.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not a good purchase from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is good but Amazon has DELIVERED A DEFECTIVE PIECE TO ME.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The device heats up and also there is reception problem. The device looses connectivity every now and then.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope that Amazon will call me to address my concern.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please do not buy phones from Amazon!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsungs good phone but&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good phone by samsung in a budget category. Getting 4.3 screen with 1 GB ram is very good combination&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;however&lt;br&gt;the body is made by cheap material, the screen resolution is not good compare to moto g&lt;br&gt;and off course camera quality is average.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone wants budget phone with good configuration, then go for galaxy core.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;poor power storage&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This item working good but dont keep battery power , maximum power 5 hrs thats all then low battery  , this mobile poor power storage&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review - Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features are fine but would have feel happy if they given flip cover with the handset.&lt;br&gt;I would suggest to go with Grand2 instead of this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;warranty certificate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;warranty certificate &amp;amp; packing material list yet not received.operating manual also not received.kindaly send it as soon as possible.so i utilise it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Price in this site is bit high compare to other site&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Price of this product Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 in this site is bit high compare to other site. This should revise by this site.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not Good nor bad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Processing is slow&lt;br&gt;After installing few more app&lt;br&gt;its become slow&lt;br&gt;Camera quality is good....&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget Samsung Device - Not worth the money.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy Core is a budget 1GB ram device from samsung released in June 2013. It was a decent device when it was launched,but now,for the price you can get far better devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Display : 480 x 800 pixels, 4.3 inches ie only 217 ppi. The screen brightness is not that great,which means it is very difficult to see the screen under sunlight. The viewing angles are good.There is also no light sensor which means Auto brightness feature is not there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Processor : Dual-core 1.2 GHz Cortex-A5 processor. This is no powerhouse Good enough for your day to day tasks,but lags behind the quadcore processors coming with similarly priced devices like Canvas Magnus, Turbo Mini,Xolo Q Series, Moto G etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antutu Benchmark : 7470 ( For a comparison to show how low the performance is, Xolo Q700 scores - 13000, Micromax Turbo Mini - 17000 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera : 5 MP , the image quality is not that great. It can't even record 720P HD videos while even many under Rs 8000 devices are able to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating System : Samsung TouchwizUI on top of old Android 4.1 Jellybean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battery : 1800mAh. This is NOT good enough to take you through one day of moderate use (with internet on). Cheaper Xolo Q700 priced at Rs 8500 ships with a 2400mAh one is to be noted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verdict : Galaxy Core is not a value for money device in my opinion, as many other devices coming at this price ships with far better performing components and newer Android version. Buy this only if you want a 'branded' budget device and are ok with the issues it comes with.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard â€“ 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu â€“ 11900+  ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 â€“ 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard â€“ 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu â€“ 11900+ ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 â€“ 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Decent buy...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Not the best smartphone in this price range especially after the launch of moto E but gets the job done...&lt;br&gt;Biggest con : lags a lot&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent Phone /Good Call Volume&lt;br&gt;Samsung S Duos 2 - S7582&lt;br&gt;I Purchased it from other Online Website .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feature Specifications:-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1)Real RAM working in Task Manager :- 717 MB&lt;br&gt;2)ROM:- 4 GB&lt;br&gt;Out of which System Storage :-1.82 Gb (We Can't Use it) , 2.18 Gb Remaining Storage is User Available .&lt;br&gt;3)Dual Core Processor&lt;br&gt;4)Boot time :- 25 Sec only&lt;br&gt;5)Good Battery Backup&lt;br&gt;6)Good Graphics&lt;br&gt;6)Run Temple run 2 &amp;amp; Subway surf without lag&lt;br&gt;7)Support HD Videos.&lt;br&gt;8)Good Camera&lt;br&gt;9)Looks like High end S4 phone&lt;br&gt;10)Android Version :- 4.2.2. Jelly Bean&lt;br&gt;11) Overall Very fast &amp;amp; Excellent Phone&lt;br&gt;My Rating to this phone in 10 K Budget :- 10/10&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very Important Feature :- Very High Earpiece Volume / Call Volume&lt;br&gt;In addition to High call volume , Samsung give a option "Adapt Sound" in Settings&lt;br&gt;which can further increase call volume according to your hearing capability&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed Technical Specifications&lt;br&gt;Internal Storage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SD CARD - Up gradable upto 64 gb&lt;br&gt;Internal Storage : 2.18 GB ---&amp;gt;268 mb used ; 1.9 gb free&lt;br&gt;Available Storage : 1.89 GB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAM&lt;br&gt;Total RAM : 716 MB ; Available Ram : 205 Mb ( 27 %) ; 502 Mb used&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPU Architecture ; ARM Cortex A9 1.20 GHZ&lt;br&gt;GPU : Broadcom VideoCore IV HW&lt;br&gt;Clock Speed ; 312 Mhz -1.20 Mhz ; Core 0 :- 800 MHZ ; Core 1 1200 MHZ&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resoultion : 480 x800&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saurabh Mathur&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Quite satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features n more no. Of apps r supported within a genuine price....dats too gud...except one drawback of less battery backup&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best online service i recieved ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its verey good to receive the order quickly and the product is very satisfactory. Here after i will reccommend amazon to my frnds for the best online shopping&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very well packed. Product as described in the picture.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product reached on time. Well packed. The item was as described on the product page. Working fine. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone nd god price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice phone nd god price,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,i m facing sm prblm with hanging,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,but still is nice phone with white colur and slim madal.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my mobile phone is not working properly.there are so many problems in this set&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I'm not satisfied with this product. Many functions are not working.which create problem to access so many features. I will not purchase anything from ur service&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SAMSUNG GALAXY S DUOS 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing product by samsung.good screen,processor,ram and camera.it runs hassle free specially when you play games like temple run or sub way surf.Excellent features,i fully satisfied.Good battery back up,it last for one and half day if you dont active your wifi,internet etc always,keep your brighteness low during net connet for better backup.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.1 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.1 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;No 3G !&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's a budget phone from Samsung. Good for normal use. However, beware of the fact that it has no 3G. That's kinda annoying.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Dysplay stoped working in a day&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;samsung mobile is gud, but 1st day itself it stopped working..&lt;br&gt;that can be understood.. electronics na, chance of failure..&lt;br&gt;but waiting for cash return from last week.&lt;br&gt;too bad response frm amazon, always telling wil dispatch cheque to soon.......&lt;br&gt;they are nt ready to giv cash as neft, only cheque, so i hav to wait at bank also to make it as cash.....&lt;br&gt;better go to flip,snap&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you are looking for a good budget android smartphone, this is the phone for you. Not going into specifics here (like only 2MP Camera, no 3G) because its a budget smart phone. Well worth its price. As usual, delivered on time and good service&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung star pro&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good services we have get infuture in book other items also. n suggest to my freind also .............thanx.&lt;br&gt;arif shiakh&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This a very wonderful mobile at this price. Only problem is its charger,s Input : should have been 110-240 volt Ac  instead of 150- 300 volt AC. I have already written to to provide me a new  charger with input 110-240 volt ac&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Galaxy Star Pro - A budget android device suitable for basic use&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Galaxy Star Pro is an upgrade to Samsung's Galaxy star. This is a budget device,so as you can expect it comes with a lot of flows.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Features&lt;br&gt;1) Single core,Cortex-A5 1Ghz processor&lt;br&gt;2) 512 MB Ram&lt;br&gt;3) 1500mAh Battery&lt;br&gt;4) 4 inch TFT screen,480x800 resolution.&lt;br&gt;5) Jellybean&lt;br&gt;6) 2 MP camera - Image quality is below average.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Main issues you are gonna face with this phone - Processing Power and Battery.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This device only has Cortex-A5 Single Core processor which is very outdated,and very basic. Dont expect to get good gaming experience with this device at all. Battery,1500mAh one, cant even last one full day of average usage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy this only if you want a branded budget phone. But beware,this thing is gonna hang and lag often while multitasking and opening apps due to a very low end processor it ships with.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Gifting idea&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Haven't used the product yet as its a gift. Great service by amazon now no need to worry about ordering electronics online&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amzon ... you will never get your product on time .. but delay with 4 -5 days .. with the pathetic service of Amazon ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FlipKart is better than this .. wahiyat service provider ....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I LIKE IT BUT....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;THE RAM AND CAMERA DISAPPOINTED ME THOUGH IT IS IN A STARTING RANGE AND I THINK IT TO USE IT AS A REGULAR CALLER PHONE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good. we r satisfied with this product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super mobile from samsung family. this mobile having wonderful features. we are hereby recommend you samsung GT7262 is useful for all&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00G8UGSGG</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Star Pro GT-S7262 (Midnight Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;This is upgraded version previous S Duos Best Android Phone in this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;***First Dont compare this phone with High Range bcos its a upgrade to previous version Galaxy S Duos s7562 *** A budget phone is different from High Range phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;comparison it only with budget phone and the features and price quoted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Features :&lt;br&gt;1. 4*inch TFT Display ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;2. WVGA 480*800 pixels resolution with 16M color depth ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;3. Dual Sim ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;4. Weight 118g ( previous version 120g )&lt;br&gt;5. Dual core 1.2 ghz cortex A9 ( previous version single core 1ghz with cortex A5 )&lt;br&gt;6. Android V4.2 jellybean ( previous Android v4 icecream sandwich )&lt;br&gt;7. Rear camera 5mp cmos and front 0.3p VGA ( same as previous )&lt;br&gt;8. Battery 1500mah ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;9. HD (720) Video Playback &amp;amp; Recording 30fps&lt;br&gt;10. GPU Videocore IV ( previous version its Adreno 200 )&lt;br&gt;11. Ram 768mb ( same as previous )&lt;br&gt;12. 4gb internal and Microsd upto 64 Gb ( Previous its 32 Gb )&lt;br&gt;13. Priced at 10k in Flipkart ( previous version 9k )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally The changes from previous version not much but plays a major part in performance as previous version has many drawbacks in performance :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Processor dual core 1.2 ghz cortex A9&lt;br&gt;2. Video recording 720p&lt;br&gt;3. Os Android v4.2 jellybean&lt;br&gt;4. Videocore IV GPU&lt;br&gt;5. Sdcard Upto 64Gb&lt;br&gt;and some little more&lt;br&gt;6. Ram must have been updated to 1gb but you dont need it since its dual core and you may not worry like before. 768mb is more than sufficient for moderate use with apps and games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;100% you wont have lag and worries compared to its previous version based on updated configurations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the previous version s7562 had many drawbacks in terms of performance , lag , restart , battery down , and many other faults .... This version is just a rectification for those faults and a pretty Moderate update and a price tag that is optimized to capture market when compared to other range at similar configurations ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you search for a mobile at 10k at such configuration and i would suggest to go with Samsung Galaxy sDuos 2 s7582 and you can also update the Android version later.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard â€“ 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu â€“ 11900+  ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 â€“ 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Probably one of the best smartphones below 10k. A must buy if that's anyone's budget. Very Happy with the set.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;What u want everything is here. So dont wait get 1 else not regret.&lt;br&gt;Only crap is d 768 mb ram which could be 1 gb&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i have ordered and got this product with in 48hrs and i am very much happy about product quality and packing quality.&lt;br&gt;i am sure i will suggest my friends to buy from amazon and i am fully satisfied&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;amazon...  amazing.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;quality and service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good quality product dispatched in 2 days. Very good mobile and i bought for my elder brother, He is happy and the price is cheaper than any other website,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;I AM THANKFUL TO AMAZON TO GOT RECEIVED PRODUCT THROUGH AMAZON.HOPE DO IN FUTURE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cheap rate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome product purchased for cheap rate compared to all other online stores. ..&lt;br&gt;This product works very good. I recommend this product and amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I almost searched all the online stores,  But Amazon was the cheapest.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Thanks Amazon for your quick delivery...&lt;br&gt;Now about the product.  Look is decent, Camera captures decent pictures.  Only problem is with Battery backup.  But i installed easy Battery saver, which manages the battery power accross all the apps.  Inbuilt memory seems to be less, but still you can expand by SD card.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Working absolutely fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Using this phone since last 2 months. Working excellent.&lt;br&gt;The phone arrived in time and was well packed in a box.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Cost against perform&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Not worth to spent 50k - not doubling performance then it's last gelexy model but double the cost almost.&lt;br&gt;Wait till cost reduce or find other option&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S5 ..The 'Next Big thing' is here..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all, Samsung Galaxy S5, successor to hugely popular Galaxy S4 comes in two versions. One powered by a Qualcomm Snapdragon 801 chipset and the other powered by Adonis Prime2 (Quad 1.9GHz + Quad 1.3GHz) of which, later version is available in India. If you have doubts check samsung india galaxy s5 page for full specs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both are very powerful chipsets and the benchmarks scores are almost identical. This has 2GB of ram,unlike the Note 3 released earlier which had 3GB of ram. Throw anything at it,whether it be a full HD video or a high end game,everything runs on this device without any issues. One thing which is missing in the version available in India is LTE support. S5 available in India supports HSPA+ 42.2Mbps speeds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;##  Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;The display quality is much better than its predecessor Galaxy S4's display, and there is a small increase in size (5.1 inches from 5 Inches on S4 ). Everything looks sharp and vivid on S5's Super Amoled screen and is said to be one of the best displays available in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The back of the device is now a 'leathery' plastic giving it a less glossy appearance but giving it a better feel when holding. One important feature S5 boasts is that this has an IP67 certification which means that itâ€™s water and dust resistant. Overall the looks of the device resembles older phones in the Samsung Galaxy line up. I think its high time for Samsung to improve the looks of their Galaxy Flagship devices. Look at HTC One M8 for instance,the build quality is top notch and Samsung is nowhere near that type of attractive looks and the built quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Camera&lt;br&gt;Main(Rear) : 16MP (1/2.6â€, Phase Detection AF)&lt;br&gt;Sub (Front) : 2.0MP (1920 x 1080, Wide-angle lens )&lt;br&gt;The camera on the S5 is ,as you can expect is better than the one seen on S4,and offer common software features like HDR (Rich tone), Selective Focus, Virtual Tour Shot. 4K video recording is also supported (5 mins limitation is there ). One other feature Samsung boasts about the camera is the improved,faster auto focus capabilities. S5's camera is without any doubt,one of the best you can get now in an Android smartphone,but when comparing to S4,the difference in quality is not that huge. Low light performance is also not that good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Software&lt;br&gt;This is running the latest version of the Touchwiz UI on top of Android 4.4 Kitkat. As you can expect, the UI and the apps operation are very fast with almost no lags. Since this is a flagship device,this is eligible to get future Android version updates too. It has features like Fingerprint unlocking,Heart rate monitor etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Some Highlights and Misc Features&lt;br&gt;The home button now includes a capacitive fingerprint sensor.&lt;br&gt;A heart rate monitor next to the LED flash.&lt;br&gt;Sensors : Accelerometer, Gyro, Proximity, Compass, Barometer, Hall, RGB ambient light, Gesture, Fingerprint, Heart Rate Sensor&lt;br&gt;Connectivity : USB3.0, BlueTooth 4.0&lt;br&gt;Storage : 16GB User Memory + microSD slot (up to 128GB) .&lt;br&gt;Emergency Mode, Ultra Power Saving Mode, S Health, Quick Connect, Private Mode, Kids Mode.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;## Battery&lt;br&gt;2800mAh one is good enough to get you through one whole day of moderate usage.Ultra Power Saving Mode turns the screen into gray scale,with limited apps,which helps to get more juice out and can last longer.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;** Verdict - Should you upgrade from Galaxy S4 ? **&lt;br&gt;Overall a great device,coming with the latest,and the fastest available processors and many cool software additions. As you can expect, the price of the device is at the high end of the spectrum,and in my opinion is overpriced. If you are an S4 user,i think this is not a very great upgrade in terms of performance and software features. Many of the software features and the new touchwiz is gonna land on S4 eventually anyway. For an S3 user,the look,the performance and the camera are surely gonna be very refreshing and the overall experience would be far much enjoyable. If you have enough money, and for some reason don't like similarly priced newer HTC One M8 or Xperia Z2,look no where else. This is the best you can get.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great mobile. But beware of duplicate /used products&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The box I got was opened, so it should be a duplicate mobile or used one. So I returned it. Purchased this mobile from retail store even though the price was higher than online price.  This is a great mobile, with almost everything.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S 5&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile is really good. Camera is good and pictures are crystal clear. You can buy it without hesitation. I feel this is the best mobile available as of now.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Overpriced, Bloated, lacks essential features but adds unnecessary features. It's spill proof not waterproof either&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This another bloated overprice junk from Samsung. This company seriously doubts the IQ level of Indians. We are supposed to pay more for than US &amp;amp; other countries &amp;amp; yet get a comparatively inferior version.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Like many previous reviews have pointed out this phone has Samsung Proprietary Exynos Octa processor, which is slower than Quad Core Snapdragon 801 in US, heats up pretty quickly, eats too much battery, does not support LTE, &amp;amp; worst of all there is no third party developer support because Samsung is too lazy to provide documentation &amp;amp; driver binaries for developers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Build quality is same old plastic Samsung is known for, plus they have added flaps to make it waterproof but it is still not true waterproof phone like Sony Xperia Z, it can be called spill proof phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera has been improved a bit but no OIS like many other phones or any innovation like HTC One M8 with selective focus with dual camera lenses.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Size keeps getting bigger &amp;amp; bigger, wonder when this trend of making bigger phones with so high pixel density will stop.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They have added Fingerprint scanner which is too a gimmick rather than necessity to justify this price tag, also there is heart-rate monitor, don't who would be interested in this.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Their TouchWiz has been bloated for years &amp;amp; it surprises me with every generation they somehow manage to find even more bloat to add to already bloated OS. Anyone remember Magazine UI in latest Note series that even managed to lag on Snapdragons even Google was upset with that UI.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They have added NSA sponsored Samsung Knox, which may be useful for &amp;gt;1% of users but is irritating for rest of the 99% of users. It won't let you root your phone, if you like tweaking Android's internals then be prepared.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall this pricing is final nail in it's coffin, Galaxy S4 numbers were low compared to S3, now be prepared for even low numbers. If you need a better phone get Nexus 5 but if you need a better camera wait for HTC One M8 or Xperia Z2&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;- Camera Features are excellent.&lt;br&gt;- Screen quality is the best one. You can see each pixel and each color very clear.&lt;br&gt;- Value for money now, as now the price gets reduced to 36K.&lt;br&gt;- Faster performance compared to S4&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very fast and light weight... Prossesor is quite fast.. Superb camera... Satisfied with finger print scanner but it needs a lot of improvement. Loving my s5.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super quality ,satisfied packing, nice look ,ok ,ok ok, ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok,ok ,ok ok,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung hype is a flop in India&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung galaxy S5 hit the market few day's back. Preluaunch offered a  straight discount of 20%. If you book thru Citicard. Little did Samsung know they have already admitted the price is up by 20%. When samsung learnt that HTC one M8 is hitting the market! immediately they have brought the price to Rs 49990 to have level play with HTC. Flipkart is selling at Rs43990 , delivery on the same day, now the market price is further slashed.  Samsung will have to bring down the price to 40) k to match the initial offer of Citibank. Had they priced it properly when launching without entering in such gimmicks, they would have by now swept the market. Their poor market strategy has eaten away the value of product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good execellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice timely deleivery perfect sealed new phone amaizing exp yes yes yes yrs yes yes yes yes yez yes tes&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00JB6RXBI</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S5 (Shimmery White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone! Tried and Tested for almost two years. battery life is little weaker than the others.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using this phone for almost two years now, and have loved the experience. So I decided to gift this to my not-so-tech-savvy Mom, because android is actually very user friendly, and truly has the best app store in the world.. The samsung phone DOES have an issue regarding its battery life, especially if you have a lot of apps downloaded on it. As compared to phones in the same range from some other companies, this one drains out a lil faster.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Shipping and delivery was very quick too. Mom received it in 3 days, including weekend.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Apart from that, the phone is quite sturdy. In all these two years, I've only once had an issue, which was with the power button having become too sensitive, but that was quickly resolved by hard-resetting the phone.&lt;br&gt;Love that the front camera is so good too! The speakers are awesome.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thumbs up to the S3!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its awesome. i love this phone too much. Please post your recent offer on phone to me.  thank you. :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product from Zoomin&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hey Hi guys time for some feedback and thanks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ordered my Samsung S3 and was very delighted with the product and the seller and of course Amazon for providing such good deals of unique and genuine sellers like Zoomin. Would recommend and of course endorse, no complains.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The phone arrived on time and carefully packed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Vale for money, best rate, had compared almost everywhere but Zoomin rates and brand name, no one could beat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Love it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice Packing.. Product was quality and fulfilled my expectations. From now on will purchase any new products from Amazon only&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best phone under 20k&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it was 36k when i bought it first time,&lt;br&gt;after that now bought it again for 18k,,&lt;br&gt;hv purchased 9 s3 phone for ma family,,,&lt;br&gt;its the best phone to use,&lt;br&gt;even after the price drop the quality is still the same as it was launched&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Sealed mobile (includes scratch resistant glass too)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good quality mobile (sealed). Also scratch resistant glass attached built in. But it take more time to receive, thats the only disadvantage.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Still a great phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Bunch of features and reduced price tag....makes it still a good phone to buy..&lt;br&gt;Probably the phone needs a new android upgrade.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Phone in 2014 Uner 20K&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Main criteria is the gorgeous  Display.It has super AMOLED display with bright colours.Lot of inbuilt Memory for all applications(16GB) out of which 11GB is available.CPU Architecture is cortex-A9.It is much more Efficient than A7.Temparature Issue is there  but its a minimal thing.I got a temparature of 45 as highest temparature while playing asphlat 8 after 15-20 min.It Come to Normal temparature(32-35) with in 4-5 minutes.If u didnt like touchwiz try out other launcher.Im using Go Launcher EX with sony xperia z2 theme because i like xperia UI.&lt;br&gt;So it worth it for its price.If u want to AMOLED display go for it.Watching videos on this screen is awsome.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;excellent product&lt;br&gt;awesome price&lt;br&gt;the only problem i noticed is about the sound volume of the mobile .it is not up to the mark .if this problem is ignored ,it is a wonderful deal&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;customer service sucks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon service was pathetic. Blocked my account after debiting money from my account due to some issue with card merchant. Asked for documents to be faxed (who uses fax in this day and age) and had to waste her with their pathetic customer service and still they could not solve the issue.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Will not be using Amazon in india&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="3.9 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.9 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B0080DJ6CM</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S3 GT-I9300 (Marble White, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Truly Said "Desighned For Humans"&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is truly said that S3 is Desighned For Humans. I Bought this phone because I Loved its Looks and that day it was available for 19990.:)&lt;br&gt;Has Plenty of Features which are available only&lt;br&gt;in this phone.Like smart stay,Nfc,Smart Alert in drive mode,screen mirroring , Multi window.&lt;br&gt;Has a 1.4 ghz quadcore processor and 1gb ram so you cant complain. The back 8.0 mp  camera is superb and takes nice pics and the front camera is OK. And music quality is also superb.&lt;br&gt;The best think I Saw was The Display, I mean to say its super awesome.The clarity of colours and The display.And the screen size is the best 4.8 which can be easily operated by hands and fits nicely in poket.The battery Lasts a day in normal brighrness but if you play heavy games like asphalt 8 then it will drain very quickly.&lt;br&gt;But for regular use its decent.It is better than S3 NEO because it has quadcore and NEO comes with dual core.At Last I would say that You will be Happy after buying it this is my guarantee. People will say that its old but you will not find such stylish, sleek , handy phone.And the colour&lt;br&gt;PEBBLE BLUE Looks nice and gives a rich feel.&lt;br&gt;Better than HTC. As No one offer features which are available in S3.Finally Don't Listen to anyone.Just Listen to your Heart and Go For It.&lt;br&gt;:)&lt;br&gt;.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using iphone since the day its launched but the i would recommend Samsung as the second best phone...easy to useand great phone with sleek design.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i liked the mobile very much and again rates were very competitive it is a very good competitor for flipkart&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product from Zoomin&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hi I purchased my first Android Samsung phone and its awesome, just got it delivered and love it !!!&lt;br&gt;Has ordered from Amazon, the most trusted online shopping site and I must say the seller Zoomin, do know how to get it right the first time and always&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Nicely and neatly packed, got the product on time and with all original bills and in the box items.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best part was value for money.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank you so much Zoomin and Amazon, keep going great:)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;S3 is the Flagship mobile, so need to tell anymore. And amazon with zoomin is very nice to shop online&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice experience of 1st time Online Shopping. Very good and prompt response every time from ZoomIn, good people to deal with..!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product is too good...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is very good mobile ...I love it...I recommend this product...And amazon.in is very good website which is providing the product in cheaper rates...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;awesome phone, upgraded from galaxy r, is much faster and screen is brighter and clearer. only screen looks bad after lots of smudging by my fingers. hope the battery lasts. one day delivery by amazon, very good packaging.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Battery sucks!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Battery drains in an hour, its not even a month. Of course I have the warranty, but its a gift and it turned into nightmare. why the hell I ordered in amazon ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone to have.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I really liked the phone. This is amazing android phone from Samsung.&lt;br&gt;I would recommend it to all my friends.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B007VCRRNS</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S3 GT-I9300 (Pebble Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews></reviews><rating></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00A4A5CO0</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S3 I9300 (Marble White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awsome Phone by samsung..Feature rich and stylish!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all, i would mention the excellent delivery system by Amazon.. i made the order at 10:00 PM in the night and this beauty was in my hand the very next day at my office door sharp by 2.00 PM... Superfast and excellent delivery. Also would like to mention that the delivery guy interacted very well he made me check the Phone and told about the return policy and all other details.. handed me the bill and all this with a smile.... Thats called customer satisfaction!!! 5 Stars for the delivery system of amazon...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now coming to the Phone... Alll i can say it a super smart fone with cutting edge hardware.. with 8 core's is way ahead of any phone right now... every single feature mentioned in the catalog works.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The display is ultra smooth n buttery. with a very high resolution..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The best advantage is you get a 13 MP camera with excellent picture quality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;My verdict: Go for this beast... !!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Speed, Sleek, Stylish, Sexy - S4&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone blows my mind off with its Speed firstly. It is sleek and when kept on a surface feels like you need to pick it up to use. When you play with the interface and its touch, you feel the product is extremely stylish and well thought of when made, and it responds like a dream. Octa core processor makes this phone's installation and uninstallation so quick you dont have to worry about waiting. I'm a part time photographer and the camera leaves me spell bound with its manual features and a magnificent 13 MP camera. It's post production editing features are also quite cool and similar to Instragram. I will sum it up in one word - Sexy.&lt;br&gt;The best android phone ever made. Hands down, I would definitely give it a 5 star anyday.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazon sells old phones to Customers - Worst Online shop&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very disappointed by amazon. I am a regular buyer in flipkart , Thought I would give a try in amazon for one time as amazon is global and all  . The product I received is not new . It didn have the Samsung s4 matte outerplastic film instead had a screen guard which has been put after taking the manufacturing plastic film which is not possible for a new product . The weird thing is the seal was not broken . I had a S4 earlier and it had Samsung s4 plastic film covering the device all over but the one I got from amazon is not new&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i love amazon service and the product quality received is simply the best one.&lt;br&gt;thank you amazon for such a good service&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Defective Mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The delivered mobile hand set was defective. There was over heating problem in the mobile hand set provided to me.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The BEST phone in the market&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is the best phone ever. If your looking for the ultimate android experience you have to go with this. The  Galaxy S4 is the best phone in the market and it beats the iPhone 5 by a long run. This phone has everything you want a phone to have. So don't think twice and go for it!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;super satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Service of amazon is remarkable!!!!&lt;br&gt;and to add to it product is also awesome with extra screen guard which came as a surprise....&lt;br&gt;thank you amazon for making our life easy....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone.....strongly recommended&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Galaxy S4 is amazing phone and is very user friendly. It meets my requirements. I would recommend to buy this phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Deep Black is Very Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Upgraded to Galaxy S4. Very Happy with this phone. The screen resolution is great. The Deep Black comes with a faux leather back cover, which removes the need for an additional back cover reducing the overall weight of the device. The back cover also makes the device classier.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone....,&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;1. Excellent phone with kitkat update. I bought this phone at 27800, which was superb price four months back.&lt;br&gt;2. It is an excellent cell with excellent customization. Screen is large and bright and there is no screen reduction because of kitkat soft keys which have seen in other phone.&lt;br&gt;3. Battery can last one whole day with normal usages.&lt;br&gt;4. I preferred this phone over LG G2 because of GPS which is very important for me.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CL4HUSI</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S4 GT-I9500 (Mist Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 4 - used to be very good value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a very good product. I got a good deal at Amazon and ordered this. The package was delivered within 24 hours! Delivery process was amazing. Balle balle to Amazon!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPhone is very well built, and should last a long time. Accessories are also very good. Also, for a phone that is 2 generations old, it is pretty fast. in fact, it is as fast to operate as an Android in my home, which is the latest model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wanted something that was not too large, had a very good build quality and was easy to use. I was looking at Nokia and Apple products. Nokia was too bulky and all the iPhone owners I spoke to were very happy with their products so I went for it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is very easy to setup. Only problem is getting a micro SIM - which any mobile shop should be able to do. Speakers fidelity is very good. Display is also great. Applications like facebook are also very well designed. Touchscreen is amazing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a bit expensive, but I feel its good value. And I also used 4S and 5 in stores but could not discern an appreciable difference in performance. Maybe the camera is better, but I use a DSLR so I am not sure what the improvement in the picture quality will be. The photos I clicked were good considering this is a mobile.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope this review helps you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review after 6 months of usage - The phone has stood up well. I have installed lots of apps for my kids and they love playing with this phone. I feel the material for this phone is better than the 5 series and takes abuse well. The glass surface does not get scratched and I use a phone guard as well. My friends who have 5 have scratches on the back side of their phone but my phone with a glass back looks really good even now. In terms of device looks and construction, this is hard to beat in the market. All we see nowadays are plastic phones with plastic screens which don't feel that nice in the hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for iOS 7, its a huge step backward for iPhone4. If you are thinking of upgrading from iOS6, don't even think about it. If you are buying a new phone, buy Android since iOS7 looks so much like Android anyway! iOS7 on iPhone 4 and 4S is slower than iOS6, and works Ok on iPhone5 series. I think Apple have lost it after Steve left. The apps are slower on my phone but I just use facebook and my kids use my phone more than me so its Ok till they don't complain! The interface to make phone calls and read messages has also become slow and a bit irritating but the construction and the looks of the phone are still hard to beat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would I would buy an iPhone4 again? I might, because it looks good, is constructed well and will stand up to kids playing with it. I don't do too many apps and stuff so I am Ok. But I would definitely look for a good deal since its an old phone. I would also prefer to have a set that has iOS6 installed!! But if I get a Nokia Windows phone or an Android with tough glass construction, I would prefer that anyday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Update after 8 months - the iOS7 has killed the device. It has become so slow that I am sometimes tempted to just throw it - but having spent 20k plus on this, I tell myself to use it for some more time. I don't use many apps and I keep resetting the device and closing open apps. Still the phone runs amazingly slow now. Messages take forever to open. Searching for contacts to make a simple phone call is arduous. When you make a call, and you want to go to bluetooth or speaker, the other person has said hello 5 times before those options turn up on the screen. Please stay away from this phone unless you get one with iOS6. I have reduced the rating to 2 stars.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best service ever I have got in my 6 years of online experience!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have always considered that flipkart has the best services, may it be refunding process, replacement process, cancellation process or delivery time. But this time, amazon.in has played its part after stepping into the world of competition in Indian market. Trust me I'm amazed the way they have started their website by such low prices for almost every product. Their own courier facility is even better than Flipkart that anyone can rely on it without keeping any followup. I must say that other leading websites like Flipkart and Ebay must start thinking upon their new rival now as its gonna be the best in few time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wish you guys all the very best! Kudos!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Really bad piece&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone produces some disturbance while calling and is nuisance  .... There is a disturbing notice when I am trying to call some one .. I have used the phone with utmost care but the problem has popped up suddenly&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it for 18000 bucks..thanx to saholic..market price is around 22500 and here on amazon too its again available for more than 20K. nice buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;we received the package within a day. The service was excellent and it was well packaged  cant ask for more. also well priced&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Joke&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone was the thing that led to the advent of smartphones we use today. Respect for that.&lt;br&gt;But looking at it alone, buy this now would be a Joke. Biggest Joke.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i got it like few weeks ago and i m very satisfied but d fine heats up while charging  but after putting on a case on it it is normal&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best price i got for iphone4&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got iphone 4 at best ever price, best product at price, good customer service with quick response too. thanks..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget Phone with Premium feel&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Knew all technical specifications so no surprises there. But Got very good deal at amazon &amp;amp; nearly saved 3-4 K .&lt;br&gt;Good phone to gift&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;bill&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;give me the bill of iphone 4,&lt;br&gt;i need  bill for technical support .&lt;br&gt;please prove me bill of phone&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.4 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.4 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CL8XFJW</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 4 (White, 8GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good ( 100% recommended )&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product was delivered very safely packed and as advertised ( new),From VIJAY SALES&lt;br&gt; most importantly manufacture date was couple of week back only,still it had the manufacturing smell and a shining product,&lt;br&gt;Which was very good ,considering even apple resellers,do not have new stock for almost all the products,&lt;br&gt; Do not use the low cost (150 â‚¹) MATT screen protector, after switch on the phone it looks like a TV ( with all dots ),&lt;br&gt; Cannot see clearly , if you still want only matt then go for the costlier one ( 400â‚¹ to 1000 â‚¹ ),&lt;br&gt;( 150â‚¹ ) classy is good i am using it now,&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thank you&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent phone and the size fits my hand perfectly. Touch n finger print sensor is good. The only drawback I can say is the wi-fi signals are intermittent and have to set up with passwords again and again which is irritating&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best phone bar none&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Beautifully designed, smooth OS and imaginatively simple navigation. Love the security and consistency of the finger-print scanner. Wish the battery life was longer though.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I phone 5s space grey colour.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice phone and very good services by amazon as well .Quality of phone totally meets to my expectation.&lt;br&gt;Thank you amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPhone 5S&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Perfect quality from the seller. Love the phone, amazing features. Must buy if you're looking for a multi purpose phone that can stay with you for a long time&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SUPERB !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was more than expected well within time line specified. The interim status review was also very helpful.&lt;br&gt;Good deal without any hassles whatsoever and delivered at door step and collected the payment.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Go for it online @ amazon.in&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's cool, it's bold, it's elegant, it's Apple!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Happy and satisfied customer, experience the same once you own it yourself.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Phone EVER!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Without any doubt the best purchase I've made on Amazon so far... The best smartphone in the market as of now and loving every single moment of it...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have used lot of phones but i would like to say it's supeb .... Performance is too good.. Tuch is osam&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5s great buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Exactly as ordered. Brand new and sealed. Cheaper than buying from an apple retailer and exactly the same product at a cheaper cost.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLC9V4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Space Grey, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple is apple but I missed in disk space&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Beware 16 GB iPad comes with usable space of 12 GB and if u install the recommended apps it consumes almost 8 GB. I made mistake. I don't find usability of cellular feature. I can make hotspot by mobile and work&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best product from Apple.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had my Iphone &amp;amp; Ipod.But this product had exceeded my expectations.Good connectivity, fast booting &amp;amp; delivers in nano seconds.Apple iPad Air is far ahead of its rivals.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ipad air&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a cool nice beautiful tab...nice picture quality....fast....light weight...easy to hold in portrait mode&lt;br&gt;A little bit pricey....otherwise its a worth buy..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Ipad Air- Light on accessories also&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was surprised to note that there is no ear-phone with the Ipad Air. Even though it was advertised that programmes like pages and Numbers are bundled free,they did not come pre-installed.&lt;br&gt;The Tablet as it is is okay performance-wise.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got wrong product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had placed an order for ipad air and got ipad mini instead, although the money was returned but i don't expect this from amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Careless Service from Amazon !&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had the worst experience with this purchase.&lt;br&gt;I got IPad mini instead of an IPad Air !! When I called the customer care executive they told me that my product was not in stock so they sent me IPad mini instead. I was hoping for a replacement but was asked to return the product and make a new purchase for no mistake of mine.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Must Buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best tablet in the market and great apple apps designed specifically for ipad air its the best and buy the 64 gb or up version. I got the 128 gb and its crazy storage and Value. Its Thin and Light (ultra light and thin). Its fast with the A7 64 bit processor&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Simply Supreb..one of the wonders of Technology&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent App ipad.&lt;br&gt;Only think I dislike about product is download is limited to 100MB for Cellular data ipad ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad Air shows  why apple is the best in business&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Right from look to touch to feel and performance, ipad gets you hook on to it. Apple creativity is shown right from app distribution to charger and usb (apple) design.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great, hope other companies follow apple in creativity and ingenuity&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPad Air&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good operating speed and so light in weight. A must buy for everybody who lives iPads or the iOS&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00GRLYSDQ</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPad Air (Silver, 16GB, WiFi + Cellular)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Iphone 5s is Swiss watch of phones&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When we buy a swiss watch, What we get for such high price is the Quality, Design and Perfection. The same is applied to iPhone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. I love its design over any other phone.&lt;br&gt;2. UI is so clean, clear and with useful features&lt;br&gt;3. Data/Charging cable that can be used in any direction is a unique feature.&lt;br&gt;4. Fingerprint scanner is faster than my office attendance machine and that too from any angle.&lt;br&gt;5. Exclusive features like Fingerprint and 64 bit Desktop Class processor in which competition is lagging about a year&lt;br&gt;6. 120 fps slo mo is awesome. It replaced old Go Pro camera.&lt;br&gt;7. Dual flash also produce excellent lighting results.&lt;br&gt;8. Airplay offer audiophile quality audio transmission to Airplay speaker.&lt;br&gt;9. M7 sensor help my NIKE+ move app to be more accurate for health tracking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;all in all The best phone that i can have&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The worst retailer to buy from&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had purchased a 5s on my birthday from Big Retail which was defective. Such a huge disappointment from retailer!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone, no words to describe. Perfection. Some think that Android is the best with all best configuration and plenty of features. And they debate saying its cheap too. For all of that opinion, people who cannot afford apple wil always says that. People who can afford wil enjoy the iPhone silently.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;super phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent service by amazon.. very prompt delivery.. genuine packed piece.. I bought it as a gift for my wife and she loved it.. still the best smartphone around by far..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Apple iPhone 5s Review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;There is something a prospective buyer should understand before even looking to buy an iphone 5s.&lt;br&gt;I'm no apple fanboy, trust me, but it IS the best phone available on market right now.&lt;br&gt;Not the most value for money, but the ultimate best. The Primera.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks wise, I'd say its not a bad job. The same signature look that it has carried on since long. The gold and gray look fantastic, and feels nice in hand as well. But looks aren't even the intro to the whole story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The A7 chip inside is the best processor available on market for mobile devices, even better than the top of the line SnapDragon 800 which is the best any android/windows phone can offer.&lt;br&gt;The performance gains are not significant enough to matter to a casual user, or any user unless you were really looking for it. Its like saying ones a lockhead blackbird and others a falcon htv2. FYI, they're both insanely fast aircrafts. For people like us, its insignificant which is really faster. The 64bit architecture wouldnt matter much to the normal user as long as the applications dont make use of it. Its just apple being paranoid as usual about being future proof.&lt;br&gt;In addition to the processor capabilities, a major plus of Apple devices is that iOS7 was optimized for A7, while android(kitkat or jbean or whatever) is not. Android runs on a vm which leeches out a bit of the potency.&lt;br&gt;The GPU performance is commendable, and the motion processor m7 is also a unique characteristic, though if its full potential can be used in normal scenario remains to be seen. Yet.&lt;br&gt;The fingerprint scanner is a new innovation, and seems to work pretty good unless your hands are too sweaty. Currently its use is limited though in time in-app authentication as well as credit card/bank acc/wallet authentication could also be done using it. Lots to look forward to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Downsides are also there, iOS7 needs more optimization to be better. And some might prefer a bigger screen to utilize all that juice inside. Though IMO the size seems optimum, not too big for a phone, and not too small to be disappointed. The battery could be a bit improved too, to last more than a day. A7/M7/PowerVR6 does drink a lot of power.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All in all, I5s is not your casual whip-it-out-of-the-pocket-and-throw-it-to-the-bed smartphone, its a carefully constructed marvel. Powerful, future proof upto maybe 2+years, which is not something any other phone can boast about. Only two things stand in the way of it being the optimum phone, 1st being on the higher side of the food chain, and 2nd the more important one, we dont need that much power or performance. Yet. The app ecosystem, however large and varied it is, still doesnt have any applications that make use of the a7/m7 processors inside, or the 64bit architecture for that matter. And without it, its just a lamborghini on indian roads. Still, It IS the most expensive phone on the market. And again, it IS better than any, and you don't get to be the best without beating the best, and it costs to do that, like, a LOT.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Build Quality: Unmatched (The closest competitor would be the HTC One)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Display: Many people complain that this 4-inch retina display offering is joke when compared to what other manufacturers offer these days. But this is not a phablet; it's comparatively much easier to use with one hand and the color tone of the 5S is much better than the overly saturated displays on the Galaxy S4 and Galaxy Note 3.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Processor and RAM: The 5S has only 1GB RAM and a Dual Core processor which seemingly pales in comparison to what other flagship phones have to offer. But if you are a serious buyer, don't be fooled by these specs because the iPhone 5S is actually "The Fastest Phone ever tested" till date. The reason why the iPhone 5S blows away the competition is because it's processor is made specifically for the phone and it utilizes and squeezes processing power in the most efficient way unlike other phones whose processors are generic and used across various manufacturers without really utilizing available power to it's full extent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera: The 5S has a excellent camera but it is not the best in the market.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Call Quality: Normal calls are just as good as any other phone. But not many people are aware of the new facetime audio HD calling feature across iOS 7 users, the clarity is almost too much! You can even hear a person swallow or smack his/her lips. Little too intimate if you ask me :-)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Special Feature: Fingerprint Scan and unlock your phone. People may argue over the pros and cons of such a feature but I would personally prefer such a feature which I will certainly make use of; instead of an almost useless fancy feature which I rarely use. (Eg: Touch to share)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Price: Considering that the manufacturing cost of the iPhone 5S is just one dollar more than that of the iPhone 5 whose manufacturing cost is around INR 13,000; I would have liked the 5S to be priced at 40,000. It is without doubt EXPENSIVE!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Everything as expected&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It delivers the same way as expected. 4G LTE feature is good and fast. Battery drains  with 3G/4G, but overall a good product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very happy with the product. Since it's my first apple product, It's very user friendly and amazing phone. Amazon service is excellent. Keep it up!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best Iphone 5S&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Worthy buying puting into right way of use makes me to achieve my goals and to aim maximum benefits inn&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome is the word! An amazing phone worth having. The Light weight n sleek body makes it more desirable !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It is simply awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great service... Received it within24 hours... Has awesome features..great battery backup.. Gets charged really fast! I just love it :)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.5 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.5 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCD38</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Gold, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;1 complete year warranty is not provided.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When I checked the warranty period of Iphone delivered to me, the perod is reduced by 45 days from 1 year ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 5S is ultimate...GabbarDeals a great online store..Thanks to Amazon's Fulfillment team!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got my iPhone 5S from GabbarDeals at lowest price and it's genuine iPhone from Apple.&lt;br&gt;Validated the warranty and service details via Apple server and it's 1 Year!!!&lt;br&gt;No issues with any feature in iPhone. Great call quality, excellent speed, perfect OS(iOS 7.0.5), Better battery back up, nice look and comfort..  Thanks a lot to GabbarDeals and Amazon.in...Keep up the great work!!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nothing better then Iphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got this excellent hand device on 24 June. It is simply awesome. Nothing can even beat iphone . Iphone 5s is a great looking and excellent processor phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I order this product on 23 and 24 I received and checked my validity on Apple.com, it is valid for 1 year. Genuine product, excellent mobile, raise your status , rest phones are not even nearby to this iphone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera is clear and better than iPhone 5. Amazing features like Slow motion, Finger Touch, Touch to buy products online. Simply incredible! Sound is clear, nice speakers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;MAIN FEATURE I LIKE, if someone is calling you, you can disconnect its call, and iphone will remind you in 1 hr or when you leave from your office that you got a call from this number or person, shall I call them back? I love this feature. Simply awesome and useful.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iOS awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's complete nothing else u want it's crafted perfectly it's too good too too good it's never lacked anything loved it iPhone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;******Awesome Phone******&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The built quality and the looks of this phone is EXCELLENT and is at par with other phones available in the market.iPhone 5s is extremely fast and very smooth to operate.The price available on Amazon is the cheapest on the market.Very happy with this product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Camera is clear and better than iPhone 5. Amazing features like Slow motion, Finger Touch, Touch to buy products online. Simply incredible! Not a Apple Fanboy, but iPhone 5s has resolved battery issue to a good level. Now I can use it without charging for like more than a day when I use it to maximum level! Simply designed and has classy looks!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing features with more apps den any other cellphone. Picture n video quality is much much better den Nokia n samsung .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Apple iPhone 5S as usual very good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amazon good service &amp;amp; best price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very Good Packing . . . .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The 'BEST" from The "BEST"......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was not able to get any discount on the iPhone 5S from any of the dealers or Apple Authorized Stores which is when I decided to try and see if there was a good deal available online.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And boy was I surprised, to find the iPhone 5S available on Amazon at INR 47615, a huge saving on my pocket.....to top it up, being a Citibank Card holder, I am entitled to a cash back of INR 1500....Now thats some deal....Thank you Amazon!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice product in this segment....and great price at amazon. want to buy 1 more but amazon wouldn't let me do that.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="3.9 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.9 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00FXLCG7G</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5s (Silver, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Successfully delivered a used product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon india has successfully delivered a used product. The phone was activated on 9th april but however the item was invoiced on 13th April.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;some  times it  hang and battery life is very low with 3g i always need to worry about battery back up&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;No GIFT WRAP!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I'm completely disappointed about Amazon service. I specifically mentioned that i wanted my order to be gift wrapped &amp;amp; checked the necessary options for it.. &amp;amp; amazon charged me for that. I absolutely do not care about the money.. Do u guys think that u want me to go to some store &amp;amp; gift wrap my order myself , even after i specifically mentioned that it should be gift wrapped.. If you guys are not going to do it.. why provide that option.. don't give false promises okay.. Do u think u refunding me the amount for the gift wrap is gonna make my order magically gift wrap itself.. Seriously Amazon service sucks..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Who does'nt like to flaunt :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Basic iphone at an amazing price from amazon. Meets all the requirements, with style statement as added bonus. Technically far better than many phones in this range but 1 star less for a poor battery life and below par front cam.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone is hanging sometimes&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is hanging, for getting normal state need to restart the phone.&lt;br&gt;when it hangs am unable to slide to unlock the phone. and getting very heat while using internet.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Bad Touch Screen&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The touch on the Apple iPhone black lags badly. I want to find a customer service centre to replace it. I just pray that they will&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;exceed expectation!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Perfectly packed and its working great! i am loving it. No complaints at all. Thanks amazon for being so quick.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;upset with the pricing, after i bought it the price went down by more then 800 Rs even after observing it for some time&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome mobile in this range.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;THis product is far better than samsung or any other android or window phone in this range..&lt;br&gt;Good mobile if you are ready to spend amount appraoax 25k.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my 4s heats up quickly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;my iphone heats up more than warm just while doing simple tasks, and my hands sweat profusely, especially while charging the phone gets really hot and its making me worry. Is this normal? is there anybody facing the same problem as i am??&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00GFGE5VS</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 4S (Black, 8GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;at the service center the very first day&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I was too too excited to open the sealed box of Apple 4S. but when I turned it on, all my excitement turned into agony when I saw vertical lines showing on the screen all the time. I rushed from one service center to another and have given it for replacement.&lt;br&gt;Mind it- only the handset  will be replaced not the boxes. the sr number on the bill and the box will be different from that of the handset.&lt;br&gt;very depressed&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very unfortunate.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very sorry to inform you that I met a very bad experience in doing shopping with you. First of all the courier company didn't deliver the package to me on time. The gadget kept lying with the local courier people for three days. They didn't even think of informing me. Secondly the phone camera didn't work at the timing of opening of parcel. Now I am in a contact  with apple people for replacing or repair of my gadget. See the irony all my charm of getting new phn has gone. Thanks for great experience.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent decision to have bought the iPhone4S&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;As the new iPhone models got launched, like the iPhone5S and 5C, the price of the once flagship phone model from Apple, the iPhone4S dropped. At amazon, the best price was offered and it was the best price available online with warranty.&lt;br&gt;The smartphone, nevertheless to say houses a host of dynamic features. I was keeping an eye on the 8 mp camera on it that offers 1080p full HD video recording. The camera is capable of capturing broadcast quality footage. I am sure, its going to full full my plans to make a quality short-film using this equipment. I have done some sample shots with it and i am highly impressed with the results. Those who are really serious about shooting footage may buy a paid app from istore, FilmicPRO,(Just Rs.270) which is much better than the standard video app that comes with the device. The App lets you set and lock exposure, focus, white balance etc... also it allows to shoot footage with varying bit rates as well as compression formats. You can add desired matte like for eg. 2.35.1 etc...while shooting itself&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The device comes equipped with the latest iOS version and Siri is also very helpful. The hardware is awesome and the feel of using an apple hardware in itself has got a charm factor. The display is vivid and the touch is a breeze.&lt;br&gt;Overall at this point of time it provides the best value for money. It is not as expensive as the iPhone5 series, at the same time it has got pretty decent capabilities in all areas. Overall a highly recommended smartphone for someone who is smart enough to squeeze out the real smartness in it !&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got the iPhone in 3 days in perfect condition&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent service from amazon...completely satisfied with the product...i am happy to get the iPhone at such a price...keep rocking amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Moved from android to iOS, and the switch has been smooth. It is nice to have a smaller phone in my pocket for a change!&lt;br&gt;Battery life with moderate usage (2G + wifi) has been really good with a single charge lasting up to 2 days. Perhaps the only thing I miss is access to much more "fine-tuning" that is possible on the android platform.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome !!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Brand new one..&lt;br&gt;Wonderful UI and it's really butter smooth ...&lt;br&gt;Good battery backup - easily stands for more than a day without much usage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Only drawback is the space available. Out of 8GB, OS occupies 2GB and all app installs eat up the remaining.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Overall it's very good for people looking for decent screen size and holding in hand factor.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone-arrived in time&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the phone in time from Amazon. Thank you&lt;br&gt;The phone arrived in time and was well packed in a box.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Quality phone now at affordable price June 2014&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its very good phone. Touch response is excellent and best in the price range.&lt;br&gt;Its UI is not very easy to use, it needs a little time (1~2 days) to understand.&lt;br&gt;Camera is decent, not the best as hyped. I saw NOISE in the photos.&lt;br&gt;Though it has DUAL core processor, its very very powerful and "Iphone 4s" will get&lt;br&gt;"iOS 8" as upcoming OS upgrade.&lt;br&gt;You will lots of quality apps for IOS compared to other platforms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I bought it for my dad, he can't use 5inch phones.&lt;br&gt;Apple is QUALITY PHONE and also STATUS SYMBOL in my opinion.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I own Sony and Samsung android phone. I am hardcore SONY FAN.&lt;br&gt;Sony's UI is very easy to use among Sony, Samsung &amp;amp; Apple.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Samsung's camera is excellent among the above three.&lt;br&gt;But Sony phones suck at low light shooting, they fail at processing image.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Apple iPhone 4s" uses SONY's sensor and "G" lens on their mobiles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion: Super Quality phone with minor flaws.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's a superb phone it looks premium it feels premium in ur hand and great price &amp;amp;dont compare with plastic phones like Samsung or any body&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I've a question&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Is it unlocked? I've an airtel sim card which i am currently using with my nokia phone.Can i use the same with iphone?&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="3.9 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.9 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00GFGKC92</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 4S (White, 8GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Overall a good phone who are starting with apple. I got a good bargain and cetainly good value for my money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Top Class Product and Service from Amazon.in&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I recently used [...] to purchase an iPhone4 8GB and I was very pleased with the service that I received. I did call up the customer care number of Amazon.in to get fair quote and to know about the billing details and the warranty in India and the representative on the phone was very helpful and provided me with all the necessary details. I did placed an order at Amazon.in for the iPhone4 8GB with my credit card right away. They had offered an excellent price for the iPhone4 8GB. My iPhone4 8GB was delivered in just 2 days. It was a very prompt delivery. The iPhone4 8GB was sealed and I registered the product with my Apple ID online. My iPhone4 8GB works like wonder and it is an excellent phone for the price that is offered. It runs on iOS7.1 and is working well for my use. I recommend Amazon.in and I am very much satisfied by the service I had received from them.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Trustworthy Workhorse... although showing signs of ageing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought my iPhone 4 in 2009 (Incidentally, it cost as much then as it does now!).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Its seen me through 3 new iPhone releases, but continues to be a decent, usable smartphone. Given Apple's ability to control the ecosystem, this phone continues to get the latest iOS releases along with the newer versions. The latest release (iOS 7) though seems to really stretch this phone. I think this is probably the last OS update that the iPhone 4 is going to see.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Based on having owned this phone as long as I have, here's my take on the Pros &amp;amp; Cons, vs Android phones that may cost as much:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;- Access to the latest iOS experience, without having to pay a bomb for it&lt;br&gt;- Perfectly usable screen (retina display; can't go wrong with it)&lt;br&gt;- Most apps, including graphic intensive games, continue to be usable&lt;br&gt;- Battery life is decent; (can last for a day and a half with moderate usage)&lt;br&gt;- Call voice quality is great;&lt;br&gt;- Vs Android Phones: Ease of Use(Idiot Proof); better app quality (UI, responsiveness)&lt;br&gt;- Very Durable; dropped it 50+ times- nothing!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;- Camera quality can no longer be called 'great'(5MP); Great for instagram, not much else. Same goes for video&lt;br&gt;- End of the road from an upgradation perspective (Don't see this getting iOS 7+)&lt;br&gt;- Phone speakers are not especially loud; I frequently miss calls&lt;br&gt;- No LTE; A concern if you're in a city that's seeing 4G/LTE connectivity (Pune, Bangalore, Kolkata)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion:&lt;br&gt;This phone was amazing 4 years ago, but that was when Android phones were just beginning to become good. Things have changed. The Nexus 4 / Samsung Duos or even the Micromax/ Karbonn phones offer much better value from a specs / rupee perspective.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The only way I'd recommend this phone to someone is if they're looking to experience an Apple phone for the first time, but cannot afford to go all the way. It's a great usable phone, and you won't miss the frills that an android phone offers. If however, you're a stickler for features, and want the most bang for your buck, you should be looking at other alternatives.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Still the best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;iphone 4 is comparable to Windows Xp. Gold standard for any smartphone and difficult to replace by Apple. Same story as windows Xp as till date microsoft is struggling to find a replacement.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome..amazon nd....i phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I phone is i phone..not like other biscuit phone....dignity of use..royalty..always looks great&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Great great great..great&lt;br&gt;Amozon  is good ..rocking&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;complaint against Iphone 4 apple&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased I Phone last month &amp;amp; found that 1 speaker is not functioning. The sound is very slow &amp;amp; difficult to hear the voice of another one. Pls guide me if i can go to Apple service center in gurgaon (India) for solving the problem or otherwise if i return to you. Any other solution from your side pls.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am happy with the delivery of the product. Firstly I saw some negative feedback from various user and got disappointed that I took the wrong decision by ordered this from this website.&lt;br&gt;But when I got my product and I happy with the product.&lt;br&gt;Keep up the good work !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Replacement&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I just had to replace some ones phone. Never used it. nor would I want to be caught dead with one.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 4&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I'm a I phone user for the past 4 yrs and I wanted to buy another I phone for my wife. I found iPhone 4 in amazon.in for a great price and immediately bought it.&lt;br&gt;Great phone and my wife is happily using it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;For Gulshan's query&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;only one speaker works in iphone.Left speaker is for microphone.Its absolutely normal and not a defective piece.Its same in all iphones&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.6 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.6 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CL8XE8Y</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 4 (Black, 8GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Master piece&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a master piece of technology. Price is high but you know that you are paying for innovation and hard work gone to make this wonderful piece. It hurts when you see the same is being copied by making use of legal loopholes and sold cheaply.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;waiting for same rate again asap with white colour do it as soon as possible&lt;br&gt;hope for the favourable response&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very reliable phone and bug free OS&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First off, I do believe this is overpriced and I would probably not have bought this at a 45K price tag. However, I ended up getting one without paying for one(provided by my employer) Like all Apple products, very high quality build and a fantastic iOS operating system that does not crash mid way! This could be missing some fancy features that competition is boasting of, but that is easily compensated by the assured reliability this offers. I have owned the previous generation of iPhones and i have a iPad along with a first gen Galaxy Note. I can tell you from my experience that if price is not a constraint, there is no better phone to buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got a damaged piece.. Disappointing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I really love apple products and I dont blame Amazon for this damage but I have received a product which is unfit from Inside and is giving weird sounds of a loose part when shaken. This certainly is not expected from Apple's level of fit and Finish and also not expected from Amazon's store which keeps only fit and perfect products..&lt;br&gt;Would like it if replaced with a better one. For now disappointed..!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;well an iphone is an iphone!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Piece of art you like to keep holding onto, this is what an iphone 5 is. Its not plasticky,neither is its software crappy.&lt;br&gt;Yes its cost u around 5k extra, and u pay it for no nonsense.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Shocking experience due to fraudulant supply of goods&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;a duplicate apple i phone 5 without a warranty &amp;amp; mismatched serial no. was supplied which we came to know only after taking this to a i phone store in Chennai. the subsequent handling of the complaint from Amazon.in was highly disappointing, because they are trying to pass the problem to their supplier / vendor with whom we the customer have nothing to do. The on line order was placed on the trust we have with Amazon.in . we are still pursuing the complaint with the hope Amazon.in would do proper investigation and provide justice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;hope better sense would prevail with Amazon.in to ensure the trust is not lost in the initial stages of their operations in India.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The best phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The best phones I ever used its awesome very efficient, very easy to use and handle Touch is simply superb including the processing speed.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;iphone at it best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I think it's worth the price tag. Easy to use and has maximum features. Beautiful screen with high quality camera. OS 7 is by far best easy to understand and use.Need to improve Battery backup.&lt;br&gt;But really iPhone 5 does need any comment.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;When you r planing to purchase your 1st phone ... bought from you hard earned cash... It better be an apple :-) Thanks amazon!!j&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone with sleek framework, which is well armored with an A6, 8MP ,16 GB, wacky apple apps.&lt;br&gt;You luv it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;low weight,fast,easy grip touch  but jeb pe bhhari,  yahi hai mobile mania  ki akhiri taiyari. ye dil mange more i phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.4 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.4 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CL8X3UI</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 5 (Black-Slate, 16GB)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;iPhone 4 - used to be very good value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a very good product. I got a good deal at Amazon and ordered this. The package was delivered within 24 hours! Delivery process was amazing. Balle balle to Amazon!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;iPhone is very well built, and should last a long time. Accessories are also very good. Also, for a phone that is 2 generations old, it is pretty fast. in fact, it is as fast to operate as an Android in my home, which is the latest model.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wanted something that was not too large, had a very good build quality and was easy to use. I was looking at Nokia and Apple products. Nokia was too bulky and all the iPhone owners I spoke to were very happy with their products so I went for it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This is very easy to setup. Only problem is getting a micro SIM - which any mobile shop should be able to do. Speakers fidelity is very good. Display is also great. Applications like facebook are also very well designed. Touchscreen is amazing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is a bit expensive, but I feel its good value. And I also used 4S and 5 in stores but could not discern an appreciable difference in performance. Maybe the camera is better, but I use a DSLR so I am not sure what the improvement in the picture quality will be. The photos I clicked were good considering this is a mobile.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hope this review helps you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Review after 6 months of usage - The phone has stood up well. I have installed lots of apps for my kids and they love playing with this phone. I feel the material for this phone is better than the 5 series and takes abuse well. The glass surface does not get scratched and I use a phone guard as well. My friends who have 5 have scratches on the back side of their phone but my phone with a glass back looks really good even now. In terms of device looks and construction, this is hard to beat in the market. All we see nowadays are plastic phones with plastic screens which don't feel that nice in the hand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As for iOS 7, its a huge step backward for iPhone4. If you are thinking of upgrading from iOS6, don't even think about it. If you are buying a new phone, buy Android since iOS7 looks so much like Android anyway! iOS7 on iPhone 4 and 4S is slower than iOS6, and works Ok on iPhone5 series. I think Apple have lost it after Steve left. The apps are slower on my phone but I just use facebook and my kids use my phone more than me so its Ok till they don't complain! The interface to make phone calls and read messages has also become slow and a bit irritating but the construction and the looks of the phone are still hard to beat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Would I would buy an iPhone4 again? I might, because it looks good, is constructed well and will stand up to kids playing with it. I don't do too many apps and stuff so I am Ok. But I would definitely look for a good deal since its an old phone. I would also prefer to have a set that has iOS6 installed!! But if I get a Nokia Windows phone or an Android with tough glass construction, I would prefer that anyday.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Update after 8 months - the iOS7 has killed the device. It has become so slow that I am sometimes tempted to just throw it - but having spent 20k plus on this, I tell myself to use it for some more time. I don't use many apps and I keep resetting the device and closing open apps. Still the phone runs amazingly slow now. Messages take forever to open. Searching for contacts to make a simple phone call is arduous. When you make a call, and you want to go to bluetooth or speaker, the other person has said hello 5 times before those options turn up on the screen. Please stay away from this phone unless you get one with iOS6. I have reduced the rating to 2 stars.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best service ever I have got in my 6 years of online experience!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have always considered that flipkart has the best services, may it be refunding process, replacement process, cancellation process or delivery time. But this time, amazon.in has played its part after stepping into the world of competition in Indian market. Trust me I'm amazed the way they have started their website by such low prices for almost every product. Their own courier facility is even better than Flipkart that anyone can rely on it without keeping any followup. I must say that other leading websites like Flipkart and Ebay must start thinking upon their new rival now as its gonna be the best in few time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I wish you guys all the very best! Kudos!!!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Really bad piece&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone produces some disturbance while calling and is nuisance  .... There is a disturbing notice when I am trying to call some one .. I have used the phone with utmost care but the problem has popped up suddenly&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it for 18000 bucks..thanx to saholic..market price is around 22500 and here on amazon too its again available for more than 20K. nice buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;we received the package within a day. The service was excellent and it was well packaged  cant ask for more. also well priced&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Joke&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone was the thing that led to the advent of smartphones we use today. Respect for that.&lt;br&gt;But looking at it alone, buy this now would be a Joke. Biggest Joke.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i got it like few weeks ago and i m very satisfied but d fine heats up while charging  but after putting on a case on it it is normal&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best price i got for iphone4&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got iphone 4 at best ever price, best product at price, good customer service with quick response too. thanks..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget Phone with Premium feel&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Knew all technical specifications so no surprises there. But Got very good deal at amazon &amp;amp; nearly saved 3-4 K .&lt;br&gt;Good phone to gift&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;bill&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;give me the bill of iphone 4,&lt;br&gt;i need  bill for technical support .&lt;br&gt;please prove me bill of phone&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_5 " title="4.4 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.4 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00CL8XFJW</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Apple iPhone 4 (White, 8GB)</value></title></item></items>