<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;It is meeting my expectation&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The shipping and handling was good. Also the phone fits my budget and expectation. The only draw back I found was, the phone get bit slower while downloading 2-3 video from whatsapp, but its ok&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung core I8262 review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is really awesome mobile phone. It is cost effective. Everything works fine in this mobile. I would suggest that if you want to buy a mobile within budget with all features equal to class smartphone  then go for Samsung core I8262. It is a class smartphone within the budget.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy Core GT- I8262, Not good to use , hangs alot&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I chosen 2 star cause right now am feeling its not worth to buy it from Amazon :(&lt;br&gt;Mobile is very poor, hangs alot..... to open any particular items take a long....&lt;br&gt;i want a call from amazon ppl cause no number left to call.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;fine product. only flash light image slightly yellowish. with 1gb RAM superb product.&lt;br&gt;worth having it. enjoy shopping with amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Smartphone in range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Camera quality is good. Browsing speed is good. All functions and games are running smoothly. Front camera is nice for video calling on skype...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Got it quickly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super..got it quickly..original packed piece. good service, mobile is superb with lots of features. best buy for the money spent&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Price Great Set&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is an awesome set just loving it my mom is using it since 1 year and cant see anthing better than this.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very slow hangs from first day&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i bought it from amazon .. but i found it overheating and hang problem on first day of my buying.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good to have&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its really  a very good expiriance to buy things online.&lt;br&gt;i got it safe... COD.. easylly.. and more over cheeper then the other.&lt;br&gt;Thanks AMAZON&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;M D P RAO  HYDERABAD  9849565017&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have received the unit on 07.6.2014. It was functioning well. Suddenly since 15.6.2014, it started giving problem - not charging and the battery was totally drained out. Today I have deposited the instrument with the Authorised dealer of Samsung as detailed below :​From: Mukkavilli dharma prakasa rao &amp;lt;mukkavilli.dharmaprakasarao366@gmail.com&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;Date: Tue, Jun 17, 2014 at 11:15 PM&lt;br&gt;Subject: Re: Fwd:&lt;br&gt;To: Electronyx Bazaar &amp;lt;info@electronyxbazaar.in&amp;gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thank  you very much for your reply. As advised by you today I took the instrument to your Authorised Service centre M/s Suman Telecom Services, Tarnaka, Secunderabad 500017 and the same is deposited vide their work order No. 1425 of date and Bill No. 4175869616. I understand major replacement of main parts such as mother board etc., are to be replaced.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It is very surprising just after usage of 6 days how the major parts needs to be replaced and now I am scared to handle the instrument. As it is under warranty, the major items are being replaced and what is the guarantee it does not get break-down again. As I have passion to have all samsung products in my use i.e. Laptap, AC, Washing Machine etc., I am rewarded heavily by supplying me a defective unit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In view of above, please arrange to replace the item with new one and I am not interested to use the present repaired one.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recently I returned from USA with lot of SAMSUNG products as gifts and no one complained about the performance rather they are all very happy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please ensure to deliver me the new unit or else please return me the payment of Rs.12,690/- paid by me for the product.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanking you and awaiting for a prompt reply. I am not collecting back the unit from your Authorised Service Centre.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;M.D.P.RAO  HYDERABAD  9849565017&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On Tue, Jun 17, 2014 at 12:32 AM, Electronyx Bazaar &amp;lt;info@electronyxbazaar.in&amp;gt; wrote:&lt;br&gt;Sir&lt;br&gt;Please do the needful now, I want replacement with new item (not defective like present one)&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone but donot buy it from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This one is the Affordable Phone with Brand Name .. you get almost what you need in very affordable price ... But Pl. My dear friends never purchase any product from Amazon  .. it has worst service ... you will face lots of trouble and mental frustration  ... It is sure that you will never get your order on time but delay of 4 to 5 days  ....  I am truly frustrated with this .. if you want genuine product on time .. pl go somewhere else .. but not here ..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;helpful amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The amazon is a very good purchasing site.realy it is very easy and its work very nice.i also purchase a Samsung galaxy core only 11000 but its marketing rate is 12800 .so it is helpful site thank you amazon. Com.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;worst product...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This Phone heats up like chines phone.. u can't Keep in your pant pocket..it doen't support HD video...&lt;br&gt;poor battery...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone @ reasonable price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No other phones have such nice features as core have and that is also in reasonable price itself. I am very happy with this purchase. Such a nice brand in affordable price. A++++&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its a good phone...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this phone met our expectations.... we are enjoying the phone with all its features, except its frontfacing camera rest all is very good...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;as its good budget phone with latest feather and as its brand is good also so will suggest to buy this phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;duplicate items&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i think that online mobiles r duplicate..but it has so many changes r there..&lt;br&gt;orissa state mobile product r another software..nd and online product r another software...so that plz if u purchasing mobile phone then u purchase from ur own city and it will proft that original product...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good but it could be better..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a good product in this price range,but it could be better in terms of like, you can't use OTG cable, can't play HD videos, low spekar volume&lt;br&gt;otherwise good phone with 4.3" screen with good, clear display, works good on heavy use like games etc., with 1gb ram, dual sim(both active micro sim), slim phone, good net surfing.&lt;br&gt;I would recommend this phone who want a good smartphone in this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;VERY GOOD PRODUCT AT LOW COST&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;VERY GOOD PRODUCT AT LOW COST&lt;br&gt;SAMSUNG BASIC PHONES IT IS THE BEST ITEM I HAD EVER USED FOR SIMPLE USE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Core good mid size mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile is good in the mid size range. Easy to operate for people used to Samsung products. Good features.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellant services, beyond satisfaction&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like Amazon's commitment. I find services beyond my satisfaction.  Keep it up, I will always prefer Amazon for future purchases.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung galaxy core review&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good Mobile as a specificaion wise ,but its an older model now a days .&lt;br&gt;Not a updates available in this mobile .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone but need improved back cover design to Improve grip&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice phone but need improved back cover design to Improve grip.&lt;br&gt;The standard back cover has extreme glossy finish making it slippery to hold.&lt;br&gt;Overall good package for the price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent service i have been taken mobile in time&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;But i unable to get my HDFC credit card 10% cash back offer till now,Will you forward as soon as possible to my account&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks&amp;amp;Regards,&lt;br&gt;krishna kappera&lt;br&gt;09014061244&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Pack of knowledge&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;awesome piece and happy with its performance. Great service by Amazon. In time and perfectly packed with care and love...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;switch off while talking and hanging&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;switch off while talking ...and hanging ,takes too much time to open a application too...this is not a good product. i lost my 13000 indian money and i lost  the trust on amazon and  samsung mobiles.sorry to review this .pls do the needful.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome set in this price range.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is awesome in this price range.&lt;br&gt;Battery backup is also good.&lt;br&gt;Performance is also awesome.&lt;br&gt;No hanging, no legging.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Waste of money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Facing a mutiple issues with the phone. If you are required to use multiple Apps, don't even think of buying this phone else you will regret&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good, with small patch&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Yes its good, but small painting on phone, which as exactly on the centre of rim.&lt;br&gt;rest is all good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;not the best on this price tag..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Games are not working properly, better to buy Micromax HD, very good phone. Samsung need to improve the hardware and serve the better.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO?pageNumber=5</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;reached @ time&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice packed and very good phone I ever used an I got it within 2 days&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon an transporting services&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its just o K !&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good phone,, everything is fine..soooperb excellent&lt;br&gt; camera..front cam too,,, but i heard b4 buying that samsung phones are getting hanged.. i didnt take care,,bt this phone is too,, some hang somewhere,, its not much good for gaming and huge prcess to do..only a simple phone for a common man.. otherwise sysytem goes hang with lot of apps and prcess&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone &amp;amp; experience with Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ordered for my mom who was upgrading from a basic to a smartphone. Compared prices in all local stores &amp;amp; online - amazon offered the best price!&lt;br&gt;The order arrived in 2 days.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Good phone. Mom is very happy with the performance and wouldn't part with it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;This is a Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is definitely a good one with all its features and specifications as mentioned by Samsung.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pros:&lt;br&gt;Good Features&lt;br&gt;Light weight&lt;br&gt;Clear Sound&lt;br&gt;Good Music&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cons:&lt;br&gt;Not a very good camera... definitely it doesn't meet 5MP expectation if compared with other camera phones of same Mega Pixels.&lt;br&gt;Battery is also weak seems like 1500mAH&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this product is good and fast dispatch in my home i m happy bcz i buy only 11000 rs. and market pries 12500 Rs.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;my first experience with smart pone, which is excellent.&lt;br&gt;Speed is good for multi-tasking. in range of 11K it is a good option&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Returned the product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have not used the product.It was election time and there was a delay with parcel company.But Amazon interacted excellently especially its customer care.I got back money with out any huzzle.Bought the product again from amazon.This time it reached with in few days.This review is for the amazon.I did not start using the phone till now.Will let you know later.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good device at midbudjet price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice look,&lt;br&gt;camera is good for daylight,&lt;br&gt;speed is good for multiple tasking&lt;br&gt;overall is good device for midbudjet range&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First of all i want to say something about who are saying bad about Nokia X.&lt;br&gt;-dont have google play store, camera is 3 mp, only 512 mb ram ....android without playstore no existence etc etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i just wanna say who are saying dese are the chinese mobile promoters or who haven't used android phone,... (Expand)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;I AM THANKFUL TO AMAZON TO GOT RECEIVED PRODUCT THROUGH AMAZON.HOPE DO IN FUTURE&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;OK mobile at this price, has some battery related issues&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery issues -  gets switched off, doesn't get charged properly etc.etc. Otherwise Ok performance. Don't buy from Next Online, very poor after sales response.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone with good features at this price.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased this phone after research of phones in market. I found it is a good choice after using it for one month. I can get good battery backup after setting inbuilt battery saving function. I got 2 days battery backup for my average use. Screen quality is decent and the sound quality too. I like the quality of  Sound through headphone, it's amazing. No lags in general games like Subway surfers, Temple run2, etc if battery saving is off. Battery saving mode reduces game performance. Overall it's a good choice over Sony xperia M &amp;amp; LG L7 II dual P715. I think it's worth to buy because of Good display, Ram 1GB, Internal memory 8Gb and good performance.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsungs good phone but&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good phone by samsung in a budget category. Getting 4.3 screen with 1 GB ram is very good combination&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;however&lt;br&gt;the body is made by cheap material, the screen resolution is not good compare to moto g&lt;br&gt;and off course camera quality is average.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If anyone wants budget phone with good configuration, then go for galaxy core.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;poor power storage&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This item working good but dont keep battery power , maximum power 5 hrs thats all then low battery  , this mobile poor power storage&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review - Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features are fine but would have feel happy if they given flip cover with the handset.&lt;br&gt;I would suggest to go with Grand2 instead of this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;warranty certificate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;warranty certificate &amp;amp; packing material list yet not received.operating manual also not received.kindaly send it as soon as possible.so i utilise it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Price in this site is bit high compare to other site&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Price of this product Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 in this site is bit high compare to other site. This should revise by this site.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not Good nor bad&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Processing is slow&lt;br&gt;After installing few more app&lt;br&gt;its become slow&lt;br&gt;Camera quality is good....&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;br&gt;a&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget Samsung Device - Not worth the money.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy Core is a budget 1GB ram device from samsung released in June 2013. It was a decent device when it was launched,but now,for the price you can get far better devices.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Display : 480 x 800 pixels, 4.3 inches ie only 217 ppi. The screen brightness is not that great,which means it is very difficult to see the screen under sunlight. The viewing angles are good.There is also no light sensor which means Auto brightness feature is not there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Processor : Dual-core 1.2 GHz Cortex-A5 processor. This is no powerhouse Good enough for your day to day tasks,but lags behind the quadcore processors coming with similarly priced devices like Canvas Magnus, Turbo Mini,Xolo Q Series, Moto G etc.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Antutu Benchmark : 7470 ( For a comparison to show how low the performance is, Xolo Q700 scores - 13000, Micromax Turbo Mini - 17000 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Camera : 5 MP , the image quality is not that great. It can't even record 720P HD videos while even many under Rs 8000 devices are able to.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Operating System : Samsung TouchwizUI on top of old Android 4.1 Jellybean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Battery : 1800mAh. This is NOT good enough to take you through one day of moderate use (with internet on). Cheaper Xolo Q700 priced at Rs 8500 ships with a 2400mAh one is to be noted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Verdict : Galaxy Core is not a value for money device in my opinion, as many other devices coming at this price ships with far better performing components and newer Android version. Buy this only if you want a 'branded' budget device and are ok with the issues it comes with.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not a good purchase from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is good but Amazon has DELIVERED A DEFECTIVE PIECE TO ME.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The device heats up and also there is reception problem. The device looses connectivity every now and then.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I hope that Amazon will call me to address my concern.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Please do not buy phones from Amazon!!&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_3_5 " title="3.7 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3.7 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00D8XYAIO</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy Core GT-I8262 (Metallic Blue)</value></title></item></items>