<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a good handset for normal usage of a smartphone. Battery backup is average. Camera is good and the LED flash attached to it is also worth. Apps doing good but always use with memory card inside. Resolution is average. Sound of music player is very good with original head sets. Look is attractive.&lt;br&gt;The price is not at all competitive according to the hand sets available in the market even in lesser price. But if we retain the Samsung brand, the price is then ok.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cdma&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Is this a cdma phone. I am looking for a good cdma smart phone. Please suggest. I have searched some suggest Lenovo.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;My first change to Smart Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I would have given it 41/2 star rating. It  totally met my requirements except that I expected it to be little bigger in size.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;easy purchase of a valuable product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have purchased this beautiful phone for my sister, and she is well satisfied with the features and performance too. I think the phone is one of the good smartphone in this range and it is easy to use and works faster compared to any other branded phone in this range. I also wish to appreciate the quick and smart way of delivery system offered by Amazon to get this product close to my home. Thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb phone.......&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I didnot buy this one from amazon but it is an awesome phone at a price of 8k........&lt;br&gt;It has a bunch of features.....&lt;br&gt;Only problem is battery backup for which is below average. But the phone is really nice cos it never hangs despite of have 768 mb of ram. All in all its a wonderful phone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;smart phone at resonable price..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A phone with so much reasonable price, carries all most evry specification which other costly phone have...a best phone to at low price..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;worth for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i bought it few months ago.&lt;br&gt;this phone works great and camera is very nice.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but poor in battery backup.&lt;br&gt;still worth for the money&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice product but logistics needs improvement&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;a good product from amazon but the packaging and logistic is so bad. items were missing from the pakage. over all a good product and good portal to buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not a standard phone, buy if you don't care about Class&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Not a great piece in this range. Body looks cheap, graphics are too big and simply speaks "I m China made". Not classy.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is a modified version of earlier one.Performance is excellent,quite fast.Battery life is also good if auto sync is kept off.&lt;br&gt;Moderate picture quality,OK for normal photography.One of the best under Rs.10000 smartphone.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=7</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;buy power bank or go for lumia&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Using for 10 days running smoothly battery is worst on wifi only 4 hr surfing. Camera good but Nokia 525 also click decent pic even without flash in lowlights&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;different seller sent the product instead of my chosen one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered my phone from seller called chrome retail because it was owned by tata enterprise. But, I received the product through another seller. The product was in sealed box when i received but, it is hanging up frequently while using and need to restart most of the time. I am not happy because the seller ive chosen has been replaced by amazon without my consent.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Sweet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Really cool. No problems so far. Scratched it already in a week and dropped it thrice, no signs of damage though.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Bharosemand Seva.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Mobile is OK. Aapake Dawra Beja Gaya Mobile Acha hai. BaviShya me Aapase Aur seva ki Aasha Rkhate hai. Thanks.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Potent phone reasonably priced&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone i gave it as a gift to my Brother he is very happy with it looks great and works swiftly,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;BVN&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fine very good service nice working this mobile fantastic my enjoying with this one children very very happy to got data service fastness&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;poor battery backup&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;After using the phone for only 2 weeks what I can say is Poor battery back up..picture quality is not up to the mark(for a 5mp camera)..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good price when compare with other sites&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;fast delevary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;i have recomanded my two of friends and they have bought same mobiles too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;regards,&lt;br&gt;tharun :) :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a good product , the camera is good , the touch is also good .But the ram could have been much better&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;5 star rating for my side&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice mobile. .. Thanks amazon for your quick service. .....&lt;br&gt;keep it up. In future i will recommend your service.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;battery backup is not up to mark.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;within 25 days of purchasing my mobile speaker  got damaged. again i got repaired from service center. i never expect within 25 day  this kind of damage. also battery backup is not up to mark.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A Very Good phone at this range and handy, picture quality is good.. Good service by Amazon. Will shop again.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;GOOD MOBILE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;THIS IS THE BEST MOBILE FOR LOW RANGE WITH ALL FEATURES AND CLARITY SOUND WAS GOOD AND VERY GOOD. AND EARPHONES CLARITY ALSO TOO GOOD.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;GT S7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is very good phone. I am very thankful to amazon.in to dispatched this phone to me safely. Packing is also very good. amazon has to include my city also for COD.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing Phone Samsung S duos 2 You Beauty!!!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone,Excellent features, Touch is very good ,Price is at rock bottom , camera TRUE 5 MP not like any other smart phones.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Great smart phone with in 8000/&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;My views are a under&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its a very small attractive and handy cell phone.&lt;br&gt;Its easy to use and operate&lt;br&gt;Beautiful look&lt;br&gt;Its cost effective&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Product is nice and is delivered in a good condition.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have ordered a black phone but I received a white phone., Anyways white phone is also nice and i want to use it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Working absolutely fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Using this phone since last 2 months. Working excellent.&lt;br&gt;The phone arrived in time and was well packed in a box.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;i am loving it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;awesome phone. awesome services by amazon.in.&lt;br&gt;must buy if you are not a heavy user. recommended for beginners,who have fobia to use touch screen&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;BETTER PHONE BUT NOT THE BEST&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have been using this phone since last one month and I will have to say that its among the top android phones under Rs 10,000/- but Its battery is just useless, drains very fast.I have to charge it twice a day.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;very high price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very low in features for the price in comparison to other brands.nothing special in this phone totally wastage of money&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;neat handling but Hurry to sign on paper, first customer let to see, product is their then u take sign ,&lt;br&gt;Thank U for my review&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Quality of music player is good....touch works well....very useful for skype video calls. ..on the whole a great deal for the price paid if u get it online. ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing budjet phone from samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this phone from amazon after lot of review checks on different websites, i would like to thank amazon for 1 day delivery option, this is my first smart phone, however i would like to tell all the users that this is much better than the rest of the phones available.&lt;br&gt;Only felt sad because there was no screen gaurd, however i'am happy to have this phone in hand touch is responsive.&lt;br&gt;Guys if you are planning to buy any smart phone this should be your first choice provided if you are budjet constraint.&lt;br&gt;happy shopping.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its a good smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;worth for the money that i've a save some amount when comparing to the market price ,&lt;br&gt;and its a good working model with a great camera clarity&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good mobile with reacenable price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Currect price and good perfomence.flash light s vry bright.other vice k. Usage friendly good job keep it up just do it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's a very good phone at low price &amp;amp; nice packaging by the Amazon.in. I thing overall best phone of the price of 8k.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Average&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Little bit slow. Internal space is too low as the camera is 5 pixel. It is worth to that price.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice update on processor&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Less lagging Compared to Samsung galaxy S Duos S7562&lt;br&gt;Display is ok.&lt;br&gt;Nice phone at this price level and ram is ok.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung sDuos 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;All features are fine but while attend a call its hang. As compare Samsung sDuos Volume is little beat low.  I like its Keypad function most.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Item Delivered fast and as per Described&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is cool and exactly what i searched for..Nice combination of various features. direct wiFi, hotspot,flash cam, front cam, OTG support etc..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's has battery problem !! Battery get very over soon . Totally unhappy with this phone !! Actually this is gift for some &amp;amp; that person told me this problem !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;be careful with amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Never book a mobile with amazon . The service is really bad. There are so many websites better than amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i got my phone as gift from my father and mother and its the best smartphone in this range&lt;br&gt;and ithas got almost all features no prob yet encountered superb in specs and in size&lt;br&gt;i recommend buying this strongly&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;GOOD&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I COULD HAVE GIVEN A 5 STAR RATING TO THIS SET, BUT THE BATTERY LIFE IS TOO SHORT, IT WILL BE DIFFICULT TO USE WHEN TRAVELING IN A LONG DISTANCE TRAIN, IN WHICH STILL THERE ARE TRAINS WHICH DOES NOT HAVE PLUG POINT SUPPORT&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Supurb&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I like this mobile because it is compact and it is easy to carry. I gifted this mobile to my wife&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;super shot&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Super amazon&lt;br&gt;ur service is better than any other corrier services i like it ,I congratulated to ur sservices thnks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At first site this phone looks great....and it doesn't get heated event after long time function..i would rate it as best samsung android phone within 10k.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;except battery everything is good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice nice phone, battery is low, In bluetooth tethering secured websites like google not opens. Amazon packing is very good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super quality ,satisfied packing, nice look ,ok ,ok ok, ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok,ok ,ok ok,&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased it and it was working well only thing is battery capacity is not sufficient, otherwise it is good device.&lt;br&gt;samsung must improve the battery capacity for next model&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NOT BAD&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;CHARGING IS SO POOR AND I HAVE MORE BATTERYS SO NOT BAD. IWANT MORE BETTER PRODUCT IN SAMSUNG SMART PHONE.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Gift Piece.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Sirs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Should dare I dare comment the unfailing art in communication and media? The system is cheap and best, specially it gave more value for money.&lt;br&gt;Thanks&lt;br&gt;Manohar&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cheaper than the local distributors' rate..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;8040 rs...&lt;br&gt;this is quite good deal..&lt;br&gt;however, other companies provide many more things in this price..&lt;br&gt;but samsung is again samsung..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Go for it&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Reasonable price, modified version as compare to last model....Increased RAM will surely make this worth...I am happy with this purchase&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best quality&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice i like this product soo cheap and the best quality. Its replacement policy is soo good so i love amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;phone is very good, as per expectation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;very good ,everything is fine.  satisfied by product&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;thanks and regards&lt;br&gt;chirag joshi&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good smartphone in this budget.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;first of all i like amazon's service it's fastest delivery and lower price&lt;br&gt;packaging was very good&lt;br&gt;and now about phone-&lt;br&gt;camera quality is unbelievable(i like it)&lt;br&gt;screen is very clear and sharp.&lt;br&gt;battery backup is very good&lt;br&gt;i'm able to watch HD videos on this device&lt;br&gt;after sale service is very good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone at affordable price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Would definitely recommend buying this phone as it is good price for the specifications given. However the android version could be more latest and there it fails with Motorola phones.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazon.in is the best shopping site .... and samsung galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 great mobile .......... Thanks amazon .......&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=9</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good smartphone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a very good smartphone. It has a very smooth touchscreen.and very good spekers in this smartphone. And no henging problem in this smartphone&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I recently purchased samsung - 7582 it is working simply superb. I advise to take this mobile in your budget.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;2 gt s7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery backup is not so good. other wise phone is very good. Only  50 mints. net surf phone battery fully discharge....main problem is battery.... kindly improved put better battery.I am buy this phone for amazon.in super fast delivery only 2 days received my phone in my office address. amazon courier service is very very good a per the commitment always delivered on time. thank you. but only one request kindly mention correct information for the battery.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great phone at this price. Has not given any problem for the last over 2 months. Before this, I had used Xolo A500, which kept on giving problems.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i like this mobile..my dream mobile now...........................................its looking so cute and comfort........also low cost in many features..&amp;amp; specifications..thats y ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok types phone!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good phone! but cost is too high..it should be priced at 6,500/- incl everything...i paid 8,300/- for this now Nokia X2 is coming with similar specs!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its OK&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;If you are not looking for serious multitasking this phone(Smartphone) is just OK at this price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It opens any applications a little late, due to RAM (less than 1Gb)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lightweight and Android makes it suitable for simpler smartphone usage.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb mobile but battery is minus point&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I m buy this phone for amezon.in superfast dilivery only 2 days recevie my phone in my home. Best picture quality..hi speed no lang but battery is very week..&lt;br&gt;Very week means 3 times charge in day....&lt;br&gt;Only 1 hour net surf phone battery fully discharge....main problem is battery....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;fine&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Super experience with Amazon l am really happy with your amazing online service. Great to buy in your store. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice smartphone for tight budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice cell phone from Samsung, I am using it for 1 wk, till date it is not showing any hanging problem. It is quite fast. And at that price from the seller (around Rs:8000)) it is not a bad smartphone. But in my case the delivery time from amazon was not up to the expectation. . It took 6 days for delivery.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=5</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;niceeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee\&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good mobile small comfortable easy to keep in pocket no hangini fast mobile so no problem in purchase my suggestion it is excee&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cool phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is a very compact phone, its very fast and the touch is excellent.&lt;br&gt;picture quality is good.&lt;br&gt;cost is very reasonable&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome product!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great product...good work by amazon...worth buy below 10k..recommend every one to buy it...no problem at all and good service by amazon..!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;VERY GOOD PRODUCT AT LOW COST&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;VERY GOOD PRODUCT AT LOW COST&lt;br&gt;SAMSUNG BASIC PHONES IT IS THE BEST ITEM I HAD EVER USED FOR SIMPLE USE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone for average user&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent Phone,good service by amazon......&lt;br&gt;only constraint is RAM, but if you don't use High end gaming...Its worth&lt;br&gt;I bought from amazon Just Rs. 8300, however market price was Rs.9500 (Approx)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good amazing Samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good phone in budget. ..smartphone..................I like the phone camera and speed of processor. ...thanks amazone. ....thanx samsung ..like...good..samsung...xjfkffk cdeodei dwkssi&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not worth Paying 8000&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its not worth paying 8k.&lt;br&gt;Lots of other good smart phones having better specification are available in this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best ever price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased this product by reviewing the price over 8 to 10 online stores.  I got this product at the best price with neatly packed and reached with in 4 days. thanks amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome mobile phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I just loved this phone.Probably one of the best smartphones below 10k..Only problem is with Battery backup.but still I am satisfied.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;never buy product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;features r good but worst battery life  only 10 to 12 hrs standby time. not recomended to purchase. never buy.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=10</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;REDUCE THE PRICE TO 7K TO COMPETE WITH MOTO E&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Moto E is offering a lot for 7k,like CG Glass 3,1GB RAM,latest OS and a bigger screen.,Samsung wins in terms of rear Cam and bundled accessories.But for a smartphone user top priorities will always be the processor and RAM.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I had bought mobile online for the first time.&lt;br&gt;And It was a great experience.&lt;br&gt;I had received a good deal for this mobile at amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Meets all my expectations and beyond .has features and camera with flash to give great pictures.a must possession for my pocket.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;i give it three star&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;ok . it meet my expectation.....i give it 3 star...ok . it meet my expectation.....i give it 3 star...ok . it meet my expectation.....i give it 3 star...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;packing excellent and in time reached better than price in markets thanks amazon.in i request who were buy more items announce special gifts&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice budget phone .. I gifted my Dad this on this 62nd Birthday. Yes for him it was little difficult to start with Android and Touch Screen.. But He is happy with Camera and over all performance of the phone. Buy I see now the price is 500 less..Not good ;(&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice phone at nice price.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;However found camera a little low as compare to other smart-phone of other brands. otherwise performance of the phone is great.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Gati is worst courier service for small town s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Gati courier service is worst in my city. Product is fine . Price drop comming soon. Packaging was good. Moto e is better&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got it at the best rate when compared to the retailers.  No complaints.&lt;br&gt;The screen resolution and touch sensitivity are good.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cheap and best phone from samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i had purchased three phone of Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-7582 and happy with the results. This the cheap and best phone and has almost everything that a user must have in the price range.  The camera quality of the phone is excellent and the videos played on this phone are also good.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K?pageNumber=6</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;This is upgraded version previous S Duos Best Android Phone in this range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;***First Dont compare this phone with High Range bcos its a upgrade to previous version Galaxy S Duos s7562 *** A budget phone is different from High Range phone.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;comparison it only with budget phone and the features and price quoted.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Features :&lt;br&gt;1. 4*inch TFT Display ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;2. WVGA 480*800 pixels resolution with 16M color depth ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;3. Dual Sim ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;4. Weight 118g ( previous version 120g )&lt;br&gt;5. Dual core 1.2 ghz cortex A9 ( previous version single core 1ghz with cortex A5 )&lt;br&gt;6. Android V4.2 jellybean ( previous Android v4 icecream sandwich )&lt;br&gt;7. Rear camera 5mp cmos and front 0.3p VGA ( same as previous )&lt;br&gt;8. Battery 1500mah ( same as previous version )&lt;br&gt;9. HD (720) Video Playback &amp;amp; Recording 30fps&lt;br&gt;10. GPU Videocore IV ( previous version its Adreno 200 )&lt;br&gt;11. Ram 768mb ( same as previous )&lt;br&gt;12. 4gb internal and Microsd upto 64 Gb ( Previous its 32 Gb )&lt;br&gt;13. Priced at 10k in Flipkart ( previous version 9k )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Finally The changes from previous version not much but plays a major part in performance as previous version has many drawbacks in performance :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1. Processor dual core 1.2 ghz cortex A9&lt;br&gt;2. Video recording 720p&lt;br&gt;3. Os Android v4.2 jellybean&lt;br&gt;4. Videocore IV GPU&lt;br&gt;5. Sdcard Upto 64Gb&lt;br&gt;and some little more&lt;br&gt;6. Ram must have been updated to 1gb but you dont need it since its dual core and you may not worry like before. 768mb is more than sufficient for moderate use with apps and games.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;100% you wont have lag and worries compared to its previous version based on updated configurations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Conclusion :&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Since the previous version s7562 had many drawbacks in terms of performance , lag , restart , battery down , and many other faults .... This version is just a rectification for those faults and a pretty Moderate update and a price tag that is optimized to capture market when compared to other range at similar configurations ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you search for a mobile at 10k at such configuration and i would suggest to go with Samsung Galaxy sDuos 2 s7582 and you can also update the Android version later.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard – 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu – 11900+  ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 – 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Probably one of the best smartphones below 10k. A must buy if that's anyone's budget. Very Happy with the set.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;What u want everything is here. So dont wait get 1 else not regret.&lt;br&gt;Only crap is d 768 mb ram which could be 1 gb&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i have ordered and got this product with in 48hrs and i am very much happy about product quality and packing quality.&lt;br&gt;i am sure i will suggest my friends to buy from amazon and i am fully satisfied&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;amazon...  amazing.....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;quality and service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good quality product dispatched in 2 days. Very good mobile and i bought for my elder brother, He is happy and the price is cheaper than any other website,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;I AM THANKFUL TO AMAZON TO GOT RECEIVED PRODUCT THROUGH AMAZON.HOPE DO IN FUTURE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;cheap rate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome product purchased for cheap rate compared to all other online stores. ..&lt;br&gt;This product works very good. I recommend this product and amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I almost searched all the online stores,  But Amazon was the cheapest.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Thanks Amazon for your quick delivery...&lt;br&gt;Now about the product.  Look is decent, Camera captures decent pictures.  Only problem is with Battery backup.  But i installed easy Battery saver, which manages the battery power accross all the apps.  Inbuilt memory seems to be less, but still you can expand by SD card.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;BEST &amp;amp; EXCELLENT&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;EXCELLENT, QUICK DELIEVERY&lt;br&gt;PRODUCT IS GOOD&lt;br&gt;BEST EXPERIENCE&lt;br&gt;I WILL DEFINATELY RECOMMEND MY FRIENDS, FAMILY&lt;br&gt;OVERALL VERY GOOD EXPERIENCE&lt;br&gt;THANKING YOU&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><rating><value>&lt;span class="swSprite s_star_4_0 " title="4.2 out of 5 stars"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4.2 out of 5 stars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</value></rating><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YSW6K</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Black)</value></title></item></items>