<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone under 10k Budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice look as other Samsung phone.&lt;br&gt;Work with ease without any issue, Battery backup is not so good as expected if u will use for both calling &amp;amp; data it will give backup of 7-8 hrs.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good fone in its range..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;hi ,samsung mobiles are reliable as always. performance is a little more good than of samsung s duos which was ganging some times. Moto E is a good choice considering features and 1 gb RAM; if u think u can rely on google's new motorola.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;happy to purchase&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good performance&lt;br&gt;Beautiful piece of art&lt;br&gt;Recommend to purchase&lt;br&gt;Reliable brand&lt;br&gt;Good after sales&lt;br&gt;Good battery life&lt;br&gt;Comfortable fits your palm&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;White Magic galaxy s&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;amazing value for money. I love the simplicity and design of the Galaxy S. Is absolutely robust and smooth for basic use.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;gudd&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good mobile that fits my budget... everything works fine..browsing is soo fast. but the problem s about the battery.. It drains quickly even if I don't use it...no app to sd ext support...These proml&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good.But They took a while to reach and failed to post about the shipment.Overall Good Product.Thats all folks.Thank You.God bless.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;just few days ago i received this phone.Amazon provides satisfactorily service.thanks  .provide service in future also.there is no any problem yet.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Everything as expected&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got the phone really quickly.. and it is well sealed. and service is very fast. we can rely on amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good entry level phone from Samsung. But Moto E has given this model a tough challenge.&lt;br&gt;This phone is reasonably good. Call quality is good. camera is decent.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool phone in your budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Awesome phone with really cool features. Low price and great features. Touch is very smooth and camera quality is good.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=4</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;waste&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I think that it is good one.but it was not good and it was very slow and hanging so it was d wste phne firstly i saw so i am suggesting d pupil to avoid buying s duos 2&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone nd god price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice phone nd god price,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,i m facing sm prblm with hanging,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,,but still is nice phone with white colur and slim madal.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent usage of mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is an excellent mobile having all the features required by me. Since it has dual SIM feature, there is absolutely no problem in switching over.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;duplicate....warranty problem from amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;duplicate...warranty problem from  service..so dont purchase from amozon...first thing is that no samsung india warranty..only seller waranty.....so problem r there in seller warranty&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;wonderfull creation&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;s duos 2  is the return of s duos......with lot of xtra features.....  battery backup is good than b4. colour quality is better than s dous 2..... all the way u will be satisfied than other samsung set arround ur budget 10,000. its wonderful.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;smart and intelligent&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I suggest this phone for users who must need a dual sim mobile cause you will get Lumia 520/525 at this price range and they are better options(Moto E is not in the list for its HIGH SAR VALUE) if you settle yourself to single sim and don't get bothered by those famous shortcomings of Windows OS.But the different types of prepaid plans as well as Internet plans forcing we Indians to have 2 different sims and here wins S Duos 2 with all its rectifications from its previous version S Duos. No lag till now. Camera good.Music in headphone superb but supplied headphones are waste ,have your own.Display good.Battery should have been at least 1800mAh .&lt;br&gt;It lasts 7/8 hrs in heavy use of internet but 2 days in standby and 1 day when you only use this to make voice calls.&lt;br&gt;Hope you enjoyed my real review not specification base reviews that are very common now.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;very good entry level phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;has all the functionality needed on an android.&lt;br&gt;No performance lag, very good value for money. The memory on board is just 4GB, so I installed an additional 4 GB&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Problem with ringtone volume and speaker volume&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice phone for this budget&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I have faced the problems in Ringtone volume and speaker volume which automatically goes low&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good brand name but shoddy product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;First I would like to thank Amazon.in for prompt refund of  Samsumg Galaxy S Duos GT-S7582.  The product was not at all up to the mark especially the brand name of Samsung.  The camera of the set returned by me was very poor.  It was poorer than Star Pro.  I am unable to understand why the customer will buy this if the same is available for 5000/- (approx) which has better camera.  Either the product was bad or it was reserved for online customers.  Really a bad experience for Samsung customers.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Worth purchasing..very handy mobile phone at such a nice price tag..thanks to amazon.in, will continue to purchase some other products also from amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=3</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;satisfied .. :)&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I hesitated first to Order Mobile online.,. but now Im happy with my order.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Im really satisfied with product, Thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very wonderful phone consider buying it again for my wife. it is elegant and almost have all the features which are required in smartphones&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Phone is very good But donot buy it from Amazon ... you will never get your product on time .. but delay with 4 -5 days .. with the pathetic service of Amazon ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;FlipKart is better than this .. wahiyat service provider ....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;perfect handset for women&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;bought it for my wife. she is a first time smartphone user. phone is perfect in size for easy handling and carrying in yr wallet. price is quite competetive looking to the features it offers. Best Buy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;best price and good quality best cash on delavarey tanq amazon india best onlion sellare but some item price deffranice&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;happy with the phone..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;thanks a ton to amazon for its service, i received my package all safe... its a good phone to buy at this price range.. had a good shopping experience.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Feedback&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was a gift for somebody i didn't use it ,other wise handset is very good i had check the reviews&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;feedback&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Dear Sir&lt;br&gt;SAIRAM.&lt;br&gt;AQt the outset i must say that the mobile phone i purchased through your esteemed organisation id giving a lot of problems&lt;br&gt;1. it gets hung very often&lt;br&gt;2.the screen stats rotating by itself even without touching the phone&lt;br&gt;3. whilst in phone mode sometimes # sign is displayed various times&lt;br&gt;4. with result of the above battery consumption is higher and i have to recharge it twice a day.&lt;br&gt;Kindly advice what action i must take.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;not upto level&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;camera quality in not 5mp as written. It is abt only 2mp.Operating system is not satifactory.Battery getting very low very quickly.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SUPPLYING WITHOUT QC CHECK. PLS. OPEN THE BOX AS EARLY AS POSSIBLE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;RECD AND CHECKED ITS WORKING.&lt;br&gt;GIVEN AS BIRTHDAY GIFT ON 8.06.14.&lt;br&gt;HEATING PROBLEM,BATTERY EXHAUSTED EVEN AFTER SWITCHED OFF WITHIN 4-6 HRS.&lt;br&gt;10.06.14 WENT TO SAMSUNG SERVICE CENTRE THEY ARE TELLING TH IC IS FAULTY WE WILL CHANGE THE IC YOU COME NEXT DAY,WE CANT REPLACE THE PHONE.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;IF IN 3 DAYS YOUR IC IS FAULTY WHY YOUR QC IS NOT RESPONSIBLE?&lt;br&gt;IF IAM PAYING FOR NEW PRODUCT HOW CAN YOU GIVE ME REFURBISHED PRODUCT?&lt;br&gt;PLS DO THE NEEDFUL AMAZON.................&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=5</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung s7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this one is nice product by smasung and really enjoyable product its nice and good&lt;br&gt;and also good camera and speed&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Thanks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ok kind of product. Battery is the problem for all Samsung mbls needs to be improved.  Rest I'd fine. Thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;about my mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is very good to get this mobile because i needed it &amp;amp; very useful for me. i like it......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;I got wrong product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I ordered Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 7582 pouch, but i received a wrong product i.e , Samsung Trend GT-S7392 Pouch&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice&lt;br&gt;Nice service&lt;br&gt;nice online service&lt;br&gt;good service ,&lt;br&gt;Nice phone Godd service by amazon pleasure to buy in amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice but battery back up poor  camera rear good front not good internal memory not enough because down load any application system slow&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is worth the money spent. Good performance and seems to be stable. S Duos 2 is far better than the S Duos.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good option&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its a decent phone to carry or to work with.it suits to a person who use a smartphone for confined purposes.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesum&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice and brilliant !&lt;br&gt;It is good to be in touch with Amazon now waiting for Citi Bank cash back offer.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;My Mobile was hange so,please advice for this.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I need halp Regarding mobile hange,&lt;br&gt;  I have not down load application more than two &amp;amp; three but its hange,&lt;br&gt;  So,please advice me what can I do.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=2</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Asking for reducing the rate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The mobile is attracted and good.It has good features but its too costly.I wish you can reduce the rate to Rs.7000 Please !!! I Love this phone.I want to buy this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;phone is good to use. but it crased sometime while playing game&lt;br&gt;but it is good phone in this budget. camera and net speed is very good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok type&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;not bad not good...in this money better stuff from samsung... but only one problem all the samsung sets looks alike same...samsung should think about it...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Ok it is working and good packing, and I like much about your packege, with that product I may satisify.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;worst smart phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Worst phone... super slow... poor battery... hangs prob on every step... even when the device is hardly loaded with apps&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SATSFACTORY&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product is good and also cheap as compared to market. Amazon a good sight to shop in online shopping.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;service for Amazon.in&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best service for Amazon.in. more than item launched try to amazon website.&lt;br&gt;எனது கனவு நிறைவேறியது குறைந்த விலையில். Thanks for Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung galaxy s duos 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i brought this phone 1 mnth ago very bad phone of this price .&lt;br&gt;main reasons&lt;br&gt;1. very hang during using internet and even open messages&lt;br&gt;2.charge didnt lasting . need of 3 times charging per day&lt;br&gt;3. only 512 mb ram&lt;br&gt;4.i had a serious doubt that this product from amazon is a second quality item .&lt;br&gt;5. vry slw performance&lt;br&gt;micromax canvas doodle 3 is bttr than this&lt;br&gt;samsung mobiles are also hanging evrywhere&lt;br&gt;please didnt buy this product . plzzz dnt buy that&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I purchased this product by reviewing the price over 8 to 10 online stores.  I got this product at the best price with neatly packed and reached with in 4 days. thanks amazon&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;littel slow&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice mobile for easy handeling for use. Music is very nice ane speed is also very good. Battery is good&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;DHAMAKA FOR AMAZON&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked the shoppibg the amazon.com I satisfied the product recived today is working this is nicely &amp;amp; me suggested by all friend for shopping the amazon. Com&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great value for Your Bucks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value for money deal;) One can not have better than this product from the house of Samsung trough Amazon.&lt;br&gt;Thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;thanks for timing deliver&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i got Samsung safely thanks for it  i gave it to my wife for my wedding 6 year anniversary good to see smile on my wife face&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Worst&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It lags, UI is not smooth, camera is worst. At first, battery life is good but now it becomes worst...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;quick delivery&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Quick delivey and best price with right product. I hv gifted to my relative but not checked bill wether its genuine or not.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice amazon service....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice amzone service....thanks amazon...................&lt;br&gt;pls inform me discount offers&lt;br&gt;pls pls ...............nece my 2 phone ...service best amazon....&lt;br&gt;thanks  .....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Amazing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;i got this product immediately after ordering this, it was well packed, and working good..&lt;br&gt;this product is worth... i recommend this..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Purchase&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's hang while playing Subway surf. It should have 1 gb ram.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Worth buying in this price range if you compare it with Moto E.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome smartphone at smart price luckily to me&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this galaxy s duos 2 is best phone at the range of 8000.i purchased it at 8099 which is the best price uptil now.&lt;br&gt;advantages of this fone-&lt;br&gt;1.best quality camera&lt;br&gt;2.best touch screen&lt;br&gt;3.best speaker sound quality&lt;br&gt;4.good hi speed processor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;disadvantages.&lt;br&gt;1.not able to use internet from slot 2.i don't know the problem.but i am trying to sort it out&lt;br&gt;2.not good for downloading too many games as RAM is only 768MB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;but overall this phone is best as we are not getting any branded phone at this range.samsung rocks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its fantastic&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Fulfills all my requirements. Its value for money. Service levels of Amazon is also excellent.  Price is also competitive. All the best.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=7</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;worth of money&lt;br&gt;i got this product with two days only.thanks to amazon.we had some good sellers like DUKAAN RESOURCES PRIVATE LIMITED .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;fully dissapointed ....&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I did not get the above mentioned product. i waited for 3 to 4 week. Now i have reorder it through amazon itself. that was 2 week before.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Flipkart use to call and tell the reason for cancellation. Amazon can learn a lot from companies like Flipkart and SnapDeal.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Genuine Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Mobile was very good. The product has not tampering. Very Fast shipping and the product is as expected and in proper working condition. Very much satisfied.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Quite a good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got this phone on very reasonable rate compare to market prices, that's why i prefer amazon. If your requirements are quite normal then this phone is worth buying in its class.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good One for he money you spent !!!!!&lt;br&gt;---- --- -- -- ---- ---- ---- --- --- --- --- --&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;phone mouthpiece not working&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;phone mouthpiece not working just after 5 days&lt;br&gt;Battery draining like water under 50 degree heat&lt;br&gt;Look for other option&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White). Good Product in this range of price. Looks nice.&lt;br&gt;Better performance than GT-S7562&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;In my point of view.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good piece. every thing is there in the phone. i have bought it for my friend and he likes so much.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I Loved it Amazon product it's so awsome thanks to amazon team for giving this nice product to me ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;super quality ,satisfied packing, nice look ,ok ,ok ok, ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok,ok ,ok ok,&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=6</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;best for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good to buy &amp;amp; best use of your invested money.&lt;br&gt;good to buy &amp;amp; best use of your invested money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Latest Anroid Application . Budget less than Rs 10000.I am satisfied.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good .Item received ,Speedy Dispatch .Good Features. Good Touch Screen .Latest Anroid Application . Budget less than Rs 10000.I am satisfied.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone for me becoz it's work without hanging...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Phone for me becoz it's work without hanging...&lt;br&gt;so finally i purchase this phone working toooo goood...Really trust me..&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good deal on Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is real a good product,its nice 3G connectivity .&lt;br&gt;Gifted to My Wife. now she is all the way using internet.&lt;br&gt;Thank you Samsung and Amazon to get me this deals&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Its ok, but the battery back up wasn't good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its ok, but the battery back up wasn't good.&lt;br&gt;its ok ,,,but for this price new mobiles are coming this days you can go for that...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very Nice i love amazon.in&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Expect the Unexpected Prices from amazon great to have a shoping sitting at home l love it guyssssss very nice&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Thanks&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I'm got easier from you amazon .In thanks I purchased a new phone easily thanks once again my phone good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;s7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;VERY BEST PHONE  BEST DISPLAY,sound camera mice touch charging very fast . . . . . .. . . .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;9413421620&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Great service.... great phone at lower price. ... will be in touch whenever I will purchase some or other thing. ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice product &amp;amp; nice service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;very good service AMAZON AND HELP FULLY CUSTOMER SERVICE&lt;br&gt;I WISE TO GROW IN FUTURE&lt;br&gt;special THANKS  Amazon TEAMS PEOPLE&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=9</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;A product worth its price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;In the price range, the phone is good. Though had Moto E come out a little earlier, i would have gone for it. Otherwise, this phone is pretty ok.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good mobile at this cost. Samsung hardware quality is best compare to any other mobile hardware. 5 MP camera is gr8....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone in this budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Firstly I was worried about this phone's battery backup. But its battery backup is fine. With normal use, battery can last upto 2 days. This phone provide nice picture quality, Flash, fast processing and also all the features of android phone. This is really a good phone in this budget.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I face 3-4 days delay in delivery of this phone due to network issue of Amazon, but it can happen with any organization.&lt;br&gt;I must recommend Amazon to improve their delivery services.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Easy to handle size and price with all required features. Very good for my key requirements&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-- Size&lt;br&gt;-- Features&lt;br&gt;-- Price&lt;br&gt;Performance is good so far!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Never, ever buy it.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Hello,&lt;br&gt;I have been using this phone for almost 9 months and I can say with utmost certainty that its my worst purchase, ever. This phone will soon start hanging 20-30 times a day, its incredibly slow and it will become unbearable to use. And its not just me. I know 2 other friends who have the same experience with this phone. I am requiting you, PLEASE  DONT buy this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Dont buy this mobile ...it is updated vergion of Samsung Gt7562&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I brought GT-S7562 6 month before ....&lt;br&gt;Battery backup is very weak and camera quality is not good in comparison to other ...&lt;br&gt;When play game like temple run .. Subway surf than suddenly its being hang ....&lt;br&gt;In my opinion  dont waste your money to buy that type of mobile ...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;AMAZON ROCKS&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good smart phone &amp;lt; ₹10,000........but guys also check out new MOTO E......got my order with in 3 days...amazon u guys rock.......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;if one is looking for Branded good budget Phone...u can buy this....I am satisfied customer ....Camera is also very good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;os is not working properly&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;os is not working properly...can i xchange the product...please change my mobile immediatly i want another piece&lt;br&gt; required?where i can exchange it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;service is no good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;battery packup is very low&lt;br&gt;and not take reverse pick up&lt;br&gt;and No Responce me&lt;br&gt;so I give this comment&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=11</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;battery life is not adequage&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;the battery life is not adequate enough even for 6 hrs in day time and need frequent recharging to keep it alive&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice product of samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is a good product of company and it provided me by amazon very instantly. thanks to amazon to provide it for us.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;It's Good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am happy with my Samsung. It's simply good in it's range. Screen along with Camera quality are good when compare with other phones in the same range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A very basic smartphone for all your needs.&lt;br&gt;smooth touchscreen, very little lag, has almost all the features for a good mid level smart phone. internal memory is a bit low.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for Movey product !&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Satisfied with Amazon's prompt service :)&lt;br&gt;I received the product within 24 hours and packed well.&lt;br&gt;Well done Amazon,keep it up :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good product ; But now you can buy Moto E for Rs.7000 with great specs with latest Android OS go for it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;all nice and sending option also super.amajan pls keepit up .dont send by private couriyars please&lt;br&gt;pls pls pls pls.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very disappointed when i see 1500 rs less MRP of this phone just 10 days after i purchase it :(&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;exellent features reasonable priced&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;exellent features reasonable priced great product&lt;br&gt;samsung has done well with dual core processor&lt;br&gt;great experience must buy . ,&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Because it is samsung product and within the budget and as good as smart phone and very easy to use and i bought it from Amazon India and these guys are very fast in delivering the product anywhere in India.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=14</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this model is .cute n tiny. very handy with all facilities, good to  carry n handle meeting all my requirements. Good to have.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Mini Core Duos&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nic phone in dis  range ..it z mini core duos...considering RAM , ROM  n led flash camera ( primary n secondary)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome experience&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it was an good exp with buying &amp;amp; the mobile usage as well.&lt;br&gt;I would surely recommend this to my friends.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone @ this price point&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I have boroght his phone for 8.6K with 10% cash back, with this price it will be a good by as compared to Moto E.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Pricing&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This was a gift to my daughter. Her first phone &amp;amp; we did not want it to be over 4" size. All in our family are Samsung users. The easy accessibility to Samsung's ASS is the main reason to stick to this brand.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Just a few weeks later Moto-E was launched, which is a whole lot cheaper and technically better.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My name is sherebanu cutleriwala.  Samsung galaxy duos 2 is excellent phone and Amazon website is very good in their services.  I  very happy with them.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its a very good phone at good price. it has all the features.good to go for this phone. :  d&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;bang for buck..&lt;br&gt;it hass good camera 5 pixeler&lt;br&gt;fast processor&lt;br&gt;Good bright display&lt;br&gt;good for dailey use&lt;br&gt;must phone for budget oriented peoples&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Problem&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;My Phone facing lots of problem, bcozz of MMI code error&lt;br&gt;so i need Customer care no or local service centre....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;good service&lt;br&gt;good quality&lt;br&gt;good packing&lt;br&gt;good communication&lt;br&gt;good price&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;allover paisa wasul product and sevice by amazone. thanks amazone&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=12</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;NO Manual, how to operate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;No mANUAL how to operate this phone. It is impossible to learn as most of the people have no time to teach.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superb mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;excelent mobile and 4 gb internal memory expandble32 gb so super mobile and batary charging is very low net using in 2hours only running.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Item ! Great Price !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this phone for my father &amp;amp; I think its a good entry level phone for new (Android) users !&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;superlike&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's a very good phone which suits in budget.&lt;br&gt;Amazon provides u the best deal to buy and overall cheap rates compared to other online shopping sites&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Safe Buy with Decent performance&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a powerful handset at an affordable price tag. Unfortunately it cannot save apps on external storage (though rooting will solve this issue). The Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is a better option in the dual core category(in the price range).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Up- Side&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Looks&lt;br&gt;Perfectly fits in hand&lt;br&gt;Good Display&lt;br&gt;Impressive camera&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Down-Side&lt;br&gt;Battery&lt;br&gt;Gets hanged at times&lt;br&gt;touch screen&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;this phone is very bad hanging problem and incoming call not recived hanging and msg type ram is very low bad phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;bhai jo ye phone le raha ho mat lena gatiya phone hai yakeen karna mai aap ko phasa nahi raha hu bas baato par yakeen karna&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;ok &amp;amp;nok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;ok but not best touch is not good smart phone ki baat hi nahi hai  ok hai parbest nahi hai&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good phone at this rate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone..good camera result.. at this price i recomend this phone is excellent..&lt;br&gt;Amazon u guyz..rocks&lt;br&gt;That i can say goood mob&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellent phone delivered in good condition by Amazon&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I got the phone in excellent coNdition. It is a best phone in this price range. Display and processing speed is ver good. Camera quality is awesome. I like the feature of adfing voice in the picture. Some features are not in even grand 1 and core.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Must buy. A budget &amp;amp; full featured phone...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Such an outstanding phone. Good design &amp;amp; build quality. A full featured phone. 5 mega pixle auto focus camera with full hd shooting result is up to expectations. Hd videos are supported in this phone. Android 4.2.2 , 4 Gb internal with around 2 gb for usage &amp;amp; expandable memory upto 64gb &amp;amp; 768mb ram on the box but 717 mb ram in the phone but still no issues of hanging i face.&lt;br&gt;If you want budget &amp;amp; featured pack phone than my advice to you to go with this device , i dont think you'll regret after buying this beauty.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=10</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good appearance.&lt;br&gt;Easy to operate.&lt;br&gt;Worth its price&lt;br&gt;The features provided are quite adequate.&lt;br&gt;Nice look.&lt;br&gt;Battery life good.&lt;br&gt;Good camera performance.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;MY DISLIKE&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;CAN ,T STORE APPS TO SD CARD . HANGING PROBLEM . WI FI CONNECTIVITY POOR . SATISFACTORY , VALUE FOR&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;but got in a broken condition&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Xcellnt response...nice service..nice packing..but the handset was damaged......but the customer support is excellent nd return policy is also very good&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;NIce Phone By Samsung&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I use this phone and it's so nIce, i bought second one from amazon and till now no problem - refer to buy it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very very satisfactory purchase.I am well satisfied with price and the quality. Hope to deal again with amazon. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;its awsome!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is gud phone i m loving it.internet speed on 3g good.overall its not a ghate ka souda on 8635&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very good phone enjoying it i am posting with this phone only you should check out this phone i am happy with it. Unlike other samsung phones it do not hang has every feature one need. If you think that screen is small i would say its the best size for a phone if you want bigger than you should get tablet but not a phone. Very good speed on 3g i am getting 0.5mbps on bsnl 3g and 1mbps on reliance 3g&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome product in cheap rate compare to flip kart and other side&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Every Product of amazon is too good courier facility is also good, it provide articals in cheap rate .  if you are buying from other side once visit amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The product received as per expectation.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White) received within the time as per expected quality standard. thanks&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Got it at a very good price. Rs. 8300. Plus 10 percnt cash back. Samsung stores were selling it at 9700&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=13</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard – 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu – 11900+  ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 – 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Budget Samsung Phone - You can buy better products for this price range though.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 is an upgrade to their earlier budget phone,Galaxy S Duos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Display and Build Quality&lt;br&gt;This has 4 inch TFT display. The screen resolution 480 x 800 pixels is poor(~233 ppi pixel density) considering most phones coming at this price range ships with a qHD display at least.The viewing angles are good. The build quality and the design of the device is almost same as the old Galaxy S Duos. Plastic.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Processor, GPU, Ram and Performance&lt;br&gt;It is powered by a Cortex A9 dual core processor combined with a Broadcom VideoCore IV HW GPU.It only has 768MB ram of which only 360MB ram is availabe for application use. This combination under performs when comparing to the quadcore mediatek devices coming at this price range. This perhaps is not that visible in your day to day normal activities,but visible in benchmarks and while trying to play HD videos.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Operating System&lt;br&gt;This is running on 4.2 Jellybean under the hood. Like any other samsung device it has the same UI - Touchwiz Interface which is quite heavy and lags when you have a lot of apps installed and are running in the background.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Benchmark Scores&lt;br&gt;Quadrant Standard – 3200+ ( Similarly priced Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 5900+ )&lt;br&gt;AnTuTu – 11900+ ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 17000+ )&lt;br&gt;Nenamark 2 – 55 fps ( Canvas 2.2 A114 scores 56 )&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Camera and Media&lt;br&gt;5 MP shooter on the back is like any other device's camera at this price range - average.It gets very grainy in low ligh conditions. 1080P video recording is NOT supported. The front camera is a only VGA.&lt;br&gt;This device cant play 1080P videos. Even using Mxplayer S/W rendering mode,1080P videos didn't run smoothly at all. Most Mediatek quadcore devices can play 1080P videos out of the box.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Storage&lt;br&gt;You CANNOT move/install apps on to the sdcard.So many big games cannot be even installed on this device.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Battery&lt;br&gt;Very disappointing.Only 1500mAH battery is included which cant even last a day ( average use ). Other devices shipping at this price range offers far better battery. For eg Xolo Q700 - 2400mAH.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-&amp;gt; Verdict&lt;br&gt;This is a good Samsung budget device,better than the old Galaxy S Duos,but keep in mind that other devices coming at this price range have far better specs and performance is better than this device. However one advantage it has over other devices is Samsung have reliable service centers all over india.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Decent buy...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Not the best smartphone in this price range especially after the launch of moto E but gets the job done...&lt;br&gt;Biggest con : lags a lot&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent Phone /Good Call Volume&lt;br&gt;Samsung S Duos 2 - S7582&lt;br&gt;I Purchased it from other Online Website .&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Feature Specifications:-&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1)Real RAM working in Task Manager :- 717 MB&lt;br&gt;2)ROM:- 4 GB&lt;br&gt;Out of which System Storage :-1.82 Gb (We Can't Use it) , 2.18 Gb Remaining Storage is User Available .&lt;br&gt;3)Dual Core Processor&lt;br&gt;4)Boot time :- 25 Sec only&lt;br&gt;5)Good Battery Backup&lt;br&gt;6)Good Graphics&lt;br&gt;6)Run Temple run 2 &amp;amp; Subway surf without lag&lt;br&gt;7)Support HD Videos.&lt;br&gt;8)Good Camera&lt;br&gt;9)Looks like High end S4 phone&lt;br&gt;10)Android Version :- 4.2.2. Jelly Bean&lt;br&gt;11) Overall Very fast &amp;amp; Excellent Phone&lt;br&gt;My Rating to this phone in 10 K Budget :- 10/10&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very Important Feature :- Very High Earpiece Volume / Call Volume&lt;br&gt;In addition to High call volume , Samsung give a option "Adapt Sound" in Settings&lt;br&gt;which can further increase call volume according to your hearing capability&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Detailed Technical Specifications&lt;br&gt;Internal Storage&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;SD CARD - Up gradable upto 64 gb&lt;br&gt;Internal Storage : 2.18 GB ---&amp;gt;268 mb used ; 1.9 gb free&lt;br&gt;Available Storage : 1.89 GB&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;RAM&lt;br&gt;Total RAM : 716 MB ; Available Ram : 205 Mb ( 27 %) ; 502 Mb used&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CPU Architecture ; ARM Cortex A9 1.20 GHZ&lt;br&gt;GPU : Broadcom VideoCore IV HW&lt;br&gt;Clock Speed ; 312 Mhz -1.20 Mhz ; Core 0 :- 800 MHZ ; Core 1 1200 MHZ&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Resoultion : 480 x800&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Saurabh Mathur&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Quite satisfied&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Features n more no. Of apps r supported within a genuine price....dats too gud...except one drawback of less battery backup&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;best online service i recieved ever&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Its verey good to receive the order quickly and the product is very satisfactory. Here after i will reccommend amazon to my frnds for the best online shopping&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Very well packed. Product as described in the picture.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The product reached on time. Well packed. The item was as described on the product page. Working fine. Thank you.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SAMSUNG GALAXY S DUOS 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazing product by samsung.good screen,processor,ram and camera.it runs hassle free specially when you play games like temple run or sub way surf.Excellent features,i fully satisfied.Good battery back up,it last for one and half day if you dont active your wifi,internet etc always,keep your brighteness low during net connet for better backup.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;the phone is fine but not the price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;just after 15 days..the phone was available at 900 rs less than the price i purchased it for. Rest the phone is cool.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Best Phone in Mid-Range. Meets my requirements. But price when down from 8.5k to 7.8k within a week is disappointing.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;a worthy successor but not worth the price though!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;samsung again does what it does best, launching new iterations of previous flagship. the phone revives its S series' reputation but fails to compete! a bit overpriced, specs not worthy... doesn't promise the bang for your buck!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;grt mob&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;galaxy s duos 2 is one of the best mob in galaxy series made by samsung.nice picture quality with 5mpwith flash.dual core prosessor is very good performing.i like this mob pick again n again&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Must buy&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Very nice and at a great price. Thank u amazon. Excellent packing. There is a myth about back date phones on the internet. But i recd. this phone with April 2014 manufacturing. So nothing as such. Please click buy button and enjoy&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent phone in this price range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Excellent looks, nice camera, good return on money. for this price range no other branded phone is available. from my side four out of five.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Best deal &amp;amp; best price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The packaging of the product was very good and I got my Product within 7 days. Very good service from amazon.in.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Product and superb features&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am very satisfied with the product and its Delivery and Packaging also. This mobile provides all the features and premium look available within its price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice product&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it ia a nice product but the cost is too much... my friend also wants to purchase it if it costs lowers to around RS 5000.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Great Product.&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I wanted to buy a dual sim smart phone within the range on 10K. This offered all the features i was looking for and even more. So inshort it will say it is value for money.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;This is the one of fast growing website forever .. so i believe&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;last time i ordered mobile phone in 10 hours i got the mobile.. i never forgot this site ..this website is valuable for us&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;EXCELLENT AND MARVOLOUS&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A GOT THE MATERIAL IN TIME AND THANKS TO ALL.FURTHER I WILL BE ALWAYS BE WITH AMAZON.KEEP IT UP....GIVE VARIETIES OF MATERILS WITH BEST RATES&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=16</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;battery backup is a matter of concern&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;gd phone....&lt;br&gt;need to improve on battery&lt;br&gt;perfmnce is gd..&lt;br&gt;spprts games..&lt;br&gt;gd phn at this price....i hav prchasd it at rs.8545 @ amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;this one is the most compact-able to all users ....it should give a great pleasure of using ..all android apps are supported easily..this could be right choice to buy an android mobile ...its cost is worthier than its quality ..its panal and facility of dual sim makes its awesome..very much easy to handle............../&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Features Bettery needs to Be Better. Overall better Model&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice Model, Only Battery could have been better Overall better Model, Its cheap and best I can say.... Thanks You&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Phone !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked the phone... not great but OK. When I bought the phone this was the best option I had. You may check Moto E at this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;great phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Quick service and genuine item, Pleased with the product. I would recommend amazon for better online purchase.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Cheers..!!!!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Superb phone in cheap rate&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Thanks to amazon for this wonderfull phone in cheap rate.Superb performance a big thanks to amazon for there service .&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;my S DUOS 2 GT-S7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is really a nice one... and it is more comfort than other mobiles. Simple to use and fit for a shirt.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone in attractive price !!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The display quality and touch sensitivity are extremely good.&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon for providing the product at a price much lower than market shops.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Review for Samsung Galaxy S Duos&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This phone is quite good in this range .Long battery and high speed .&lt;br&gt;The phone gets heated when plugged in power during charging,this is the only thing i dislike about this phone.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;5 star&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am fully satisfy with the product and Amazon.in. I have been buying from last few months. its just awesome&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=15</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 nice one&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Satisfied my expectations !! Definitely worth in this price range with all the features that one wants . Only downside is memory could have been little more&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is very good mobile, but battery back up is not up to the mark however not too good it is ok&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I liked this. good features, nice volume, good picture quality of camera.No hanging although my phone continuously connected to net. Really nice one.&lt;br&gt;Thanks to amazon, they delivered punctually within one day, as they promised.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good buy at affrdable range&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;excellent dellevry time with the product being reached to my residence within 3 days of placing the order with same being in good packaging and condition.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;good phone with additional disc on amex cards being a huge positive&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Value for money!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The battery durability is a little bit low...otherwise the overall features are satisfactory.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;#My ratings:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;1.Build quality:- 3.5/5 --&amp;gt; Build quality is good same like other Samsung other galaxy series.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;2. Processor:- 3/5--&amp;gt; Processor is ok. sometimes Lag or hang because of low ram but most of the times it is working fine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;3. Camera:- 4/5 --&amp;gt; Camera for this mobile is quite good at day time but night time with flash you can take good pictures. Video recording is also good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;4. Touch response:- 3.5/5 --&amp;gt; Touch response is quite good(butter-smooth). Typing is quite good.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5. Sound:- 3.5/5 --&amp;gt; Sound is crystal clear. You will be able to listen good music in loudspeaker and headphone mode as well. Voice call quality is very decent as it is having some other extra options like Clear sound/soft voice etc.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice Phone in this budget. Bought from amazon at its cheapest rates. Thank you amazon. Airtel offers 1 GB 3G data free for 3 months with this item and that's awesome  Only thing strange is that Samsung does not provide scratch guard and flip cover with its product. These are required for all Samsung phone to avoid the Samsung's delicate phone from scratches. But overall good phone in display, look and feel, managing apps.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;A great product at a great price&lt;br&gt;I AM THANKFUL TO AMAZON TO GOT RECEIVED PRODUCT THROUGH AMAZON.HOPE DO IN FUTURE&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;ram is not enough(762mb)&lt;br&gt;1gb may be enough&lt;br&gt;white colour is superb nd good apps&lt;br&gt;camera is clear&lt;br&gt;thats it&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;it's very good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It's wonderful opportunity to get good phone and compare to price also less in this way ....very good 100% genuine&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice Mobile in limited budget&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;When I decide to buy a mobile in limited budget then i have many option and many company but I believe in quality and after lot's of confusion I decide to buy Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=18</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Gr8 Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Value of money phone. if you want a branded phone under 10K with decent camera, good performance , good display  then go for it.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Cool Mobile&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;One of the best mobile in its category. Affordable and very easy to use. I will recommend it to everybody!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone to start with..&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It is a Good android phone for a beginner, cons: samsung should have given atlest 8 GB internal memory, almost 2 gb fills as system apps.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good phone, better than expected. Good call quality and easy to handle with one hand.Good camera too at this price range.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;great phone cheapest rate in the market.fast delievary more then expected well packed brand new with all equipments fully loaded&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A branded mid budget phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Well done Amazon!! safely packed and delivered on time. will recommend to all my friends. Keep it up. Good job done. A mid budget and comfortable specification of the mobile. happy with the performance....A small concern will be the battery,,apart from that, I like this product.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;samsung 7582&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;its a good product &amp;amp; memory and speed are like so you can buy this item eaisly thank you ok&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Perfect mobile at this rate!!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is my 1st smart phone and i feel this mobile is the best buy at this price. This mobile came up with Jelly Bean OS. Its almost 4 months since i buy. I didn't face any issues so far.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Things i like:&lt;br&gt;Large display&lt;br&gt;Good touch response&lt;br&gt;High clarity camera&lt;br&gt;Good battery life&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This mobile covered all my needs.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome phone with wonderful Amazon Service.. Loved it!!&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;This is the best phone I have ever used and truly a value for money. You can't get a product better then this within this price range. Specifications are awesome and phone delivers more than what you would have expected out of it. Worth every penny spent. I am loving it!! Amazon.. Hats off to your commendable service got my phone in less than 48 hours with an awesome packaging.. Keep up the good work!! :)&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Prompt &amp;amp; Efficient Service&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Order was promptly complied with in an efficient manner. It came nicely packed. I am happy having placed the order on this site.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=20</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Nice&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I think it is best &amp;amp; believable phone in this rate....use carefully....don't put much apps....refresh ram sometimes..by this we can avoid lags......&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;excellant android phone these budjet&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;nice phone display good sufficiant battery backup clear pics no hanging for playing games and apps net browser 2g also be happy totally best android in galaxy sduos 2&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;The Phone Was Good If U Want Budget Phone...&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I Was Happy To Purchase This Iten But Headset With My Galaxy S Duos 2 Was Reguler Type It Was Not Good...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;A decent hand set&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I wanted to go back to a smart phone after a long gap n I decided on it Thanks Amazon.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not upto my expectation&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this Samsung with great expectations, This was the first Samsung i was using, instantly i got to know this is not the phone i want to use, not user friendly and not many options to customise the phone in the way i want it. i returned the phone next day itself and will never buy samsung again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also please dont sell phones which are China made, i will not buy anything form Amazon which is made in China.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good for the price&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this product at a discounted price which is perfect and can be considered as a good choice. The look, tech and price, all are excellent. But being android, the alarm is mum when switched off, that is a good disappointment for me for I need it. The battery life is not up to expected. As a whole, it is worth buying.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;SATISFIED&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;It was timely delivered with all accessories and product as explained. Its working well yet. All is well. I recommend others to have it. Amazon offers most competitive prices.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I bought this phone one month before and it's working very well. Better option for low price. Thanks to Amazon to delivered with in a day with well packed. I'm satisfied to spend money for this mobile.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Good Entry level phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Good Entry level phone if someone is looking for branded smartphone like samsung better to spend that 2000 and buy this rather than going for star pro and trend&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Excellent Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;support 720p hd video recording,2560-1920 size stills,Very Important Feature :- Very High Earpiece Volume / Call Volume&lt;br&gt;In addition to High call volume , Samsung give a option "Adapt Sound" in Settings&lt;br&gt;which can further increase call volume according to your hearing capability.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=17</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item><item><reviews><value>&lt;b&gt;Awsm Cell Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Dis Cell Phone is just 2gud in dis budget..&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Advances Phone - Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;5Star Rated !!&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good handset&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;it is very good and best mobile. i like it.betery backup is very long and camra will be good and better&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Okay product from top smartphone manufacturer&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;At this price range you can get better choices from local manufacturers but this is from Samsung which gives you some mental satisfaction.&lt;br&gt;Let's talk about product:&lt;br&gt;Good camera in daylight.&lt;br&gt;Compact design.&lt;br&gt;Average android performance,not for powerusers.&lt;br&gt;Average battery performance.&lt;br&gt;Dual SIM support.&lt;br&gt;Nothing special about this phone...market is now flooded with these types of phones.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;satisfied and ok&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;The phone pack was great and the phone was amazing......I received it in great condition and I m completely satisfied with this product&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;your rates is high&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;so pls. down rates as per othersso pls. down rates as per othersso pls. down rates as per othersso pls. down rates as per others&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Amazon is doing good job,i got my product at right time and is good product i like service very much ,keep going on............&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;wow very good cellphone from Samsung in 8448 rs I bought. It is too good compare to first s duos. and it is fast. Thanks amazon to delivered in 2 days. I love your packaging style....&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Not beyond my expectations..averagely reached my expectation&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Nice..awesome...but very less charging backup...cool appearance. Fast performance..and it's colour is pretty...need to improve battery storage capacity..headphones not in ear..quite dissatisfied...&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;satisfaction&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;I am 80 percent satisfied with its performense but i 100 percent satisfied if its screen size is little bigger than this.&lt;/div&gt;</value><value>&lt;b&gt;Awesome Phone&lt;/b&gt;</value><value>&lt;div class="reviewText"&gt;Samsung at its best as usual,, the only thing where I am worrying is my pone is getting electric smell at the battery side when using, don't know if its common in all phones. Over all its okay.&lt;/div&gt;</value></reviews><link>http://www.amazon.in/product-reviews/B00H3YT1S8?pageNumber=19</link><title><value>Amazon.in: Customer Reviews: Samsung Galaxy S Duos 2 GT-S7582 (Pure White)</value></title></item></items>